Oh
Oh, I see
Hey guys
Back they go and hang out hang out
Yo psych I'm censored in your room your what I'm censored
Sensor YouTube censored me
Fuck you too. Yeah, that's what I say
So I'm stuck up here
Okay, well don't make out right now, but maybe later, okay, maybe later. Hey Dingo. Yo Dingo
Yeah, the only way I could talk is if I had a wrench, but that's all right. You don't have to
Really do you like you got a no, that's fine. No, no, I'm not asking you for a right
I'm just saying that's the only way I could type right now. Okay, you can take or what are you timed out?
No, no, I got censored YouTube senses me every now and then
I should I should uh mod you so you can take yeah, if you could take it away if you want after like an hour or two if you want
Are you planning on doing this shit with it? No, no, I don't do
What do you think I have, 5? What am I going to do?
Look guys, what do you think mods, I know, are members, mods and members I take seriously.
Oh my gosh, Mike.
It's weird that members aren't modded when they become members.
They should be modded, you know what I mean?
Well, but there's some members that are gifted memberships and they're they're trolls and they like you you look you look tired
That's true. I know I look terrible. I know I want medical. Is it what you tell me? Do you tell me? I know I look tired
Yeah, I don't know. I look terrible
Okay, you just rub it in JT. I'm gonna rub it in. Yeah
What's your name?
Oh, who am I again? It's been a long day
I've been along the name is BJ. Also. I'll tell you BJ from now
Okay, yo, yo, it's
What happened to me one day like 20 you were not able to chat
Yeah, it's destiny coming back two days dingo. That's a lot two days. Jesus
That's like happens to me for like maybe 20 hours
Destiny was like a little bit of an annoying person. I don't know. I don't like
You could be honest. Oh, she is
She was like you but then it's like then she started saying like, you know
Terroristic things. I just had the novelty wore off fast. Yeah, she's a terrorist. Oh, yeah
Wasn't that kind of like stuff on the resilient terrorist? Yeah
So I'll see up into my hip and goes out and I'll let you guys talk
No, it's like thanks for that reading earlier. The three years. That was perfect. I really wasn't
No, I was gonna get it on that but it was just too many people I was like
I have three of them do it
Slightly obese and the woman in the woman in the back back chat. That's a big signal. Oh shit
Slightly old woman. Oh my god
slightly obese ma'am ma'am
cover up ma'am
not even decent
I've never seen this guy smile one time
maybe that's a good thing
no no no no it's alright
forget I said anything
at least he has most of them
is it a grill?
No, oh, no, I think he had been here. Oh, no, he's frowning again. So happy. Look
You smile you he works at the airport
He's a luggage handler
Oh, he's there. He's obese leprechaun. Well, that's why he's so happy. I can see it. Yeah obese leprechaun
Simone I'm happy because I just had like six tacos six. Well
No, yeah, what kind of you know that place smells gotta meet us. I
Just had 26 tacos, so I'm more special
And I can make and I can make more I have more meat in the fridge like what happened man
He left us hanging there. Well, I know is because
That woman that I thought I was saying
bad things about America and so I cannot let you go.
Oh, that Destiny woman?
Oh, I just take her off the pan.
I told you she always drunk.
She's never sober.
Yeah.
Do you want to have your first gay experience with me?
Oh, then I'm straight.
Oh, you don't.
Come on, Seb.
Just do it.
Don't let him fool you.
He's just playing.
I see you, I see you, I see you, I see you, I see you, I see you, I see you, I see you, I see you, I see you, I see you, I see you, I see you, I see you, I see you, I see you, I see you, I see you, I see you, I see you, I see you, I see you, I see you, I see you, I see you, I see you, I see you, I see you, I see you, I see you, I see you, I see you, I see you, I see you, I see you, I see you, I see you, I see you, I see you, I see you, I see you, I see you, I see you, I see you, I see you, I see you, I see you, I see you, I see you, I see you, I see you, I see you, I see you, I see you, I see you, I see you
of the
and then put on like a thing that makes your ball hole look like a vagina.
Yeah, you know what? I think they're going to fucking Sebastian have a good time with that.
What? I better look at you with that.
I got to tell you that, that's not a good fear, it does look good, you gotta shake that thing.
I'm down.
Oh, I'm sorry
You would look better if you shave that thing
Your opinions you guys don't have your cameras on so I don't think
You guys the gay show on YouTube look we have sick
JT God the gayest person here. I was actually the leader
I was the leader of the Gay Pride Parade in New York City for several years.
I think me and Gari are the only street people on the panel right now.
Psyche, you didn't know that about me.
Psyche, you think so negatively of me, Psyche?
You think so negatively of me, but I'm actually, I was the leader of the Gay Pride Parade.
Oh, my God. In New York City, in 2016.
What do you want to win? In 2016, I was a leader.
What did you do? What did you do in the parade?
No, I don't want a medal.
I just want Psyche to give me some ta-ta.
Tick, are you on drugs right now?
You on gay points from Psyche?
Huh? Are you on drugs, sir?
No, why would I be on drugs?
Psyche, Psyche, just go one-on-one with Sebastian.
I don't need drugs.
Ah!
Yeah, you're right.
Oh, man, you sound like you're impaired.
You're like under the influence of something.
the
That's crazy confess
Confess
And I ain't gay no more
Keep going. I was gay, and I ain't gay no more pray it away. It's a song, huh?
Yeah, see you
We want to help you detox. We'll pay for your treatment. What do you think is what any treatment you think?
I'm a fucking paper your your you think that I'm a bitch. You think I need to go like nigga
Niggas you know, it's our
Needs the detox. What do you think is more depressed than him or him?
Signor Sebastian. Who's more depressed? Oh, he's more depressed know how to present
Well, I think you underestimate the Sebastian's depression. No, no, no, no, yeah, don't ask me my depression. Oh, it's very very strong
Tell us about your depression Sebastian
That's bad man. It's not good
Huh, it's not easy man. What's so bad about it?
Hard to talk about it guys. No, no, it's okay. You're you're here, you know, you're in a safe space
What's so bad about it?
those of those of those of those of those of those of those of those of those of those of those of those of those of those of those of those of those of those of those of those of those of those of those of those of those of those of those of those of those of those of those of those of those of those of those of those of those of those of those of those of those of those of those
All my depression so bad. I had to think about filing for bankruptcy man twice
Didn't you mean in the business that you don't have? Yeah. Yeah, my label section search your business. I had to
Consider bankruptcy is my only option
Because we're not doing good man. We we're offering 40 to 6% off. It's costing us man. And we're not making it
Shit, it's just me now. I don't even know how long I'm gonna last up here
Oh, fuck
Sigma you look focused man, what I saw the blinking light
It's not a charge it again
Hey, what's up, Jamie
Just leave it there just leave it like just like that
Well, neither of you
Individuals have your cameras on so I
Don't know
As much as much as I as much as I would like to take your judgments to heart
You guys don't have your cameras on fuck you in Europe. So it's every everything that you say
Like, you're saying like, you're this and you're that.
But I can't tell unless you have your camera on for me to see and assess myself,
you're just talking shit, meanwhile you could be doing a whole lot worse for me.
Why do they all have this weird camera? Why are you afraid to turn your camera on?
Why are you afraid to have a pseudonym that's not as vague as the term God?
This is what they like to do. This is all the whole community is like this
It's like a camera community is fucking queer and maybe you should ask yourself
why do you wear that hat all the time, that's what I asked my son
He's never gonna admit to why he drinks. He's just gonna say oh, you don't came up
Cam down no a lot of these fuckers need to came down
It should be a law how did van god get here how did anybody get here
Thank God, how'd you get here? Oh, God see what?
talk about transportation. Oh
Who brought you here somebody brought you
Let's talk about this who told you about this fucking sanctum
Okay, that's no longer a sanctum. No, it's the fucking desecration
Oh, shit. So Vanguard, what brings you to a place like this at a time?
A Sanctum. A Sanctum Cemorium.
Yeah, you know what that is. So what brings you here tonight?
Mates, mate. I don't call you a mate.
I'm not your mate.
Really, you're a mate.
No chance.
No, he put him in the back
For now for now he's coming back
Maybe you have you talked to signal yet
Right now I've seen this guy all over the place is a bit of a balance
Yeah, it's a bit of a villain. What do you think about that signal? You think about this vanguard fella you like him?
I don't really, I'm not concerned with other people's what they're doing.
I'm not really concerned about whether I like someone or not.
Psyche knows this.
What are you concerned about?
Many things, none of which concern you.
What is it that draws you to a place like this?
Psyche, you would be a lot better at doing this if you were on a computer.
Oh shit am I back god damn I never know what I'm here. I was over there fucking browsing
What what exactly what format is this what can we do in?
So go to the lobby
It's anybody else here and glorify thy name
What only holy
For all nations shall come and worship before thee, for thy judgments are made manifest.
And after that I looked, and behold, the temple of the tabernacle of the testimony in heaven was opened.
And the seven angels came out of the temple, having the seven plagues, clothed in pure and white linen, and having their breasts.
Peter, are you reading Revelation right now?
Fuck is what even it? You know what? I'm not even gonna question it. I don't know what the fuck is going on here, but I like it
You know, and I forget putting the backstage again, I'll accept that
So revelations of what?
The the revelation of Jesus Christ what Jesus
Fella noisome and grievous sore upon the men which
I don't know because everyone's gone insane. I
Mean I go to one person
They're speaking like they're an insane person. I go to the next person. They're speaking like they're an insane person
I try I try talking them to each other
They sound insane talk to
I'm talking, I don't know, who are these people?
Why am I dealing with these people?
Sigg, come back.
I've gotty, JB, or JT, and Vanguard.
Who are these people?
One guy's trying to sell liposuction on my chat.
No one's saying, hey, like, share, subscribe
to my channel.
No, he's just talking about 40% of the liposuction.
I don't need liposuction.
God, what are you doing? You're self-promoter
JT, what are you guys doing?
guys
Someone someone before I let anybody out. I did someone needs a don't even remember shit. I'm sorry
I'm just gonna go to bed. I don't even care anymore
These people are here without
Don't it so I feel better about having these people because they're not doing anything for my show except
Arguing it. I don't like what they're saying. Yes
So I'm saying it headpiece, you know, like you don't have to donate remember saying
I'll let one at a time someone donates a membership. I'll let God JT and Vanguard up
Her membership go by if not, I'll just go to bed. It's fine. I
Don't feel like having them on anymore. They're all bothering me all of them
What is God's God? God is reading
the Bible
JT is
He's questioning my thing.
Vanguard, he's trying to sell his life protection
on my show.
I'm not part of the coupon.
Again, do I get a commission when they say
psyche awakens for the coupon?
No.
Okay, I don't want to be part of that.
No, they're not going to.
They're not going to.
They're not supporters of the show. I mean, it's like please it was like how is it you know, you think it would be worth
You know, just telling you here. Here's guys channel. Here's bad guy channel. Here's to you. You send a reason she hurts
Yeah, come on reach guys. I'll donate one more membership today. It's someone if some three people don't it
I can't do it
Other than one more
okay every little bit helps yes it does yeah okay come on just talk about okay
Vanguard drop zone okay
no okay so i'm sorry guys god and jc i'm sorry nobody wanted nobody wanted you
want to continue on this oh look everyone's left now she's
everyone on my show
so it's a device
But Joe, are you Joe? What is wrong? Why are you so far up six butthole?
You didn't think anything but you think you know
That's the point you didn't do anything
You're what's that?
Let me one see more guests on the show
I feel like people hate me sometimes.
I was gonna go to bed.
I want you to use the sleep stream.
It is not, and yet is.
And here is the mind which hath wisdom.
The seven heads are seven mountains, on which women siteth.
And there are seven kings, which are now fallen.
And the other is not yet come.
And when he cometh, he must continue a short pace.
And the beast that was, and is not, even he is eighth,
and is of the seventh, and goth into perdition.
And the ten horns which thou sawth are ten kings, which have received no kingdom as yet,
but receive power as kings one hour with the beast.
These have one mind and shall give their power and strength unto the beast.
These shall make war with the lamb.
So you guys are getting a free Bible study right now. It's time to donate. Okay. It's time to reach into your pockets and
It's time to pull out something. Okay. I
Don't give a shit what it is. It could be two dollars. Maybe
Maybe one dollar
And we'll reach into your hearts right now and shout out the flesh and burn her fire
For God had put in their hearts to fulfill his will and to agree and give their kingdom on
I missed everything I missed all the fucking readings and everything. Oh
Can we bring him back to listen to the to the book of Revelation? I
Feel like psych psyche. I feel like you're not liking this. He's denied me
He's denied the fucking revelation of God. What's wrong with you, psyche?
You know, I give the revelation damn it
You have forsaken me. Yeah, bless it are all those that they hear. Yeah
Crazy dude
Free blessing dude
Thought I'd give a little back to you since you've given so much. Yeah, it's not much, but you know
What do you mean? It's not much. You know what it is. I'm being modest, okay?
But a lot
It's the power hour, that's right Dingo what God's
he fell asleep and now it's just us oh shit all right back to the book
and the woman which thou sawth and after these things i saw another
it's like grip that i he doesn't like it it's good for you it's good for you psyche
of the earth are waxed rich through the abundance of her
Oh, okay. I'm back
Say, what's going on man? I want to talk to you psyche. I want to know how psyche's doing today
Reward her even as she rewarded you and double unto her double according to her works
In the cup which she had filled filled to her double
How much
She hath glorified her and lived deliciously so much torment and sorrow give her
For she's saint in her heart. I sit a queen and I'm no widow and shall see no sorrow
Therefore shall her plagues come in one day death and mourning and famine and she shall be utterly burned with fire
For strong is the Lord God who judges her
the
and purple and silk and scarlet and gold and wood
and all manner of vessels of ivory and all manner of brass and brass and brass and brass and brass and iron
and cinnamon, and odors, and ornaments, and frankincense, and wine, and oil, and fine flour, and wheat, and beasts, and sheep, and horses, and chariots, and slaves, and souls of men, and the fruits that thy soul has lusted after departed from there, and all things which were dainty and godly are departed from there.
offer her fear of her torment, wheat being and wailing, and saying alas, alas, the great city,
purple and scarlet and deck with gold, precious stones and pearls."
What are you reading from there? A book?
Your mother. I'm reading from your mother's ass. How about that?
Yeah, you like that? You like that fucking sub? I'm reading from your mother's ass. This is all
tattooed on her ass.
it's been inscribed on her ass cheeks
for what
Dottie, you've been transferred to personnel
the riches has come to naught, and every shipmaster and all the company and ships and sailors and many as trade by sea stood a far off
and cried when they saw the smoke of her burning saying, what sea
like, share and subscribe
alas
all the ships to sea by reason of her costliness
one hour she is made desolate
rejoice over her
Thou heaven and ye holy apostles and prophets for God hath avenged you on her
Holy Apostles and a post and a mighty angel took up a stone like a great
You could do what?
He's out of his mind
He's been transferred to personnel
Like share and subscribe to psych for more entertaining content
No, you say it, huh? Of course, JT. What have you done for a psychic? Have you contributed any donations? I have
What the fuck have you done money talks JT money talks? Oh, yeah, let's talk about money
I have you stole like ten thousand dollars from that disabled woman money talks and B.S. Y
He stole ten thousand canary in lies lies and nonsense
Alex
What are you gonna do to me if I you pull me over and I've been speeding on the freeway
What are you gonna do to me? I'm gonna say sir
Registration I'm gonna pretend it's bad. I'm gonna say step out of the car
And I'm gonna throw you in the bushes in the bushes. I'm gonna fuck the shit on you in the bushes
Okay, oh my god. I'm gonna end up in the trees on the side of the highway
I'm gonna fucking just give it to you and then that's it my man
I'm gonna make hot coal and just go my way
In the trees, but on the side of the highway
I'm gonna fucking just give it to you and then that's it my man
I'm gonna make top call and just go on my way unless you want to go to jail
I can just can't cuff you ticket to jail or I can fuck you on the side of the highway
It's up to you my man. Okay. Hey guys everyone Alice be controversial
But Alice, he's a sweet guy. He's a sweet guy.
I'm very sweet. I'm a sweetheart.
I'm a lollipop. You can lick me like a lollipop.
How many licks does it take to get to the middle of a tootsie, pop?
Alex, can I try can I can I lick your tootsie pop Alex? Oh, yeah, baby. Oh my god, okay
I got I love this guy. This is good. He's my cutie buddy. He's my he's my cutie buddy
He gets in that you in the police uniform he handcuffs you to bed and he f's that f out of me
So, Psyche, what's going on? You can't sleep tonight, huh?
Hey there, Psyche.
I don't see anything on the screen. I only see a picture.
why you do this everywhere you go you always fuck up the fucking vibe why are you doing
best everything up tonight everything is going fine with me and god you're in the
town what are you doing what what what what what listen this is what he wants he wants this
we what we've learned from today is that flirty diamond and raging demon have are
carrying on in a fucking full gay erotic affair okay
And for some reason salmon is jealous as fuck about the whole thing.
Salmon came in here trying to fucking cock block demon like crazy.
Then Bita came storming in trying to get in on the action and it turned into this big fucking fuckfest
Everybody was just fucking yelling about everything and everybody was getting super gay and trying to say they weren't gay
And then I guess Sam was watching Psyche shower backstage
30 diamond and raging demon according to her
They were just watching movies together and jerking off together, but nobody was buying it. Everybody thinks they're in this fucking
big passionate e-romance and the whole fucking thing was going crazy and then
gay e-origin super gay everything was going super gay and then i guess
eldo came in and he was getting into the gay action with psyche
it was just one big fucking gay fucking orgy it's a big gay fest
that's what psyche wanted he was enjoying the fuck out of that
he really enjoyed that shit and that's what brought the viewers he went from
16 viewers to fucking 86 viewers
Alright, so apparently that's what's bringing all the action for sake. He's like he loves it when it gets like that
He loves the gay drama like a drama. Yeah loves that. Yeah, he loves that. He's fucking absolutely loves all right
Well, all you know, yeah, that's what you guys want. You get everybody wants gay drama in here
They don't want the Lord Word of God. They want gay drama. That's what you're gonna get. Okay?
Well, all you e gangsters you closeted homosexuals come up here and do you do you come on up Seb is waiting for you
We'll leave and now and you guys can have no panel. Yeah
Just come on up. Well, as soon as somebody comes up, I'll leave I'll get off thing
I'll definitely let you have it. That's it. You guys can have you can slob over each other
You can whip out your wings and just have a fucking
possible little Jedi battle with each other whatever you want to do
We'll just leave it's like you can sit there and have a big fucking grin on his face. Yeah
No, I missed all that
No, no, I'm glad I'm glad I did you're lucky you missed that shit. Yeah, it wasn't pretty man
No, when it came to the gay dramas, I just it just I just doesn't hold my interest
I got a front. Yeah, it would be cut a little too heated and it's nothing we haven't heard before
It's like the 20th time. It's the same stories came up over and over again
Well, God little interesting was the prostitute. Yeah, it was weird tonight
Some prostitute came in and she started
Given her trauma story about what happened to I wasn't really listening. She just
The prostitute and flirty diamond was a prostitute and then summer apparently was a prostitute
Wait, Goddy, let me ask something to do
You're gonna stream anymore what's happening stream for what stream for who yeah streaming anymore was going on with your stream there
I would be the reason what would be the purpose I'm asking you what I'm asking you are you's gonna stream or not
I mean you're not streaming anymore like what's going on with you. He's not interested in gay drama said it's
Not gonna stream anymore. That's what you're saying. I was pretty clear. Yeah, I'm not interested in gay drama
I don't know any other way to say that. Oh, I know that I know you're not streaming anymore
There's enough gay drama. You're coming here now
Well, you're looking for a discount are you?
Looking for a discount, but you're not willing to contribute
I've contributed more than you you're looking for a free pass. Aren't you GT?
Yeah, like a $10,000 free pass from a disabled and looking for drama aren't you well you'll find it
Did you know that money what you do with that money? Well, give it to you GT. Where'd you spend that money you got from Chrissy, huh?
There'll be certain conditions though. Let's answer my fucking questions asshole. No, Gotti
I'm busy with GT right now. Take a number. What you do with that?
You saw that money away
the
Yeah, he had no fucking money left everybody that he had to go buy a mattress, right? How'd he get that mattress home?
He took it on a public bus
He took a mattress on a public
Yeah, you're just I can kill you
You're jealous I'm stronger than you
Apparently you can't carry mattress you got the bus
Yeah
No, he stole 10k for a mentally disabled woman called it a donation
No, those are lies. Don't need to help me out when I was going through hard time
Bankruptcy from one of my lab businesses there 10 K. Can you imagine that?
God, yeah, JT you gotta stop bringing that up man. No, those are lies man
Some new material there you stop babbling for a fucking second. Let me get the story out
Did you hear what happened to Monica at the bowling alley? Did you know that?
That's true. What happened to her the bowling alley. She went to the bowling alley
Yeah, with a group of people off of here
Yeah, I heard about that and she had some nachos before she was bowling
She fucking just shit a fucking white
She was wearing white pants and she fucking shit all over the white pants. It was like diarrhea
It was fucking like Niagara Falls of shit
They closed that lane and they never used it again lane seven at the bowling alley
Well, she's lifted and busted her ass on it. Yeah, yeah
they had to put a f***ing coat down in the seat
God, imagine being done, would you like to be married to Monica?
No, I'd rather kill myself, are you?
I've seen a picture of her, man, she's like 600 pounds, man
and she doesn't want to get lipo-sucks, are you certain?
Can you believe that?
But she has the face of a f***ing rock
She's got a she's got a small brain, but she's got a huge body at that
I don't get a small brain and a
Fucking mouth. He's got a very tiny body, but a big mouth and a big fat body a
Perfect Kennedy for light blood section surgery though. Nonetheless. I can make a living off of her
I can pay off a few bills a few months with the bills with her absolute fucking shit show
I'm telling you
Look who else is there your ex-girlfriend Tiffany
Yeah, she's here. Did you see what she did with her? She blocked me man. She blocked. I don't even see her
Actually, yeah
Yeah, did you see that said what she did with her dog? Show me that again? I forgot
Let me show you that what she did with her dog. So you're not gonna like it
Do you have any unblock me at once so you're not gonna get the discount for liposuction?
He might like it actually
Where is it where the fuck is that picture and by the way?
I'm not in love with her anymore, man. I got over her a long time ago. Why what happened?
You were fucking praising her fucking. No, no, I didn't appreciate me. I gave her many a leg
I gave her like such a
You didn't like her digging in her ass on fucking on the street
I gave her such publicity and advertising man, and she didn't appreciate you know
I mean her more beautiful than she can ever
She didn't appreciate it though and she tried to make me look bad and she tried to throw me under the
What are you gonna ask fetish tiff? You're always digging in your ass. What's up with that?
No, she told she threw me out of the bus man, and she didn't deserve it. She doesn't deserve my my kindness and my
Digging my friendship in your ass. This is my friend sleep. Did he fall asleep? I don't know. Yeah, he fell asleep
He said this to see me did oh
Okay, I'm tired. Just see him on the panel. I saw yeah, he was fucking used way to go to look at his eyes
His eyes were like I don't like any of these people's
We ate all that food and just fucking passed the fuck out. It's like what are they talking about?
I've got bigger fish to fry than Disney though. I
Don't know why she just doesn't admit that she's a fucking freak and she fucks well. She wants the attention man
She wants to
She more or less did you know, she's into the
Totally into it. She has the fucking where we'll finish all right. She watches where we'll porn. That's one
Two she has these paw prints on her shoulders at the top of each shoulder. That's two three
She has a giant dog that she fucks every day. That's I think it's shadow. I like her dog tires though
It's a nice dog. Nice dog. All right, four. She has a nice you dog
He's excited fucking the dog. This is all fucking on taste a very nice dog very lovely
Stop denying you dogs. Tiffany. This is what you do and this is what we know you do
All right, so you can say whatever the fuck you want to say you fuck your dogs
Hold up real quick. Let me see. What's thank us. Thank you. It sucks, man. Thank you another dog fucking dude
What's with all you dog fuckers? Yeah, this thing got sucky. He's been doing it too. Yeah, look look
He has a picture of his fucking boyfriend
Good old Bowser. What are you doing up at sport 15 a.m. You know what she's doing
She's getting ready for the fucking grind to target getting ready to go to work at Target
I just have this working the food court apparently. Oh, it does see even worse
I mean she wouldn't work for the food court. I think will you let her around any food? No way, man
of the
Fucking that maybe she does maybe she's just cleaning the floors. Maybe she's like the janitor. I don't know
You know like the people that say hi to you when you get to the door. They don't have that a target
That's only we don't got that a target
What do you do Tiffany? Can you tell us that what exactly is that you do a target Tiffany wears t-shirts more like Tiffany wears a muzzle
Tiffany wears a big mouth
Tiffany wears very cheaper clothing show her face so we can get a good look at Tiffany
Tiffany wears very cheap clothing and doesn't appreciate her fans why we're not fucking embellishing the story
that maybe one day she's gonna be less narcissistic and obsessed with herself
Tiffany go fuck yourself you fucking clown bitch look at your face this is
why you're such a miserable cunt because you got this fucking dopey man face in
bread man face come on nobody gives a fuck what you do in life
god Gary doesn't care what you do in life
the
What's that? Oh, no, you've been doing don't do it. Don't do it
Good girl. Don't do it. Don't do it. And she's done enough to
Mind we're talking about him. This is a married woman. We're talking about that picture. She showed that picture on her thing
what a fuck I told you she loves the attention man and she loves the attention that that's desperation right there
Gary love her too
Oh fuck
You can't chop her head off first before you do it
Eat my ass
Wow, really, that's why we had to transfer you down to personnel is this what you're doing for attention now Tiffany. What the fuck
Holy shit, man. Tiffany. I'm very very disappointed with you. Actually. Yeah, very disappointed
You lost everything
You've locked the block. You know that black dog. She has shadow. Yeah. Yeah. Oh shadow is his name, huh? Yeah
Toddie, why do you think she got transferred down to personnel? She's lost the blood. Oh long time ago, bro
Yeah, there man
Jesus she's whoring herself. She wants the attention. I think YouTube's favorite whore
Very disappointing Tiffany favorite married whore married. Oh, sorry married whore. Yes
It's most disappointing though the most disappointing thing of her. She doesn't appreciate her fans are really good fans, you know
Dude shit on two thousand of her subscribers. She's pissed. Oh, I know I heard
The same thing pissed them away for what for this
for this shit
What the hell?
She only tries to suck up to her lip-tart friends there her little lip-tart circle of Angie and Monica and other people like that
Dumb people with nothing in the brain people that need liposuction surgery. Oh, you only got nothing inside their heads there
Absolute shit show
You know, it's amazing man. They they they got tiny brains, but they got big mouths
Well, that's all they're good for is fucking barking. Yeah
of the
and let's not forget the crying old man that shows up under like 50 million different old accounts
Oh, he must be here too. Tom. What's Tom doing there?
He's creeping around being a weirdo. I don't you guys just call him Tom already stop calling. I'm Joel Wiggin
I
Call him Carlisle. Yeah
That would get old Carlisle a picture on YouTube this guy
My favorite account with them as a trash man account with a green garbage truck riding dirty writing dirty. I tell you green garbage truck man
Best looking garbage truck you've ever seen I
Think it's only a matter of time before he's gonna get fired from target
Did you have something to say?
He usually just does a hoot and hoot and hoot.
Yeah, he makes little noises and shit like hoot.
Little buzzes and whirs. He's like a human robot.
Yeah.
My question to you, have you ever been down to the Crazy River?
Wait until I tell psyche on you. I'm gonna record this so I can play for psych
What's she gonna tell like
The case you can't tell I'm being sarcastic you stink Tiffany
Could you read that last one back to me you stink smell you know, she fucking smells. Oh, yeah
It's in man this old couple, you know, they were on the verge of tears because of me apparently
You know, I told you when I told Tom, I don't think his marriage is gonna last more than three to six months
You molested his daughter, dude. I give him more than six months for that marriage
Everybody did how long you think that marriage is gonna last?
As long as it needs to until it fucking explodes. Why would a 37 year old woman marry a 67 year old guy?
Is she after his money or is it was a couple bucks?
She might get a new tooth out of it. Yeah, I should get a couple teeth a couple of dollars more
Yeah, no, this is a match made in heaven right here like this right here
coupled with with this
perfect
I'm telling you man. There's something wrong about that picture. He doesn't fit and she's after something
Look at her face and tell me she's not after something. She's after his house or she's after something some kind of insurance thing
You put God he put it back I missed it
But this
Was that?
That's the guy you know the guy
from New York know the guy with the
Wonder the thing. Yeah with the guy the other guy. I don't know that girl. You know with the guy
Yeah, that dude with the guy with the long hair
The Puerto Rican one with the long hair money. Yeah, it's like a girl
You know what he's talking about, you know that guy
Tiffany says I triggered them all know you didn't trigger no one to think I think if anyone's triggered. It's you her smell triggered me. Yeah
the
Tiffany I'll give you to the count of three to get your lion low down stealing for flushing Cargis out my door
Pump your guts will
Another one that's from home alone to
Remember that home alone to he was watching that movie. That's the guy that says that to the other person
Well you are here right now waifern
Tiffany you need to pay for your pizza. Yeah, why weren't you are here? What are you doing?
What are you talking about? Why we don't even know who the fuck you are dude. You're nobody
Well, I know who you are. You know who Wyvern is. That's that's not why we're that can't be Wyvern
Yeah, you think that's why we're it sure is
Yeah, Joe. I mean this
Physical proof of her doing it to
What's that?
What?
What's tough the background sound? I don't hear anything
What what background there's nothing
That doesn't matter
See talking about
Anyway, Tiffany, she's looking to get into that liposuction series that I got the brand new machine, but I don't know man
I'm gonna be able to help her though
I'm gonna be a law for that discount
Not after the way she has treated me
shameful
If this is what you wanted. This is what you get
You'll need to pay full price Tiffany the cost will be substantial on the refund policies to be prohibited
What the name of the father the mother and the holy spirit and the mother
I know what she's watching. She's lurking without us. She doesn't even exist
She's filming this whole thing. God he without us. He doesn't even exist
She lives for the drama and the attention. She's gonna play this for JC and everybody. Oh, yeah, look what they did
Look what they're doing. Oh, yeah, she'll tell them to the
Tiffany how can you conduct yourself in such a manner
What kind of married woman would do something about a married woman is putting pics out like this and the husband's just sitting in the back like a
Yes, man, like uh-huh. Yeah
Yeah, yeah, I thought it was great. Oh
Oh, he loves it. He says
I wanted to take the picture myself. Yeah
Up to where he's afraid he's gonna lose her or something. Can I yeah, please sort yourself out more collect more dick pics? Yeah
Yeah
That's what she did. What an embarrassing display by Gary. You know somehow you got worse
How do you factor that in?
As a human being you just think to a new love
Tiffany the lipo suction zapper
7,000 I got the 8,000 right now
Brand new machine state-of-the-art technology just for you Tiffany for your love handles and the fact that you're not able to get rid of
By working out either she doesn't eat lipo suction. She needs facial reconstruction
all that too.
Because she's going to need more than 60% off on that.
Yeah, well, she's concerned with her body, though, more than her face.
She really needs to get rid of that stubborn fabric.
She's come to the conclusion that working out is cheaper than plastic surgery,
and I give her that.
It is, but...
the
If we find your wife
No fucking way
You know I tried to make her look good by taking pictures screenshot pictures her
I made her more beautiful than she can make herself. I mean nobody she didn't appreciate that so now
I don't know if I want to do her another favor. I think twice before I give her another favor
the
of my concern that I've got bigger fish to fry
that's a perfect candy for liposuction surgery as a matter of fact
excellent candidate, prime candidate
you can't get about 20%
20 pounds right off of her man and one single procedure
I give it this look
this is my expression right here
so how's hanging JT, how's your girlfriend?
I was gonna say how's your girlfriend, but you know, she's not around
Been waiting for a girl like her
You know waiting for a girl like you
I would
I think you could
I could have got her
If I was living in her state I could have got her
You could get her
Look at this
You could bag that easily
You wouldn't want to hook up with this come on
I would have hooked up with her compared to other people
I've seen worse
There's worse out there right
I'm saying I think you could have a good time
I've seen worse but I've seen better
No
you don't like the little thing, the little accessory on the lip
I don't care if she's missing any teeth, to be honest, I don't care about the teeth
I forget the teeth, I'm saying that, what would you do with that one?
Who's overrated, who needs teeth?
You don't need teeth
That's not nice to me, you know, once she showed me her feet on camera, she showed them to me after I asked her
I didn't get a good shot of them
You didn't get a good, you know, I asked her and she showed them to me, she took off her socks and she showed them to me
No, let's talk about wart play
They were great, but they didn't suck
Would you suck on her wart?
on the bottom of the
the
of the
I give her maybe a six to seven. Maybe it was a quick glance. I didn't get a good look
I've rewinded it
Remember when she was in the attic hanging in the attic like a
Yeah, I remember that in the attic. Yeah, that was a long time ago. Yeah, that was back in the day
So what's a dot were you creeping around the whole time or were you just wait? No, no Tiffany called it
is that how that works
Oh there she is, she's in the site chat now, watching us
She's still using your picture
That's what they were doing
I'm telling Dougie
It was very generous of you to show me your feed that one time
Dougie, Dougie, here's the
Wait until Dougie Doug finds out about this
Dougie, how's the marriage going with Tom? How's it going there?
How's it working out with Tom so far?
Oh Carlisle. Carlisle must be happy as hell. She's cooking for him every morning. Yeah, but how are you there? Are you happy though, Dot?
Are you happy? Alicia, what's going on with that? Well, she's making a TV dinners every day. It's going great.
Hey, TV dinners are good, man. They're really hungry to hit the spot. And if he's really good, he gets a hungry man.
Oh, a hungry man dinners. I used to buy one that used to be less expensive back in a few days, a few years ago.
the brown yes with the brownie in the car
brownie brownie
and sometimes she'll even butter the mashed potatoes
and the corn
who doesn't want the brownie
you know the buffalo chink of fingers
they were the best remember that
that's great
I used to buy them I tell you I used to buy them
they used to be $1.99 now they're like $5.99
that's it I'm telling
way too expensive guys for frozen dinners
way too expensive a big rip off
the
that's that's that's that's that's that's that's that's that's that's that's that's that's the
he's he's doing something isn't he
of course he's doing something you know what he's doing
he's undercover
we can't say it here because it's very
well I don't want to say what he's doing but
it's very bought in what they say
anyways Alicia it was very generously that time
when you showed me your feet I do appreciate that
I did appreciate that
do you like that
who JT showed you his feet
No, I'm talking to Alicia in the chat man. Oh, Alicia. Oh, you show me your feet that one time
But now she's married so forget her. She's off the market
Now why do you say Alicia when everybody's saying Alicia?
Alicia, let's see whatever
well, it's funny how people hear one thing for like a
Thousand years and then all of a sudden they got to change the pronunciation
What are people called Tom the draw a wig and I find it silly
Why don't you just call him Tom and stop the nonsense rules around here?
Okay, you know some people need to stop the nonsense and start to talk business
There's always fucking rules that rules
Remind to be broken rules have to be followed that needs to be order
These broken wings
the
or what about passion 1980
The great song like that song. Don't you GT. It's a great song. It's an awesome song Rod Stewart, man
He did some good songs in the 80s. My sister died a couple weeks ago. This is in memoriam
That's the pieces that's Hannah
What that's a picture Hannah, isn't it? That's my sister asshole. What are you fucking trying to say?
That's not your sister. Is that your sister? That's my sister. She died
That's my no, that's my fucking sister. She died a few weeks ago. Oh, yeah. Oh, I'm not sure I thought it was
I thought that looked like Anna. No, that's Denise. Oh
I don't know if you're being serious. Anyways, Mike and doles is to you. Thank you, sir. Thank you. Appreciate it
You know that I
Didn't know that no, I don't know everything man. That's Denise Scottie. Yeah, I had no idea. That's true. That's true. I had no idea
What's that? It's my cousin pose. Oh, that's Anna. That's Anna. Come on. I don't know. I know that's that's Anna
I'm on your channel man. Oh, it's an armpit. Oh, sorry
All right, it's an armpit. No, that's and I knew it was Anna. I knew you were lying. I knew it
All right, Pete bitch
What's Tiffany doing up at 4 3 7 a.m. If she says she works you want to know what she's doing
Why she up? You know why she's not able to sleep or she's spying on
She can't resist being up to listen to if her name is mentioned at least one she loves to hear the sound of her
Of our voice you're right does
She loves my voice I
Saw her looking at me one time with her bedroom eyes. Oh
Shit, did she give you the look I gave her the look of love man
the look of lost the look of lost the look of lost the look of lost the look of lost the look of lost the look of lost the look of lost the look of lost the look of lost the look of lost the look of lost the look of lost the look of lost the look of lost the look of lost the look of lost the look of lost the look of lost the look of lost the look of lost the look of lost the look of lost the look of lost the look of lost the look of lost the look of lost the look of lost the look of lost the look of lost the look of lost the look of lost the look of lost the look of lost the look of lost the look of lost the look of lost the look of lost the look of lost the look of lost the look of lost the look of lost the look of lost the look of lost the look of lost the look of lost the look of lost the look of lost the look of lost the look of lost the look of lost the look of lost the look of lost the look of lost the look of lost the look of
this is this is what makes tiffani happy
as you need to stop these games that tiffani with a drama in the nonsense and the attention seeking
you need to grow up and stop that and focus on your life
and don't do this anymore whatever this is don't do that
what was that what was she doing in that picture i saw that picture i was wondering what she was doing
she was digging in her ass what does it look like she's doing
good grief man what were you thinking tiffani
that
the law's got him
of the
What are you ever gonna pay that woman back that 10,000? That's a lot of money to can't pay her back man
It was a donation. That was four years ago, man. She gave it to me now. She got her money back
I told people that she got it back at like three years ago man with her welfare checks every month donation of ten thousand dollars
Yeah, but other one shot man
Another one shot and a bunch of small installments of like 200 300 400 stuff like that
the
what do you think, you don't think that's good, I was working for my company, I was then the CEO and president of StrikeForce, and things were going well, but that's some financial problems
well, you know
came across some financial difficulties
but your depression is better, right?
how's it going, platform boots?
now my depression is going terrible and my depression is going pretty bad right now
well, when you look at this face, does it make you feel just a little bit better?
the
you know i took some better pictures of tiffany myself when i did the screenshots personally
look bad that was the best you were gonna that's the best you were ever gonna make her
i took some of the best-looking screenshot pictures of tiffany that anyone's ever seen
and she never even gave me the credit for that some appreciation uh well what did you give her
you didn't give her anything he's got no appreciation whatsoever man no appreciation i boosted her
popularity for that for that one no dick pics no nothing what are you giving her you're not giving
I'm not giving her any of that
That's for sure. She won't be getting that it from me
She's not gonna be getting that whatsoever
No special treatment she'll be given no leeway whatsoever
I boosted her popularity that one week when she went on GT's I mean the JC stream and she tried to throw me on the bus
I remember that
the
I'm just neither one really gives a shit be honest. I don't know
Which one beautiful they're both beautiful
Let me just okay a you know when you're at the eye doctor a or b
one or two
One yeah or two. I don't know that's pretty pretty sexy man in her prime. She was very sexy in her prime
Well, she's doing her prime actually. Well, so you're saying you would go with with be then, right?
I don't know man. I don't know Tiffany's not too bad looking herself
But that's only because I made her beautiful through the screenshot maker. Did you make her beautiful?
You know, I think I'm maybe the only one that's ever made her beautiful because some of her pictures are not too flattering
What what do you mean? What not too flattering? I've seen her ain't too flattering
Well, I wouldn't understand. What do you mean? And I was kind enough to give her some flattering pictures
But no, she didn't appreciate that. You know what sometimes you can't please everybody some guys of all the luck
Some guys of all the pain
What do you think some guys get all the brakes JT some guys do nothing but complain. Well, you know the speaking of complainers
She got this one here. What do you think is what's going on with this guy right here?
I guys know that guy's out of his mind. He's got married
He was having he's supposed to be on his honeymoon and all he can do is bitch
About JT and Gotti and rusty of course, right?
It's like you think you'd be happy
the
that's not very flattering to so to speak
that's not my fault that uh...
that's not my fault that this guy here
you know this fucker right here was jerking off to my voice
I know that's weird, that's one of the weirdest guys I've ever seen on the internet
you know that?
that shouldn't chill a guy, I don't know what's wrong with Shane but he's got some serious problems in his head
That's one of the weirs guys, you know that guy pretended to be a woman for four years, and I thought he was a woman
Did you really I really thought it was I talked to that guy since 2019 JT seriously
I mean in the chats in the in the Vegas
And he pretended to be a woman. It's German woman. He said he was from Germany, and I believed him
I thought he was down the truth
That's crazy. He was nothing but lies. I've seen crazy your shit. Oh, it's nothing but a bunch of lies
the
I have a shattered dreams and empty promises that I knew that she'd never keep
She sent many people to the heartbreak hotel right off of broken dreams boulevard
You know when I look at this it breaks all my dreams
You know, I need like a pallet I need a pallet cleanser
all I could care less about them than missing a few teeth and all that doesn't really bother me
I don't care about the teeth, fuck the teeth, fuck the wart, just fuck it all
I don't care about women with big breasts or if they're missing a few teeth
I care about their feet and they got long hair and a nice feminine looking face, you know
Oh, there you go
That's what I need, that's what turns me on
There you go, dude, looks like you can have Seb
That's what gets me going
That's what fuels the engine, if so to speak
you see what I'm cooking
It's great. You see what I'm talking about Tiffany
We're triangulating
I hope you try and go at my location
Come bring me a pizza. Tiffany pretends to work hard
You know what she pretends to work in manual labor, but I've looked at her hands. She's got city hands
But to be an actor Jesus Christ
I don't even think this bitch believes the shit that she says after 50 you got city hands
You've been counting money your entire life. So this one here says she's like, you know, I got four kids
I'm pushing 40 and no nobody wants me. I'm damaged goods. So what does she do?
She resorts to a fucking man. Yeah, it's epic
80s or something
and she thinks she's gonna build a life with this fucker
No, Tom's a 68 for my calculation says he's born in 56 and makes him a 70
What's he gonna get out of what's he gonna get out of it? Oh, she's gonna fucking raise his disabled daughter
That's what she's gonna do. I think he was born in 57 not sure, but I know he's born about the mid to late 50s
Woo, I know she's after something man. There's a catch there. There's something off. There's something wrong about that picture
Why would a 33 year old wouldn't marry a six seven year old guy a 38 year old woman?
Something off
You know what? I'm worried about ice. I'm gonna get iced soon. You know, they're gonna fucking take me
You're afraid you're gonna get deported by ice. Yeah, they're gonna take me back to Mexico
the
of the
one of the
Tiffany I want to ask you how many days a week do you work four days five days?
What's your schedule? What's your work schedule?
Fucking Mormon
Well, the rest and can you hold a panel down by yourself? I don't know. I'll try but I'm about to leave soon though
Can you probably not give you a
Providing entertainment for a while now needs I need you to hold it down for me
Okay, you don't know you're you're going to bed. Well, I need you to screenshot all this shit, and I need you to use it
Okay, it's this
All this shit see all this trash right here. I want you to use it
Use it for good and not for evil understand. I got no more time for that kind of drama nonsense
I got bigger fish to fry man
I'm going into bankruptcy here my liposuction surgery company listen, man
The government the state's gonna keep fucking paying for your little section eight. Whatever the fuck it is
I'm gonna need to file for bankruptcy GT things aren't going well man our family customers aren't paying their bills
you know you could always get a you could always get another fucking 10k donation
You know you know these fat customers, man
They took advantage of our special discount of the discount that I offered them
No
We paid to take off take the fat off their body man to make them look better to improve their appearance
Oh, you mean appreciate and don't put which you know don't put this photo up. Is that what you're asking?
it was to no avail because they didn't they didn't even appreciate it
You guys want to expose me for cash
Who's that guy?
So
It's my cousin. I don't recognize that guy
You know, I don't even I don't even know this fucker is they come tell you the truth
I think you should all get together and figure out a way to expose
Who's got a better-looking feet Tiffany or dot I can tell you that Alicia's better-looking feet. Oh
Okay, just like team Tiffany's feet, man. I'll tell you one thing
Face alone face alone this or this this or this which what are we gonna? I gotta go with Alyssa. Oh
But I had some of the pictures I seen a Tiffany man. I made her look better
Well, it wasn't this picture
But I'm from what I've seen from Tiffany man her feet. They're too flat
They lack an arch and her toes are too chubby, but that's my opinion though
So they look like man feet then but yeah, kind of but that's my my my personal
Expert opinion on her feet. So you're saying her feet are a little men ish because I'm an expert in women's fee
I love women's fee
Yeah, her feet. They're not feminine enough man. They got they lack an arch
They got her toes are too. They're too small and chubby. It's just her feet. Don't turn me on man
Not enough. I mean you could learn to love them. You don't think so. I see better feet man
Trust me. Yes, would you would you put your tongue in between in between the gap in her teeth though?
Depends. No, it depends on what what about you would you?
of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of
So you guys want to you guys want to find like a mentally disabled woman so you can tell on her to her family
That's fucking weird. Look at that guy. He says Tiffany has started. It's fucking weird
Holy shit
Well Tiffany your brothers retarded I thought you'd have a little sympathy for the for the mentally challenge
I mean, you're not much better yourself. So I thought no platform boots. I wouldn't lick her a beauty mark
No, Tiffany, those were your nudes. We went over this already, just asked Charlie.
Yes, that's true, Tiffany. You bring a good point about that, about CB.
Well, Seb, you remember when you showed me those nudes of Tiffany's?
And you remember where you got them?
From Charlie, but those weren't of Tiffany's that was CB's men and was proven later
No, that's what if we wanted you to think no, no, GT. I recognize and I reckon listen
There's two things I recognize the blue walls and her fan
And I know that Tiffany doesn't have that in her house in her trailer there
She doesn't have a blue wall or a fan like that on the ceiling
What's he already painted the walls? You didn't know that oh man come on
I saw the body man that's CB and I saw and I saw that she showed me that the proof that the text messages
Is CB yourself admitted that I was right that that was her that what that wasn't Tiffany that's been already
That's been proven beyond a shadow of a doubt
That was very disappointed with that man those pictures man, I knew it but that doesn't matter though
I don't want those pictures
It was it was weird. Yeah, the whole thing was really
You were actually very disgusting man. I didn't need to see that I could have done it without it
Yeah, I could have done it without that
No, honestly Tiffany, I knew you were a lot bigger back then it was like four years or some shit
So it's like of course you're gonna be bigger back then. I know I was bigger, but that wasn't her that trust me on that
And this I that she's right. That wasn't her and she proved it
it's just a lot of shit
it's a lot of shit
oh yeah man if you're running into bankruptcy
you might want to get another 10k donation
maybe from JC this time
I don't think so man
I work on my own stuff man
I'm working on my business but we're going to go bankrupt
then we're going to file for bankruptcy
we're about to close down
permanently
we're going on permanent vacation
JT
all we're going out of business man we're going to need to fire a few employees
even the surgeons uh well they're going to find other clinics to work for
they always need surgeons in the liposuction surgery department and business
oh shit there's no shortage of uh of good surgeons
i mean actually there's a shortage i mean they're looking for surgeons
good surgeons oh aren't we all huh
that's what I was thinking of JT, kind of like you, I'm going to start being maybe a social worker or maybe like a therapist
that you should actually, it's very, it's very rewarding
I consider that, I also consider that possibility
I consider that possibility
And the pace not bad either
Not at all. I
Consider that once when I was one I was running my liposuction search
I consider some of our heavier female customers could actually prefer much more intelligent person to talk to
That's another story
Well, yeah, but you know, you're gonna have to listen to people's problems all the time
You know, I can handle that all the trauma and they're for depression and all their bullshit
And you're gonna have to pretend to care and I can handle it man
I talked to Justin yesterday man for one hour and I heard his problems
It's a lot you need to have a friendly ear and you need patience, you know
you gotta
Yeah, you gotta be willing to listen to a lot of shit. Oh, yeah
You gotta be willing to listen you got a no one to hold them. You got no one to fold them
Everybody's trauma dumping on you. Yeah, you gotta know when it like be quiet and just listen to what the person's saying. It's
takes patience I
Can help
all the king draw what you mean the guy that tells you to shut the fuck up and and constantly demeans you on camera that is that the king you're referring to
if he obsesses on your crotch is that what you're saying
the king draw a wagon
Tom is one of the most silly people I've ever seen
the sillier guys I've ever seen on the internet
G he's got a creative a you know that you know Tom GT's got a creative imagine imagination there
With those accounts that he comes up with in the names and the pictures
Oh, aren't they aren't they just creative aren't they the most creative thing?
Hi, is that creative guy you gotta give him that he's got a creative imagination. It's great a guitar
He's just great at life. Oh, he sucks a guitar. I'll tell you that you can't even play the guitar
He couldn't play the guitar to save his life. No
I mean you wouldn't you wouldn't listen to him play guitar like at a concert
Oh, wait, man
No
Well, you think that a guy that has a guitar for that many years would learn how to play it properly
But no, he doesn't learn how to play it. Well, what's so ever?
No, he's not able to play the guitar man forget that needs to do something else
He's a fine new hobby. I'm gonna let you talk
I need you to talk to these people because I'm gonna have to step away
I'm gonna stay here, but I'm gonna step away
so I need you to entertain these people
I'm not going to be able to stay here for long though, I'm going to leave too soon
No, I need you to stay
I'm going to read the side chat a bit
Talk to these people, make them feel special, make them feel good
I'll see what I can do
I'll see what can be done
What do you see here?
Yeah, target the shark target the faggot in the sidestack. What else we got here?
You got another one of Tom's accounts the magic Mormon of underwear that's Tom's account Tom I
Told you if you're gonna use an account use the trashman account the garbage the green the green garbage truck
You know riding dirty. That's your best one Tom
I see here
And read the site chat a bit here.
There are people doing up at 5 a.m.
What's wrong with you people? You can't sleep?
Someone in the private chat here.
Oh, yeah, GT.
You create your imagination.
just about out of material
that
the
that's awesome Alyssa and you know it's
That'd be terrible. Oh, I talked people out of that man. I died out from it
I don't want to be positive. So you're gonna talk them off the ledge, but what about yourself like?
I'm still here. All right. I mean barely barely, but I'm still here man
And this is this is no medication talking man. This is natural hundred percent myself or you know what you're hanging in there
You're hanging in there. I've been hanging there for 44 years, man
And I'm still going I'll still be you're here man. You don't know what
you know what you're doing what you're here
Yeah, that's all this old heart of mine. He's beating strong
They didn't we miss I'm I'll leave you again by yourself. Okay, I
Saw that last one
Get to zip that picture real fast
Yeah, you're jealous of me target faggot what's wrong with you? Why don't you come on the panel man and make it man to yourself?
Enough of your shenanigans come on the panel and start to talk business
That's another guy that was jealous me that guy. What's his name whipperman, huh?
He's been jealous me before a couple years ago
He sucks at skiing I'll tell you that
I'm a better skier than him. I only skied a few times
Skied a few times back in the 90s. I'm probably a better skier than him on a mountain with snow on it
Some nice pictures there you got there
That picture of Scott is a chinchilla wheels. You got my that's terrible. That's Monica
One of the ugliest things I've ever seen and I've been on safari
That's Christine Newton
Collins a big backstabber man
He's no friend. It's no friend of mine
Because one of the fattest people I've ever seen and I've been on safari
Yeah, that's right platform boots Tom's been the impotent
the
Calling for a scatter showers today 80 degrees wind gusts of up to 20 kilometers an hour
Falling for rain later on
Rain in the forecast the next few days here
That's your morning weather brought to you by
Bible section surgery 40 off for each new customers
60 off for the independence day
week July 1st of July 8th
limited time off or only though
Book for your appointment today get that 60% off while it lasts
Visions and prices subject to change without any notification
Acacia, okay, you're on vacation
Well, that's good enjoy your vacation. What are you doing on your vacation? Are you with Tom?
Are you just gonna take it easy at your house?
Did I find a job yet? No, it's not easy. I didn't find a job. I found nothing but shattered dreams
Disappointments
These are going so bad
Delta file for bankruptcy
She used her two and a half months not on her kids
How many weeks you get a vacation alicia three four weeks so many weeks
Her cousin looks like your mom cousin looks just like your mom well well when you scroll up
Tiffany you went to bed Tiffany good decision unless you're unless you're uh you're lurking
Which it probably are
I know you're watching Tiffany
I know you're keeping an eye on the chat without me you don't even exist
After many people employed these days, Alysia times are hard hard times
Alysia if you ever take a trip down to Cobb County, Georgia, you better read the sign and respect the law
You'll be serving hard time
We serve in hard time I tell you
Target faggot I think a psychic I went to bed. He fell asleep. He dozed off
Does that answer your question? Is that clear for you faggot you live dark faggot?
Like it off my back
Smarten up you punk
Pick up your ears
Cuz I only give you seeing this once
from now on
Things are gonna be very different around here
Starting with you principal Flanders
All right, you little bugs
Fun stops here. You're gonna shut your mouth and behave darn it
Gonna shut your little traps and behave darn it
It's one substitute. You're not gonna mess with
It's one substitute you're not gonna mess with I'm the substitute here and you won't mess with that
he'll be given no leeway whatsoever
all right, what else here?
what else we got?
what's up?
so far, there's only alicia,
platform boots and tarq,
the faggot,
and the sidechat
that I can see
that's all
just keep rambling at them, just
keep rambling at them, just keep
rambling at them, just keep rambling
She thinks GT is going to put his reel
I hope they try this channel
You can't make this level of idiocy up. That's right platform boots. That's right rusty
Should I call you mr. McLean
Mr. Officer John McLean of the New York City police department
Tarkya faggot you've been transferred to personnel
Pick up your things and clear your desk vacate the building at once
Like I'm back here and you're still there in 10 minutes. I'll get security to escort you out
I'll escort you out to the street
Out of my office out of my building
The list you only got one thing to tell you get out of my dreams get out of my dreams and get into my car
How was your daughter Alyssia you got a daughter
I'll just stop with these fake names and just call ourselves by your real names, huh?
And I've been using my real name for the last six years
Can't you clowns just cut the crab already and then use your real names on we we already know your names, right?
And come on when it's a skinner gun just use your real names are crying out loud
Just take one dip and end it
Look Alysia the next time you dip a chip do everyone else a favor just take one dip and end it
Oh the last JT
No, that's everyone I guess I'm the last survivor, huh last of the Mohicans
Last of the real white Christian men
Last of the real brave men me
the
Don't think so dark
That's because he went to bed you idiot. It's five o'clock in the morning. It's 5 14 a.m. Everyone went to bed
Are they're tired? Are they getting up late?
Are they been transferred down to personnel
What are you gonna do Tiffany? You're gonna release the dogs or the bees or the dogs of bees in their mouths
And when they bark they shoot bees at you. Well, go ahead do your worse
That person's been trying to embarrass me ever since they knew me I've been writing my coattails and
I'm gonna take my material away from me. Well, I've had it Bart take a note
Dear mr. Burns, I'm so glad you enjoyed my son's blood
and the blood drive and
The car that you sent us was just great in case you can't tell I'm being sarcastic you stink
Here's read that last part back to me you stink
You stink Tiffany
Bad just kidding. Yeah, I'm just kidding. I'm just joking
Right on the panel and reported to the YouTube it's very sensitive
Yeah, she's very sensitive man. She wants attention
She thrives on it
She fuels on it
Like an engine like a well-oiled machine that needs oil to be well lubricated
to be well-oiled
Because without it she has nothing
These chats these streams
The drama the nonsense it's her life
It's her past time. It's her hobby
It's like a drug, you know they get off on it
the
I take a bath and I relax, but when I take a shower, I'm working in there, you know, I'm not just relaxing, I'm washing and scrubbing and exfoliating and lathering up, lathering up and washing, you know, when you got OCD, you tend to do that about eight to 10 times, you know, I don't remember the last time I took a
A 20-minute shower or less
However, remember wearing a hat not once not ever
There isn't a better chef in the world of food than Chef Boyardee
I'm gonna read the site chat here for a few minutes. I'm gonna get off pretty soon
Oh, use a sponge, do you?
Well, that's very good
Well, isn't that just lovely
I'm kidding yeah for you tiffy
Very good very clean keep your vagina clean
Keep your body clean keep your friends close and your enemies closer and remember tiffy
Revenge is a dish best served cold
But if you can't serve it cold put it in the microwave. He loved for about two minutes
Make a nice meal make a nice little supper there
Yes, but if I got something else to ask you who does number two work for
Tiffany I said
Who does number two work for?
If you know, let me know.
Otherwise, forget it.
Oh, don't be jealous of me, Mickey.
Just because I got the guts and the courage to go on the panel
and talk and do some material and stand-up comedy.
Don't be jealous of that because you can't do it.
You know that you can't handle it.
You can't handle the truth.
You got nothing, Bunk, nothing.
You work for me, that's all there is to it.
Tiffany I want to ask you if you're still there. Well, I want to tell you before I leave
Unblock me at once
Unblock my accounts
Or else you'll be given no special discounts
You won't get the 40% off or 60% off the liposuction surgery
You won't get the blocks the blockbuster gift certificate coupons
You'll get nothing
So unblock me
If you don't
So be it
It's not about the retire from the chats. Anyways, I've done enough
I've seen enough and I've contributed enough over the past six years
I'm gonna retire and let other people
Do their stuff
Because to be honest with you, it's a big waste of time. It's only been a little
hobby and pastime
and you're bored but
To be honest, it's nothing but nonsense
It's nothing but crap
It's not sense. No people aren't serious on these chats. You know that right?
You people know that you idiots know that by now been chatting for six years
Any real life some of it's real, but not everything
Pretty much everything ain't real
pretty much just crap when you think about it
it's about 80 to 90 dumb people i'm not trying to put anyone down with some people
like they're really not too bright people got nothing in the head i got no brains
some people have nothing
They don't deal with reality
Or they're stuck in the matrix because they're lip tarts
anti-white lip tarts stuck in the anti-white narrative stuck in the matrix
And they don't see the veil that's right in front of them
They don't see the the deception that's been pulled over their eyes for the for their entire lives
I'm talking about the anti-white narrative
I'm talking about the anti-whiteism
And the white get the white guilt, you know, they push the white guilt on us. They constantly try to push white guilt and
Freedom of speech doesn't exist anymore
There's no freedom of speech whatsoever everything gets censored
You know, it's one of the few times that I can actually say the truth without getting censored by some dumb idiots
Some people like JC and others they try to censor you and they try to call you a conspiracy theorist
Because they're too ignorant to do their own research and they're not intelligent enough to handle the truth when they recognize when they see
They don't recognize the truth when they see it
That's because they're very dumb people
And that's not being mean. You know, that's that's just telling the truth. That's just telling the facts
You can shower them with authentic proof and information and pictures and verifiable facts and they still won't get it
You know, they're the only way they're gonna get it is one day when they get a big kick in the behind from the liberal communism
Liberal communist soldiers when they get a big fat kick in their binds there then they're gonna realize that everything else saying was true
But of course by then it'll be too late
But that's how it goes with these these ignorant lip tarts
Ignorant anti-white lip tarts and anti-crisis
They're just too
They're too ignorant. You know, they're very ignorant. It comes down to that. They're ignorant and they're jealous
They're dumb
They're not they're not intelligent people. They all deal with the reality
They'd rather be ignorant. You know, they'd rather live an ignorant life and go through life their entire lives
Living in ignorance not dealing with reality
Their God is their money
Their God is their material things
They've been blinded for their entire lives with lies and they're not able to see it.
They're not able to open their eyes.
They've been led right off a cliff by the mainstream media and the corrupt governments.
And they don't realize it.
And they're jumping off that bridge in a cliff voluntarily.
When people like me try to warn them and try to save their lives.
What do I get in return they call me a conspiracy theorist people like us
People that deal with the truth in reality people that try to help them give them a helping hand try to save their lives
What do they do they?
They spit on you
They put you down they lie about you they try to defame your character defamation the character
Very disappointing but that's how people are so I mean
There's 90% of people that don't know what's going on
5% of people that know the truth in the world and the 1% that that all the media the governments
The banks and the school institutions that 1% the trillionaires the billionaires the bankers
Once I'm talking about that 1% doesn't want us the 5% that know the truth
To tell to warn the other 90% that don't know the truth that don't know what's going on. That's how the world works
down so that's the reality of the world right now 90% don't know what's going on they're ignorant
not able to deal with reality
The 1% the globalists don't want us the 5% to warn the 90% you get it. That's how it works
That's what i'm trying to tell you
What enough about that
Just to say that i'm gonna retire pretty soon because i'm done wasting my time with you idiots
Many of you these prefer the intelligent people out there for my fans and the people that appreciate me
Ever the people that appreciate my time people like me and da and Justin and and empty
Good guys like that good fellow white Christians that tell the truth and the stand for what's right
Then I appreciate
Other than that I'm just wasting my time and I can do better things for my time. I got bigger fish to fry
That's all I had to say about that
I can joke around I can also be serious and I can give you the straight-up facts whether you can handle it or not
That's not my problem. You my job. That's to tell you the truth
And tell you the truth what you do with it. That's what you that's what you decide to do
You can't handle it too bad. You can't help the truth get out of the kitchen. I
Don't know you can't take the heat get out of the kitchen
Many people can't take the heat you know and many people end up getting out of the kitchen
Because because they can't handle it
Because they suck because they're too lazy to do their own research and when you do the research for me give them a short cut
You generously tell them the truth generously to help them
What do they do they do everything but appreciate it?
Push it out. They lie about you
Nice people, huh?
It's people these elliptides on these anti way elliptides are full of crap
I tell you they're about the dumbest people on earth
They're the problem. You know, they're part of the problem not the solution me. I'm part of the solution, but then they're part of the problem
What else we got here we got Jim, good morning Jim you're up you're up at this time 527 a.m. Oh
No, I'm not a meth man. I don't take any drugs man. This is a this is a sober guy talking here, man
That's one of the few sober guys you're ever gonna hear
Take note of it man. I appreciate it because you don't see guys like me around here anymore
One of the few people maybe the only one that stands for the truth and what's right and stands for humanity and animals
Animals rights. I stand for Western kind Western civilization. I stand for us white Christians and colored Christians
You're never gonna see another guy like me, man
They don't call me a legend for nothing and I'm not bragging here man. There's not too many people like me. They got the guts
The curses stand for the truth and to tell the truth like I've done for the past six years on various panels
Various different panels of my time is done
I'm gonna retire man or right off into the sunset and do other stuff with my life
Because I can do better things
I've got other people to help I can't help any more people on the internet I
Can only help those that I can help I need to move on
Yeah, that'd be good, huh?
Mickey
Yeah, but Billy would never shut up Billy doesn't let other people talk. He's not able to handle a conversation. You can't talk
Can't carry an intelligent conversation. I don't know if you notice that he's got attention deficit disorder and he lies through his teeth
At least with Tom I can talk in a little bit even though Tom has a big mouth
but with Tom I can talk a bit more but
But he's too obsessed with himself on his panel. He wants to he wants to dictate everything
You know, I would need to open up a panel, but I never did that but if I had a panel
It would be fair for everyone everyone ever want to get a fair share. I don't like an intelligent conversation
That'll never happen because I'm never gonna stream
It wasn't meant to be I
Will retire dark you faggot
Even though guys like you you don't come on the panel
You only say this you stay in the side chat like a coward man. I wonder what you sound like man
I wonder what's even your deal, man?
You never you guys like you never go on the panel not even once you're a coward man. You're a you know, but a coward and
You're a hypocrite
You're probably an anti-white lip-dart stuck in the anti-white narrative and you probably try to push white guilt on people
Don't show you little buck a little faggot you little coward. You know what they call people like you men
Little gutless coward cowards and bullies man. We deal with people like you though
People like you little cowards and have like liptards like you get what's coming to them sooner or later
Probably on drugs too, I don't know you personally and I don't want to know you man
You sound like an idiot every time I see you in the side chat there target faggot you've been saying dumb things
Unless there's someone else using a fake name, unless you're Tom, but I don't think you're Tom
Because Tom has many accounts, but I don't think that's Tom. I think you really are an
individual it's a
Just a coward what enough about you though
You don't matter. Yeah, you don't matter whatsoever man. You're dismissed punk
You've been dismissed man, you've been discharged
You've been transferred to personnel, but not even transferred personnel. You're a squirt out of the building man
I'm telling you get out get out of the building. I'll have security and scorch out
You can go out of the building one way or another
That's up to you to choose
With security without security. Well, you will get out of my building though
And trust me, I'll know if you're getting out because I'll see you on the security camera
Like that, don't you so I can laugh man. I even with trolls like you I can laugh and make a joke out of it
I'm joking here, man. I'm messing around here
Wasting my time. I tell you I tell you got to be pretty pretty bored
Boring life to his time like that on chats. Oh
Well, that's what it's come to one
So be it
Oh, no way that many people will come to my stream
They'd be flocking into my stream man. Yeah idiot, but the problem is they'd censor a guy like me
They take me off right away for telling too much truth because I'm a threat to their agenda. Do you understand that you dumb libtard?
I'm a threat to their agenda because I know too much truth man
And if I tell too many people the truth and I become even more of a threat to their agenda
That's why it's not even worth streaming
Is it what caused myself problems? I would end up getting targeted
You know what I mean? Can you read between the lines? I'm not going to tell you anymore, but if you're a smart guy, you can figure that out. You can read between the lines, like what I told you.
Oh, there's no delusion about a 60% off, a 40% discount on liposuction surgery. Man, we just got the new liposuction surgery zap.
The new machine, man, the new liposuction surgery zap for 8,000. What do you think of that, man?
state-of-the-art equipment man state-of-the-art technology
And take advantage of that discount well
Well, it's still available. Well, it's still offered man because I'm about to fall for bankruptcy. Yeah, you need to fall for bankruptcy pretty soon
When the customers don't pay their bills man that everyone suffers, you know, and then we're not able to offer generous discounts like that anymore
You think it's easy giving 40% off when people aren't paying their bills
I either how the heck you want us to balance their checkbooks like that
We're not able to pay your bills man. We got to pay the surgeon. We've got to pay the technicians
we got to pay the
Everyone we got to pay the utility bill the rent the mortgage the electricity the supplies even the janitor I
Got all these employees. I got to pay
How the heck do you want us to survive like that when people aren't paying their bills?
It was fat customers man. They love you to lose the fat off their body, but they're not big to not fast on paying their bills
Oh
They're fast on taking the discount. So aren't they?
They're not very good paying customers
It's people like that that everyone else suffers some of their clients they pay their bills on time
And they're a good client. So let people mess it up
What happens
Let me see
I go to bed Tiffany or go to work whatever you do
You just took a shower Tiffany that means you're going to work right made yourself nice and clean as good
Enjoy your day Tiffany if you're still there
Join your day at Target if you're not working
your day
Stop taking those pictures at the gym
It's prohibited
They don't watch you taking pictures inside the gym in the locker room in front of the mirror
some of the clients complained
They find it to be a
bothersome to say the least Tiffany
No, I mean
There were some complaints about you taking pictures of some of the clients in the gym in the showers a
Washrooms in the toilets. Well, that's prohibitive
Fair warning, Tiffany
Cut that out. I'll be doing that anymore
We're also over with voc. You're your gym membership and they'll
I'll tell you that you're you're banned from the gym and you won't be getting a refund
You won't be getting nothing whatsoever
And then you'll be forced to work out in your trailer.
You'll need to resort to working out in your trailer,
in the woods, where you walk or you take your walks there,
and the liposuction surgery, of course.
Keep in mind, we can only take off 15 pounds
of fat per procedure.
And you can only have this procedure every like three
to six months, so think about that.
I don't worry about psyche went to bed
Dozed off I
Saw his eyes earlier. He was really like a he was he was looking tired man. He wasn't looking good
Wasn't able to handle it
Oh, he will he looked like he was either very drunk or very tired to be honest with you
Be honest with you. He didn't look too good
Then I'm since 3m Jim. I've been up the entire in the entire night. I'll go to bed soon though. I
Took a nap in the afternoon yesterday. That's why that's why I got the energy
You're wondering that's why get asleep
You might cat her up right now
The only part here is you
What do you think of that?
Let me zoom in on your picture there. Let me see what you got
Very impressive Nicole
Very impressive indeed
But to be a real snake you got to show somebody something Nicole
So how about it?
Let's see what you got
Time you out. I don't time you out man. I don't got a wrench. What are you talking about? I'm just on the panel here
I don't got a wrench. I'm not a moderator. I
Don't know what you're talking about. I'll got a wrench man
I'm just on the panel here right now
Only the lucky ones man only the lucky ones get to be on the panel of the last
First will be the last and the last will be the first
Only the lucky ones by lover boy 1983 guys
That's a good song check it out
Classic
Howdy mrs. Brary wins and wildflowers spiritual arts
Yeah, he's sleeping a he went into bed. I think he dozed off or he was very tired
Maybe it was druggers eye on drugs. He wasn't looking well earlier. I saw it in his eyes as someone was off
I think he fell asleep to be honest. He was tired
And of course I had to keep the show going all the show must go on
But I'm about to leave too soon alive for the provide enough material for now
Some of these libtards in the side chat don't appreciate me
It seems so I might be leaving pretty soon and you guys are not gonna have a show anymore to listen to
Watch
Oh, there you go, Mickey. She says she didn't time you out.
She says that she didn't time you out.
That's the answer you were looking for.
Huh, I don't even know what to talk about, Eck.
There's just no subjects that come to mind right now.
That you want me to talk to you about, Eck.
You got any suggestions? Let me know because I don't know what to talk about.
Now fresh out of material here
Yeah, it's a tough crowd, huh
Tough crowd well, you'll notice a prairie winds it
When it's lip tarts, they tend to heckle, they tend to heckle you, uh, they tend to be the heckling ones, you know
The one that's the ones that heckle you the most
They're always heckling people these lip tarts
anti-way lip tarts particularly
Especially they're especially rude and insensitive, you know and unkind and ungrateful
But they suck
Anyone with a brain can see that
They know I'm telling the truth and the truth will set them free
They modify the weather they modify the
It modify everything guys
Weather warfare weather modifications. We got bands for guys by the way. I'm just throwing that out there
They got over 140 different bands. Did you know that over the past three four decades?
They're able to modify the weather they got the technology for it and that's not a conspiracy theory do some research
Go on bitch you if you want to find a truthful information because all the truthful information gets censored
You won't find that kind of stuff on YouTube
You got to go on bitch you for that and rumble and Odyssey and and other alternative sites like that
If you want to find out about the truth about weather modification these storms that we're having and these floods aren't natural
They're not naturally occurring. These are done. These are man-made. It's man-made weather
Modification is it's man-made weather warfare. Do you know if you guys can understand that you can relate to that?
You guys probably don't know I'm talking about because you never heard of some people for
Many people know that that's what's happening with these storms and these floods and these hurricanes and even tornadoes
They're able to create everything they got pounds for everything guys. They got over a hundred pounds for these things
Just throwing that out there in case you guys didn't know that these these record heat waves these heat waves and these
These unprecedented floods and storms these things aren't naturally occurring and there's no such thing as climate change
These things are man-made okay, they're man-made and they got the technology and they're doing on a purpose
And you're gonna ask why I'll tell you why it's to create chaos
It's to create misery and suffering because they're sick because it's crimes against humanity. Okay, that's what it comes down to
I'm giving you the the short
The shortcut to with the brief the resume of it, you know, giving it to you in brief, you know being frank with you frank speaking here
It's crimes against humanity and steep population
And it's it's it's land grabbing. It's to grab land. They're trying to grab land. It's land grabs
They call it they're grabbing land. They're getting land just like what they did last year in north carolina
Just like what they did recently. I think it was last year in north carolina and uh
A few other states those are land crabs
They wanted they wanted the lithium mines and they wanted they want they want a bunch of things
You think it's by chance many we think they're doing with the you think that what you see in the sky sometimes those are chemtrails
It's not
Tell you what it is
spring programs. They're spring poison in the skies. They're poisoning our foods. They've been poisoning our foods in our water supply for years and for decades, right under our nose, right under everyone's suspicion. They've been doing that. Where do they put in the water? They put fluoride in the water. Where do they put in toothpaste? They put the same thing fluoride. What's fluoride? Do what's poison.
You think for it's good for you look at the ingredients of fluoride. What's it do? You know what fluoride does?
I'll tell you what it does
Educate you a little bit here on the troops fluoride shrinks your pineal gland in your brain your brain
You got a pineal gland and a fluoride keeps shrinking it slowly and slowly and you can't get that back. It's irreversible
They're dumbing us down
They're slowly killing us with the food with the water with the air their poisoning with the planes
They're modifying the weather
They're injecting you with poison and calling it a vaccine
Come on guys. Wake up. Wake up already
2025 these things aren't conspiracy theories
It's what's been happening for the past five years for the past ten years for the past decades for our entire lives
They've liked us, but it's just more. It's more obvious now since the past five years since 2020. It's more obvious
Why do you think they rolled out the 5g towers? Why do you think they invested it?
Billings of dollars and rolling out 5g towers. You know what 5g does to you? Do you know what it does to the brain?
You know what radiation poisoning does with those frequency radiation ways does to it to the human brain and the human body and to the
Human vital organs and you didn't know what that does. You think that's good for you. It's poisoning as guys
It's it's
It's causing side effects to our bodies. We're not able to see right away
But it's over time. It's like boiling a frog slowly away in the in a hot boiling pot and in the pot of water
You know it slowly you turn up the heat and the frogs the frog gets boiled as slowly
But he doesn't realize until it's too late when he realizes too late. He's cooked
That's what's happening to us. They're cooking us there. They're cooking us slowly if they're frying us. They're killing us slowly
And you can ask why they're doing that we'll ask them and they're sick people. Oh, yeah
They're sick to range people the people in power. They got the technology the technology
It's in the wrong hands the weather the weather modification the poison injections the 5g towers
They rolled out those 5g towers in every one of our towns and cities in our western nations and Western countries
Since the past five years without even our asking us without even our permission. Why do you think?
What do you think they did that? They got an agenda?
Find out what that the agenda happens to be I told you already it's the population and crimes against humanity
The billionaires are trillionaires. What do they do? They own four things. They own the media
They own the banks
They own the governments and the school institutions. They own everything in society. You can't talk against them or you're anti-Semitic
You're racist. You're homophobic
They label you all these names. That's their excuse. That's to get off on their crimes
They get away with their crimes by calling you a conspiracy theorist by calling you a racist by calling you an anti-semite
By calling you a homophobic they push perversions on our kids in school
What do you think they're teaching our kids right now in schools in public schools?
You think it's good to send your your kid to a public school these days?
You want to talk about some truthy look up where they're teaching your kids in school
They're not learning anything but perversions and they're pushing an agenda
They're trying to confuse your kids gender confusion
They're trying to push that crap and that poison those perversions those sexual perversions on our kids. They're attacking
They're going after our little children now
If you got a kid take him out of the public school home teach him home school
Keep him at home. Get someone else in your family to take care of them
You're not doing any good for your kid. That's like child abuse if you're letting your kid go to a public school
Your child go a public school. Well, that's child abuse. You got to take your responsibilities as an adult as a
Mother or father as a father mother as a parent
It's your responsibility to take care of your kids to do the research so they can't it's your responsibility
Take care of your kids. Take care of your life. You're responsible for your own destiny in life
You're gonna hear that anywhere else not no one else can have the guts to tell you the things
I just told you in the last five minutes
Told you a few things that you're probably not gonna hear you're not gonna hear again
And when someone tries to tell you that they're gonna call you a conspiracy theorist
They call they get called conspiracy theorists. Yeah, that's what they do
The silence the truth they want to silence the truth
Don't you know that we live in a censored society of these silencing you get canceled cancel culture
You can't say anything. You can't see anything. That's truthful
You stand up for humanity for animals and you get labeled a racist and a conspiracy theorist and you get labeled a
Bunch of names that ain't true
Simply for for being a human for standing up as a human being for standing up as a member of Western kind Western civilization
That's how things are guys that's how the world works right now
We live in a sick world and everything is about to collapse in case you didn't know
Everything's gonna collapse. It's a matter of time. It's just a matter of time
Believe me mark my words on that if it's not a financial collapse first
It's gonna be a food shortage or if it's on a food shortage. It's gonna be a financial collapse
Those are the two major things once the economy collapses
Everything's gonna fall
They're trying to do that on purpose. They're trying to set off
They're trying to create chaos and then once they create that chaos and people like a they get on the streets
And they start losing their minds are gonna declare martial law and once they declare martial law
They're gonna round everyone up put you in a prison camp
That AI crap in these smart cities. Do you think that's good for you, man?
You're gonna lose your privacy. You're gonna lose everything. You're gonna lose all your rights and your privacy. Wake up, you idiots. Wake up.
I mean, I'm talking to the people that don't know what's going on. I'm not calling you guys idiots in general, but I'm saying come on. Be smart now.
Think critically.
Stop being politically correct. Stop sucking up the liar. Stop letting these criminals and these these murderers and these rapists and thieves
Stop letting them fool you stop letting them abuse you
You know wake up man open your eyes and critically beat be a human being
Stand up for humanity and for animals man know the truth at least if you can't do anything at least know the truth and warn others
Are the truth when you can?
Because you're gonna see it man sooner or later soon enough you're gonna see that everything. I'm telling you it's true
And it's been happening and it's happening
It's already been happening and it's gonna keep happening until enough people wake up until enough people I get sick of it
Take a stand or until they get we all get killed off if that doesn't happen if we don't stand up for itself soon enough
We're gonna get killed off because that's what they're doing
What do you think they're doing is that the borders and the third world countries is the third world immigration?
What are they doing? They're bringing third world immigration into our western countries. You think that's another accent?
You think that's another by chance? They're trying to genocide us white Christians.
They're trying to they're trying to kill us off man. They're trying to genocide us and make us disappear and they're on the Western
Nations, why don't you do that in other countries man? Why don't you see a bunch of white people going to another other countries?
Why do you only see non whites coming here and our Western countries in Europe and North America in the USA and Canada and across
Across Europe and our Western countries and our Western homelands and nations
They're trying to race us
Open your eyes, man. It's time to start being critical. It's time to smarten up
It's time to stop being an idiot to start using your brain
If you haven't already if you have already use your brain and you know what's going on
Then good for you good on you
But if you haven't it's about time you woke up if it takes a guy like me to tell you that on the internet
That you don't even know well, then you need a wake-up call man. You need to start dealing with reality and the truth, you know, I
Don't know too much. I mean
Learned these things on my own man. I had to self-educate myself
I had to do some research over the past four or five years had to learn these things on my own
I took time I took hours and hours days and weeks and months
That's I'm studying man, but I did some studying in the school of life the real school guys
The real school the school of life not the school at school or colleges or university
That's only good for training people like a like an electrician or a surgeon or something like that
They're like like a trading all the jobs, but other than that, it's a waste of time
They're not teaching anything in school
the
Let your human side come out man
Stop being a sheep stop being a robot stop being a useful idiot stop being a useful tool and idiots to these globalists to these these
These maniacs they're killing us slowly that you don't see and I just named to you everything they're doing
They're killing us slowly one by one
Poisoning us there. They're making us sick. They're making us depressed with everything with a 5g with a 5g radiation poisoning
or the injections that they told you were safe and effective vaccines. We know that's crap.
I'll give you some real fast numbers. Over 2 billion side effects worldwide. Over 40 million
worldwide that died from those things, those so-called safe and effective vaccines. They were
effective, all right, at killing us, at poisoning us, at harming us, at making us sick. What do
those vaccines do? I'll tell you what they do. They accelerate cancers. Why do you think that
cancer rates more than tripled? It gives you super fast cancers, turbo cancers they call them.
The cancer is the cells in your bodies that are prone to having cancer.
Well, they get that cancer whatever you're prone to getting.
It's super fast like a turbo cancer, they call it.
People are dying of strokes and heart attacks. You think that's my chance
You think these young healthy athletes and these young healthy people are having heart attacks and they call it a sudden death
Come on man. You got to be a smart man
You got to be smarter than that you got to be able to see what's going on around you man
If you know you haven't seen it already
I mean if you've been watching the mainstream media your entire lives a little stop watching it and start doing your own research
You're gonna find out everything I told you is true
I did it for myself. I didn't fall for that crap. I did my own research before I fell into that crap before I fell for that crap
Just takes a bit of research that the desire the sincere desire to know the truth you want to know the truth you can you can find it
That's what Jesus Christ says you look for the truth sincerely
You're gonna find it, but you gotta look for sincerely. He knows your heart do what's right do what Jesus Christ would do
Stand up for what's right for humanity for animals. Say the truth. Don't don't hide behind political correctness. Don't don't be a don't be a hypocrite
You know, don't be a dummy
Be righteous man be righteous have integrity have guts have courage man have courage to stand alone even if you got a stand alone sometimes
I've been standing alone for years
Doing it's right. I don't follow the crowd. I don't I never thought that's never been me
I never followed the crowd. That's why some of these some of you idiots call me conspiracy theorists
I don't follow the crowd. That's not me. I never roll like that. I stand up for humanity and for animals
I stand up for my family. I stand up for Western kind. I stand up for Western civilization
I stand up for everyone in the world. I stand up for the victims. I stand up for the poor
The spies the rich I despise the evil the spies the evil of this world, you know
The evil works that blinds men that blinds the men's eyes
The blinds humania. It's a scourge on humanity. It's a scourge on earth
But anyways, that's pretty much what I have to tell you by that
Do your own research if you don't believe me look in look up anything weather modification
Poison in our food vaccines 5g towers radiation poisoning from 5g towers. Look it up
You're gonna see that I'm telling you what I'm telling you makes sense
I encourage you don't take my word for doing your own research. I know I did my research and I found out the truth
You can find out the truth, too
So that's what I have to say about that
Yeah, you're in a class from Nicole you bet
You're in the school of life the real school, you know, you're in the school of the West I
Graduated school to West. I got a PhD in the school of the West a real school
Got a master's degree actually not to brag if I may say so get a master's degree in the school of life
Go free Westman go free from the anti-white narrative be white positive stop letting people push white guilt on you
Go free from that anti-white narrative been trying to
White guilt us and they've been trying to guilt trip us and push white guilt on us forever
Especially now in the last two decades
Haven't you noticed that they're trying that we're disappearing slowly in the big cities that were the literally literally the minority in our
Own big cities in our own countries our own way Christian countries were the minority our own countries
Look around you go in the big cities if you live in a suburb if you live in a small town or in the country side
Look what's happening in the big cities I
Live in a big city for 20 years of my life and let me tell you it's been depressing and what I see going around and going around around me
It's
It's very upsetting and depressing, and ain't funny whatsoever, and that's what's happening.
Give me some good advice.
Take your kids out of public schools.
That's not going to help your kid.
Teach them at home.
Home school.
Keep them at home.
Keep them with your family.
Your kid's not learning anything in a public school, but nothing but crap and nonsense,
and he's learning a liberal communist agenda in school.
They're pushing liberal communism in schools, in public schools particularly.
Man, I'm just a regular guy man. I'm just a regular guy and
The one in the only gems. I'm just a regular guy man. Just saying the truth man
I'm the silent majority man
I'm the silent majority and there's many more people like me than you think because you don't see them because we get censored and they try to censor us
You tell the truth you get censored and you get
Called a bunch of names many get called a conspiracy. There's that's one of their clues man. That's one of their tricks
I mean
You know who invented that the term conspiracy theorists that was used by the FBI to discredit people that tell the truth
When they try to discredit someone that tells the truth
They call them a conspiracy thirst and they saw that something but conspiracy conspiracy theorists. Yeah, right?
That's not a conspiracy theory. Those are the facts man. That's the truth
They don't want you know that truth, you know why because it was money if you if too many people wake up
They're not able to push their crimes against humanity. They're unable to make money off of people
Why do you think they keep people sick in hospitals, man? They keep people hooked on medications their entire lives
People that don't need medications. I'm talking about things like cholesterol and diabetes and other things like that
They keep people sick. They it's a billion dollar industry, right? You know that
It's a billion dollar industry the medical industry. They prescribe you a medication
For like diabetes and cholesterol and other things like mental health problems and anxiety and depression and they keep you hooked on that in the entire
Your entire lives. They're not even treating your problem. They're just keeping you sick
They're making billions off of people like that. They're keeping people's fat and unhealthy
That's one of the reasons why it's good to get like both such a surgery to be serious, you know
Not joking here
Anyways, that's what they do. Everything's about money. That's what it comes down to in the world
It comes down to money and power and crimes against humanity and they get off
They're sick people, you know, they got no heart. They got no conscience
They don't follow Jesus Christ. They don't follow God. They don't follow receiving Jesus Christ
Man, they're following Satan. They're Satan worshipers, man
And they're trying to bring as many people down the hell as they possibly can
They're particularly attacking us white Christians. They're particularly trying to
So we're looking for the
Rather word that they're trying to
They're particularly trying to harm us white Christians. No, they're persecuting. That's the word I'm looking for
They're persecuting us white Christians and colored Christians particularly in the world
If you're a white Christian conservative man, you got everything to lose
You're at the top of the list if you're like me if you're a white Christian to serve man
You got everything to lose
Everything trust me on that trust I've been saying that for 20 years and I know that's what's happening
That's what he do I tell you
Yeah
Go revolution what you want, but it's the truth like I mean it's a truth of dark and you know it
Dark you faggot you know, it's a choose now
Told you man. I'm just an ordinary guy man
On the silent majority. I just tell the truth. I
Don't deal with the crap man. I deal with the reality
You're looking for like some politically correct assurer go to thing. You're not gonna get it for me, man
You're always gonna get the truth for me
With a bit of a sense of humor, but still it's the truth man. I'm serious. I'm dead serious, man
I ain't joking here with the things I told you tonight. I ain't joking. I joke around about other stuff
You know, but but these things I don't joke about now tell the truth now. I believe what I say
I know that I know my heart man. I'm doing the right thing. I'm doing the right thing because I'm standing for humanity for animals
And not too many people got the courage in the guts to do that
Only hypocrites and cowards man. Don't do that
Just way too many of them. That's a problem. That's why we're the mess we're in in the world
There's not enough brave men and women. There's too many cowards. There's just good people too. I mean, there's got nothing
They're all bad people. It's good people. They pay their taxes. They work every day
They pay their tax, but they're they don't know what's going on. They're afraid to deal the truth
I like it's like living in an ignorant bliss, you know
They're ignorant because they're too afraid to do reality. They knew the reality was shocked and they would turn their world upside down
It would shock them so much that they would be upset
They would be upset to know that these crimes against humanity are being done to us
They'd be so upset that they would maybe stop working paying taxes and then the entire system would collapse
So they gotta
They avoid it only that's what the government wants. They don't want the system to collapse, you know
Because once the people are stronger than the government it puts the government out of business
It's a business and they're they're a government people they try to government people once the government stops working for you
That's when you got the right to take them out. I mean not take them out
But I mean take them out of power
That's what I mean. I kill them. I'm talking about taking out of power, man
But you can't you can't you don't because it's an unfair system and the real criminals are never gonna be prosecuted
We're real criminals are never gonna get they're never gonna deal with that
They're never gonna be brought to justice and they're not they're never gonna get like a yeah
Charge for their crimes against humanity. It's
I afraid to say it's it's not looking good for us as a whole for humanity. It's only getting worse in case you haven't noticed
Things aren't the way they were in the 80s the 90s and the early 2000s. I'm talking about the last like 15 years
Especially it's gotten worse. Especially the last five years minutes. It's a disaster. It's getting worse and year by worse and worse by the year
That's 20 years. You can tell me that I grew up in the 90s. I grew up in the 80s and 90s
I'm 44 years old. Okay, and I remember I lived in a better world back then things were different
It was already like there was already corruption in the world, but not this way
But now they're they're out in the open. They're not even hiding anymore man these Satan worshipers many's globalists are not even hiding anymore
But they're using everything they can just look at the mainstream media
Just look at everything in the government's mainstream, how much they lied to you and they deceived you and they hide the truth from you, they're paid to lie to you man, they're paid to tell you lies and to hide the truth from you.
It should be the opposite, they should be telling the truth, you watch the news every day to get the truth, you're not getting the truth, you're getting an agenda, a specific agenda that they want to push on you.
They don't want you to know the truth man. Why do you think they censor and they hide things?
Why do you think you got to go on sites like bitch shoot and odyssey and rumble to find the truth because it gets censored
Because they censor truth because they don't want to they don't want you to know the truth guys
That's why they don't want you to know the truth because if enough people know the truth
They're gonna lose everything they got they're gonna lose their power
They're they're their their games and their grinds against humanity aren't gonna work anymore
But no enough people won't choose people are still suffering. We're still suffering collectively
Right things aren't done
Yeah, the priorities are at the wrong place
Why do you think I don't really watch sports anymore is it's even the sports have gotten political everything's
Everything's a political agenda. Everything's
Long story short. It's
everything's other wrong a
Parties are the wrong place. What's right is wrong. What's wrong is right. Let me make sense anymore
Not before it's not too long before people start realizing that but it's gonna be too late by the time they realize it unless people start
enough people stand up and take action and
Until enough people stand up and then call it out call out the evil and denounce it and don't take part of it anymore
Nothing's gonna change. Nothing's gonna change until then
This might be the last time you hear anything like this on this dream I
Can hear too much truth like that
Said a bunch of stuff in the last maybe 20 minutes
Yeah, I'm gonna hear that stuff anymore
You're gonna hear drugs you rather here maybe if you rather hear drunks and dumb people say dumb things people on drugs and
People drunk out of their minds saying dumb things and then the same dumb crap
I've seen it for the past six years if you want that then you'll be happy because I
Don't think you guys are gonna see me too much anymore
This is one of the rare times you got to hear the truth, man
For me for someone that cares from someone that cares enough to see the truth to tell you the truth
Whether you can you call me conspiracy there's or not. What do you think? I'm crazy or not. I'm not crazy
I ain't crazy whatsoever. Just like Mel Gibson. I ain't crazy
This ain't that movie Mel Gibson, I leave the weapon 1997 a very good movie. I
Just stand up for you many. That's what I've been doing my entire lives
I stopped talking to people because I stopped talking my family because of this
They're part of the matrix. They're stuck in the matrix. They're part of the problem not the solution
I can't help. I tried to warn them. They didn't take me seriously
Everyone that I've warned before
And I warned sometimes I don't tell you what he's saying is too much anymore to be honest with you
The people I've warned before I saw who my real friends are. I don't got any real friends anymore. I saw the people that
I got a few friends, but I mean they don't get I don't really talk about anymore
I still got two friends left in church
My church I go to the church of Jesus Christ Larry Saints. That's my church
Got two good friends from church, but I try talking about these things
But even then they don't get it because they're so badly stuck in the matrix. I've been lied to their entire lives
That's what happens. You've been lied to in condition your entire life. It's really hard to break out of it
You know, it's really hard to go free from it from the lies
I'll tell you one last thing and before I leave
You know everything they told you about world war one and two it's a bunch of lies you want to know the truth guys
I'll give you two documentaries to watch. I dare you to watch these documentaries
You got the guts know the truth if you finally want to know it really happened 80 years ago
Look at these two documentaries. Look it up find out for yourself
Don't take my word for it. These documentaries are the next or the following one of them is called Europa the last battle full documentary
Europa the last battle you go on bitch you go on a search engine
Like a start page. You can go on Google or start pages. Look that up
You wrote with the last battle full documentary. That's one of them. It's a 10-hour documentary
Divided into like a 10 parts. I think an hour each part look that up
You're gonna see everything though of what happened
You're gonna see why every world every western nation turned on Germany from the lies that you know who told them about
They the tiny hats they the Jews the tiny hats the Jews
But every country against Hitler because he made his own monetary system because they went free from slavery because they were the last people
The last country to ever stand up against the globalist back then in the late 30s and the early 30s
I mean and then the war started in 38. They were the last country that they were the last
They were the last ones the last people that ever they stood up to him
And that's why they had to fool everyone, they lied to everyone, they had to put the USA, Canada, they had to put France, they had to put Germany, they had to put Poland, Russia, they had to put pretty much every western country, every western nation in Europe and North America against Germany, because they were a threat to their agenda.
They're the same people that have been lying to us, the same people that are lying to us now.
They were a threat to them the Germans were threatened
That's why they had to put every world every country against them to start a war and Jeremy didn't want that war
Hitler didn't want that war. He wanted to avoid it. He sent offers letters. You'll believe me. Watch the documentary. It's all documented videos
videos pictures
Facts proof authentic information. It's all in the video. It's all in the documentary. You don't believe me watch it the other one
It's called it's called the greatest story never told
Look that up
You're open the last battle and the greatest story never told when you got time you want to you want to watch the documentary
They'll change your life. They'll change the way you see things that you'll finally be able to know the truth of what happened 80
years ago and
For World War one and two in the 1910s and the 1930s you're gonna find it out with those two documentaries
I just gave you you're open the last battle and the greatest story never told
You got no more excuses now. I told you the truth if you don't want to look it up. That's that's your business as you're right
They keep living in ignorance keep believing the lies
But if you want to know the truth you look up those documentaries and you'll find out you're over the last battle full documentary
You can find that a bitch you and the greatest story never told the greatest story never told find on bitchy as well and on
Rumble and on Odyssey, but you won't find it on YouTube forget it the mainstream media is gonna censor stuff like that
They censor it you're not gonna find it on the mainstream media
You got to look on alternative media alternative media sources alternative websites if you want to find the truth
They tortured. I'll tell you what they did. They they killed and they tortured 60 million of our fellow way Christians across Europe
In the 30s and the early 30s, that's why Hitler stood up against them. Okay, that's why they had an uprights. They were sick
They were dying out. They were literally being erased. They're being genocide. They're people were suffering
They were starving in the streets. It was it was they were being tortured. It was terrible
He brought his country back from the brink. He turned it around
He saved this country saved this nation. That's why from 1933 to 1938
Germany thrived and they were doing well until until them the globalists the bankers the Jews turn every western nation against Germany
That's what happened guys. If you've never heard. That's what happens. You've never heard of it. Well, that's what happened
That's the brief resume of it. What's the documentary? Please don't take my word for it. What's the documentary I told you about?
I'm doing you a favor here. I'm asking you do it for yourself. Don't do it for me do it for yourself
You want to know the truth you deserve to know the truth?
Everyone deserves to know the truth and it's still there. It's still available. I'm bitch you
Can only find those things on alternative websites because that's you know what people know true
If everyone knew that trust me trust me man
They would they would go out of power tomorrow. They lose everything. They lose everything every every the world governments will collapse man
Everyone those corrupt leaders in the world matter the and the presence in our western nations matter that they're taking the orders from the globalist
Man, they would all collapse. They would collapse. I tell you the entire system would collapse if you knew the truth
What more can I say that's look at the documentary guys
It was it was terrible because that's huge it that's a huge part of history
That's why I'm emphasizing on that because if they liked you about that what else have they liked you about
Think about they've owned the media if you think I'm crazy
I'm not crazy think about they've owned the media for 150 years 150 years
They they've owned the media before they had TVs and television says they had newspapers
They've owned the newspapers for the past 150 years going back to the 1800s
Who own those medias man have asked yourself the same people that own our medias and our governments and our school institutions and our banks today
The same people to choose the same people
That's not anti-Semitic. That's telling the truth
They take people for idiots. They've been lying to you your entire lives. You know your television
They're telling you lies on that television every day and they're they're laughing at you
They're looking at you right in the eyes and they're smiling at you when they lie to you
It's called tell a live vision that television you watch break it down in three words
It's called tell a live vision four words. It tells you lies. They tell you lies tell a live vision television
You get it. Well, that's what they do
Go free from that. I threw out my TV in 2020. I finally had it. I said to myself
What am I watching TV for I unplugged it? I took it downstairs. I threw in the garbage
I said the heck with that
I said from now on if I want to get any kind of truthful information if I don't know anything about what's really going on
I'm gonna do it myself. I'm gonna I'm gonna search it on alternative media sites not the mainstream media anymore
The mainstream media 90% 995% CNN
CBS NBC ABC all that crap, you know, it's it's a bunch of life. Who owns that? It's liberals. It's communists
Okay, it's the globalist. They're only they take orders
They're paid millions to tell you the light to tell you lies to not tell you the truth
They can't tell you the truth. They told you the truth. They get fired. They can't tell you the truth
Don't you get it guys? Their jobs are to tell you lies. Their job is to hide the truth from you and to tell you lies instead
Why do they tell you lies? Because they keep you busy. They keep you distracted your entire lives
Keep you busy on other things that don't matter while their real problems aren't being addressed
While their real problems are going there they keep going on right in front of us and it's right in front of you right
Just got to open your eyes
Guys just gotta open your eyes. You just gotta snap out of it. You gotta sober up
You gotta stop drinking stop taking drugs and you gotta open your eyes smart enough
Why do you think they want people taking drugs?
Why do you think they advertise alcohol and they want people drinking beer all the time?
And they want and they're they're trying to they want you to smoke
They want you to take drugs and they bring in drugs and they import drugs
They get drug dealers to sell you drugs on the street because they want to keep you dumbed down
They want to keep they want to keep the society dumbed down and sick
Why do you think they give you medication your entire lives? Why do you think they poison their food?
It's the same thing. It comes back to the same thing. It's to kill us slowly. It's to make us miserable. It's to make us
It's to harm us. They're harming western time. They're they're harming humanity
It's crimes against humanity. Don't you get it?
How many times i gotta emphasize it, but that's
It's that's what they're doing anyways
Enough about that, but that's what they're doing. So watch the documentaries you're open the last battle and the greatest story never told
You're open the last battle the greatest story never told those two documentaries. You're gonna get the truth
You're gonna get the facts
Something that you've never seen something you're not expecting to see something that you deserve to know you deserve to know the truth
Take my word for I mean I'll take my word for it. Trust me on those watch the documentaries
That's what I'm saying
Don't take my word for it watch the documentaries if you watch the documentaries then good on you for wanting to know the truth
If you don't so be it go on to your life and stay ignorant and keep calling people conspiracy theorists
But you're gonna die not knowing the truth man
You're gonna go through your entire life not knowing the truth not knowing what really happened
You want to live like that you really want to stay dumb your whole life
How long can you stay in there man? How long before you wake up?
You gotta stand for something man. You gotta stand up for what's right in life
Otherwise you're just passing on through and your life means nothing your life is gonna end up meaning nothing
And then one day when you're at the judgment seat of Christ when you had the judgment day what Jesus Christ is gonna say
What did you do with your life and when when people when good men good honorable men and women told you the truth in the world
Told you the truth in life on earth. What did you do?
You called them conspiracy theorists and you laughed at them and you lied about them and you put them down
They were telling you the truth. They were trying to help you
That's what Jesus Christ is gonna ask you the judgment day and then he's gonna say he never knew you
You're not gonna be able to see be saved you got to turn your heart to him
You got to turn to Jesus Christ some full purpose heart if you want to be safe guys
That's the last thing I'm gonna say before I leave. I think
You know that ended with that
Turn to Jesus Christ full purpose heart search for the truth sincerely
Search be be truthful be honest be sincere takes it only takes a sincere heart
It only starts it starts with that a sincere desire to know the truth in your heart
Turn to the Lord of full purpose of heart. He will tell you the truth. He will
Show the truth on you. They'll show you the truth
No, bless you with the truth man. He'll help you if you knock it will be open man
He'll put someone on your way in your life
He'll help you to find the truth, but you gotta be sincere. Just just gotta be sincere
It's not hard be a good person be honest. You're all probably already a good person
But you're very ignorant. You don't know the truth on people. They're very good people though. Don't get me wrong
Many people out there. They're very good people. They just they just don't know the truth. They've been blinded
They're actually victims. They're victims of lies and corruption this this world on earth guys. It's corruption
It's lies. It's injustices. It's crimes against humanity those four things crimes against humanity and justice is corruption lies
Yes, that's what we're going through
You know Satan has fooled many people in the world and he's using many he's got many tools man the fool people with
Everything has to fall down these this entire satanic agenda has to fall man
The entire pornography industry has to stop the lies have to stop the crimes against humanity and against animals need to stop
You guys stand for what's right in life if you don't stand for what's right then who are you serving if you're not serving Jesus?
Who are you serving? You're serving Satan
Serve Jesus turn your heart to Jesus
Turn your heart before turn yourself with full purpose are at the Jesus Christ, you know
Let Jesus Christ in your heart. Trust me your life's gonna get better
You're gonna get at least peace of mind
You're gonna get a piece of mind that money can't buy a piece of mind that's priceless
Some of you can't buy with money forget about money forget about material things
You can't take it with you search for the truth and be a right be righteous be a good person
Have a heart have a heart for your fellow human beings your fellow men and your animals and everyone know
That's what it's about. That's what life's really about developing love love God and love your neighbors
You'll you do those two things you'll be saved
You'll be happy. You'll have true happiness true happiness money can't buy
All right, that's what I have to say
Maybe the chad and I'm out of here
Get the side chat here
See what people are saying. Oh, that's right Nancy. That's right. I'm impression. Maybe a bit too much
I said too many things, huh? I know I said too many things. They're gonna again. It's called me a bunch of names
They're gonna call me a conspiracy theorist and a and that job. No way
Just an ordinary guy telling the truth
There's no ordinary guy that has some humanity left him and I got some humanity left to me
I'm not perfect. I'm not better than you guys. I'm not better than no one
I got I'm the first to say I got a bunch of problems. I got depression. I got anxiety
I'm not perfect. I never said I was perfect
I only said one thing that I stand up for the truth and I stand up for us, right?
I don't sell my I don't sell out to anyone. You know, I get I
Got integrity. It's about having integrity guys about having integrity and being truthful and being honest and being righteous
Being truthful and righteous. That's what that's what it's about having integrity
You can't buy that man
You don't find that too much anymore. People are afraid. They're afraid to lose their jobs. They're afraid to speak the truth
You can't even speak the truth anymore game
You can get fired for your political opinions at your job, man
If you don't got a liberal communist agenda you get fired for standing up for the truth, man
Look what they did in 2020 men and people didn't want to take the poison injections. They fired them
I'd rather lose my job. I rather lose everything man. I'd rather lose my entire life than to take those poison
I really take a bullet to the head than take those poison Jackson's to be honest
And that's what I told my girl from once I told her I'm not taking that crap
They can pull it they can shoot me in the head. I'd rather die at least
Doing what's right not not selling out to Satan not
not being part of that crap and
For those for the people that took the injections that there's ways that you can detox but you it's in your body forever
But you can at least detox and
Save your life at least from getting a heart attack and stroke and you get that graphene oxide out of your bloodstream and
But anyways, they're putting in our foods. That's another story, but I don't know I get into that but anyways like a you can you can detox
There's certain things there's hydrochloroquine as I verbectin those two things
I hydrochloroquine and I verbectin and there's other things other supplements you can take vitamin
CD and zinc
And a few other things and an iron and also the other was the other thing
There's one there's just one thing that you can take for if you really want to detox
It's called it's zeolites supplements. Look that up zeolite supplements. It's called zeolites pure. That's the best one zeolites pure
It's that the green and yellow bottle
That's the best one if you want to detox from heavy metals because that's what they put in and the poise injections
And then our food heavy metals like aluminum and and mercury and and copper and then graphene oxide
crafting hydro hydroxide and stuff like that that's what they put in our foods that's what they put in
the injections the injections and something else the injections the so-called vaccines I'm talking
about of course that's what they put in those things man and we'll really never know what's
going on with that I mean what would they really put in people's bodies
Why do you think they didn't tell you the ingredients? Why do you think that when people died of strokes? They weren't they weren't um
You couldn't you couldn't sue them. Why why do you think that you think that's by coincidence, too?
He's think it's another coincidence. It's another conspiracy theory. No come on man. Millions of people died from those things
Healthy people there weren't supposed to have artifacts. I weren't supposed to have
Blood clots in their blood at the age of 20 or 30. Why do you think they died perfectly healthy people athletic peoples? You know
the
the vaccines they were effective all right i give you an heart attack they were affecting it
they were effective at creating blood clots in your bloodstream and causing to have a stroke
and causing you to have pulmonary pulmonary embolisms a bunch of heart related problems and
and that stuff that stuff went right through your blood brain barrier you know the blood brain
barrier is guys it goes through your your head it's a little thing that goes from uh it's from
It's it's this little thing. It's it's not much space between the blood brain barrier
Once that once that poison gets through the blood brain barrier goes into your brain gives your neurological
Problems you start developing neurological problems and diseases and damage you get neurological damage
You can't come back on that once that cross the blood. You know those so-called piece
I'll tell you another thing that's so called PC
The what was I called it the PCR test matter those those tests and they were saying oh you're positive or you're negative from COVID
They call it COVID. Yeah, right COVID convit. It's a con
The pandemic the pandemic the pandemic the pandemic guys the pandemic when they told you to go get those tests
Those are a bunch of fake tests a bunch of fake
false positives of a bunch of false positives
Because whatever you do, they're first of all, there's no COVID but there's no so-called COVID that the virus was never isolated under
Microscope, but anyways coming back to it when they did they took those tests those tests were designed to make a think that
They think that when they put that little thing in up your nose like you know that thing
The cotton swab and they told you you have to do the test
I mean they did the test on you they put that cotton swab between your nose
It goes through your, it goes up your nose of your blood brain barrier over the eyes and goes into your brain
That's it crosses a blood brain barrier and goes right into your brain goes right into your your your brain part
Getting neurological damage
And they don't they don't get you to have a heart attack
They cause you to have brain damage if it's not a heart attack if it's not a brain damage
Well, it's going to be other thing is going to be vital organ failures
There's like over a thousand side effects when those boys and jacksons
Documented they document over a thousand different side effects man
From those so-called safe and effective vaccines people didn't need to take vaccines man
There's no such thing as a safe and effective vaccine and it was rushed out
Doesn't that tell you doesn't that tell you any clues?
But I'm sure many people know what I'm talking about for the people I still don't know that's what happened. That's what they did
That's what they did
I think I avoided it because I was afraid of side effects. I started doing a bit of research
I did read this research on it on alternative sites, of course
I found out some things and once you find out a few things you want to find out more things and you want to find out more truth
And then the more you know the more like you know what's going on
And you can't unlearn the truth once you know the truth once you know they're they're they're sick
They're sick agenda their crimes against humanity agenda once you know that you can't turn back
You know once you know the truth you can't turn back because you know better
Once you know better. Yeah, you're wiser. You're wise to them. You're wiser. They're they're they're evil games. They're evil
plans
It's only the unsuspecting people like the tax being a people that work every day in the well not everyone
I'm not just saying in general me
It's the unsuspecting people that they watch the mainstream media that were gullible enough to take it and many of them are good people
It's just
They weren't able to discern from the
Tell the truth from lies and they got fooled people in my family. They're good people
They're very good people. They got a good heart and they work every day to pay their tax
But darn they were fooled and one guys like me tried to warn them
They thought it was a bunch of conspiracy theories again conspiracy theories
They didn't listen to the warnings. They took the injections. They got sick many of them died many of them got sick the ones
I didn't die and they're sick and they're dying slowly some of those injections
Acted faster some of the deaths came faster some of the deaths are gonna come later
But after five days you got five to seven years have you take the injections and you've been poisoned
You got a lifespan of five to seven years maximum. You can end up
Once you got too much graphene oxides on your body it causes
Is it cause it causes it causes blood clots and your blood gets thicker ask morticians, you know like it in
What do you call those things or mortician's work?
In the funeral homes funeral parlors the people the workers there
You know the funeral homes they did some autopsies of the bodies that many of the bodies that died and they found these huge
But we pulled out of huge blood clots of people
From their bodies huge blood clots and that was only since
2021 when the injections came out when the safe and effective vaccines came out
They call them the safe and effective vaccines when those injections came out the poison shots came out
They found a bunch of blood clots and people's bodies. Do you think that's a coincidence? You think that's another coincidence. No, it's not a coincidence
All these things make sense all these things fall into place all the pieces of the puzzle fall into place and it makes sense
And it shows you the big picture. They did that to our people
And on purpose they had meetings for it before that in 2019
They planned they planned all these things just like they modified the weather just like they do everything just like they're harming us with everything
Just like they poison our food supply
Just like they're causing chaos
Everything's a deliberate plan. It's an evil plan. Anyways, they poisoned us
This or does it gives you cancers? If you don't get a heart attack, you're gonna get a terrible cancer
It's happened to people in my family. You think I'm lying. It's happened to people in my own family
They were fine. They were perfectly healthy. My dad retired
He took the safe and effective vaccines out of nowhere. He gets a cancer
He gets Alzheimer's and he gets he starts being cognit
All because of those injections because they got over a thousand different side effects. That's why that's why
And what and how did it start?
Their pretext would be the people in old folks home. You know what happened to them
I'll tell you what happened to them. They were given something a poison called
Man, what was it called? I can't remember the top might have
I can't remember the word that first they killed off many people in the old folks home. They put them on ventilators
They gave them something I
Forgot the name but they gave them some kind of poison like they gave them they give them these medications and these injections
It was poison it killed them off and then they put them on ventilators
They finished them off with putting them on ventilators and during that COVID crab those lockdowns the hospitals were empty
People in hospitals who were poisoning and they were keeping them there and they got paid 40 to 50,000 per death per
COVID death for so-called COVID death. It's part of their plan then they were paid 40 to 50 thousand dollars
They collected insurance on people dying and they banked on many people dying in the tens of thousands and the hundreds of thousands in the millions
Worldwide that's what happened. Okay?
Giving you the the express the express like a description explanation of it
I know what I'm talking about. Trust me. I'm not lying. I'm not making this up. That's just
Express the description of what they've been doing to us for the past five years since 2020 our lives were better before since 2020
We didn't have problems of these 5g towers. We didn't have radiation poisoning
We weren't feeling depressed and sick and and like tired and depressed and out of energy
We didn't get severe headaches and and eye problems and all these things
That's what these 5g towers are doing wake up guys if you haven't woken up already. It's about time. It's about time that you see it
But it takes a guy like me to tell you that on the internet that guy that you never met something so cold conspiracy theories on the internet
That she never met takes a guy like me to tell you that well if it takes that's what it takes and that's what it takes
If that's what it takes and good at least you got the
To hear it you got to hear it once
If you haven't heard it already
If you haven't believed it before maybe you should start believing it because that's what's happening in that trying to make sense of it
I'm trying to explain it to you as best I can as fast as I can
Trying to make sense of it so you guys can get the overall picture
Whoever's listening
Of course, it's true Nancy. It's very true. It's darn true just like Kurt Angle used to say it's darn true. Oh
It's true. It's darn true
That's Kurt Angle used to say that
Exactly
Yeah, you got a fight you got 5g chips planted into the bodies man, but don't I'm trying to really kill me though
It ain't a joke man
That's the mark of the beast once you take that once you take those injections
There's no going back you can only detox from that point on from that point on you can only detox
With certain things certain supplements hydrochloric and ivermectin and zeolite supplements and vitamin cd and zinc and stuff like that
That's if you didn't get a heart attack or a stroke and that's if it's not too late like it
your compromise either way you know your that's nothing your immune system you know those those
injections that your immune system once you take two to three vaccines you take out you wiped out
70% of your immune system your natural immunity is supposed to heal you from colds and and
blues the seasonal cold and flu they ended up calling it covid when did they start calling
We didn't need a so-called injection a so-called safe and effective vaccine. There's nothing but a poison shot. It's a poison shot
But they fooled you guys they pulled the wool over everyone's eyes
They pulled the wool over everyone's eyes
They fooled you with lies and they had to you know, they had to pump fear in everyone every day on the mainstream media when it came
I remember I was watching it myself. I used to watch it was on every channel every day
They talked about COVID COVID. It's so scary. It's terrible. You can catch it. You gotta put a face diaper on
What are those? What are those face diapers do they need to stop you from breathing? That's a symbol of slavery
You can actually catch a respiratory infection wearing those things for a prolonged amount of time for like eight to ten hours a day
You wear a face diaper eight to ten hours a day. That's not good for you
You're breathing in first of all you're breathing your own bacteria
And you're not able to breathe fresh clean air and that they're also making funny because they're laughing at it
They even admitted that the globalists themselves. They admitted that it's a symbol of slavery and they're mocking you
They're laughing at you when they see you wearing a face diaper
Come on even themselves and they think they took the injections you think they're wearing face diapers
No, they do it for the cameras
once they turn off the cameras they take off their face diapers and they
pretend to take those injections when you put it on TV that's a theater show
that's a puppet show man that's the fool the masses that's a puppet show the
world's a stage in case you didn't know that's another thing I had to tell you
the world's a stage it's a puppet show on a world stage the world's a stage it's
a puppet show on a world stage by them and they're manipulating the puppets
the world governments they're puppets to them everyone you see in your
Your your governments across where you live your provinces and your states there across their western nations
And the who owns them who pays them they take orders from someone they're not speaking
They don't speak for us. We know that they're corrupt and they're idiots
We know they're incompetent, but it's more than incompetence. It's flat out evil. They don't say sold out
They sold their souls to Satan these they've taken orders from the globalists
If they had any guts if they were human and they had any humanity that was right
They'd never do that to their own people. They're killing their own people. They're they're killing us
They've been killing us. They sold out. They sold us out to the globalist. They sold out. You they sold out humanity to the globalists
You call that a leader you call that they're supposed to be working for us, man. They're working for the globalist man
Wonder people gonna wake up the entire system the entire voting systems rigged look at what happened in Canada
You think they want to vote in the liberals again? No one everyone's sick of the liberals everyone knew that they were corrupt
Everyone 90% voted for the conservatives, but no they they made it look like the liberals one. It's rigged. It's rigged. It's a rigged system
Thank goodness Trump won at least you guys are lucky in the USA at least Trump
He's still taking certain orders from the globe was like don't don't get me wrong every every world leader
They they get put in there on purpose and the globalist say okay
You're gonna be able to get away with that
But we're still gonna tell you to do with certain things and they got to do it because they get threatened their families get threatened
They're still giving trump certain ores, but they let him get away with other stuff. They let him do stuff certain things
They let him do at least he's securing the board. That's one good thing. He's securing the border
He's getting also other things done like like men not playing in women's sports anymore. That's another good thing
Those are two really good things that he's done trump. He's secured the border. He's deporting the illegals
He's deporting the criminals the murderers the rapists the ones that the rape people that you don't hear about on the mainstream media
They'll never tell you down the news. They're trying to make them look like they're ordinary citizens. No
They're murders. They're killers and they're rapists. They're drug dealers and gangs. They're dangerous criminals that he's deporting those people
That's very good. That's a very good thing
And he's trying to get the
Give the the trans soldiers the men to get out of women's sports. That's another good thing
You know, he's just making a fair for the women. There's many good things that Trump is doing, but
Yeah, he's still a puppet and he's still taking orders, but thank goodness you guys got Trump
That's what I'm saying. That was my point. Thank goodness. You guys got Trump
You guys are lucky because we don't got that luck and we weren't lucky in Canada and then and like countries like England and France and Germany
We didn't get the same look. We don't got a Trump
We got nothing but liberal in competence and corruption
We got corruption and confidence with these liberal communists in Canada and then other countries in Europe
There's only a few countries in Europe left that they got patriotic leaders countries like Poland and Hungary and
few countries that's it that's pretty much the two best countries in europe they got the best
leadership poland and hungary they they care for their people and they only criminals like take
their country you know they stand up for their people they stand up for their culture and their
identity and their their heritage and their culture they don't let third world people come
come to their countries and then kill them and rape them you know and rape our women and take
care of everything we got no they don't let them they don't let that happen but that that's what's
and our western nations across Europe and even in Canada and the USA.
But anyways, that's what I'm saying. I was talking about the injections.
You get cancer, you get terrible cancers from those poison-jaxon scents.
Some people died faster some people. They're still still alive and they say, oh, there's this one guy called Ross
He tells me why I haven't died yet. He told me he took like five or six injections and he says he's fine
He's still alive. Yeah, you're still live for now. You haven't died yet. Why is gonna happen?
He's got poison running through his body. He doesn't even know it's a matter of time before he drops dead of a heart attack
Or he gets a cancer if you don't get those are two biggest things either die of a heart attack
I mean a stroke or heart attack you get a heart problem or you get advanced turbo cancer you get turbo cancers
You get any kind of cancer you're prone to it's always cancer and the heart the strokes the heart problems and the cancers
That the people get from these injections those are the two biggest killers from these injections
Many of the people had it the kinds of side effects of over a thousand side effects menus
Some people know that they know what's going on many people know that
You know, what else can I say? What else can I talk about? There's nothing else I see here
Oh, I got nothing else to say man. I've told enough truth man. That's too much. I did everything man. I think I touched on every subject didn't I?
I pretty much touched on every subject. I can't remember all these other things. There's letters and other stuff
I like to talk about that. You guys still want to believe it's round. I believe it's round
You know, there's proof. It's not where's the curve? I'll just tell you that I'll just tell you that that the people
I think that it's in the earth
It's still a globe and it's round. Where's the curve? Show me the curve
Where's the unaccounted curve for every like a few miles? It's supposed to curve every like certain amount of miles
There's supposed to be a curve right? Where's the so-called curvature?
If it's really round if it's not flat, right?
Don't want to get into that because you guys just gonna call me conspiracy for some of the people that don't know me
It was there's even less people that know about the the shape of the earth and then know about that poison Jackson
So it's a bunch of subjects you can get called a conspiracy for talking about
Yeah, you should get paid for Lizzie not even man Tark you're getting to hear the truth man
Don't appreciate at this point man. I can't tell you I can't save you man
I can't help you there's nothing more I can do for a guy like you Tark a person like you
I can't help you man if you're still you haven't you haven't figured out you haven't woken up by by now man and talking for
Maybe 30 or 40 minutes. I don't know what else to tell you man
Keep believing nonsense keep believing the lies and stay dumb and ignorant your entire life guys like Tark
I can't help you Tark man
You you prove that you're an idiot you prove that you're ignorant and you're dumb if you I tell you to you
this is a sober guy talking to you man i know that what i what i say you're not expecting me here
because you've never maybe you've maybe never heard the truth you're not able to recognize
this recognize the truth when you hear it what can i tell you i can't help you i don't know what
to tell you i can't help you man if you think i'm a conspiracy theorist if you think that it's
crazy what i'm talking about no man i'm just i'm just saying simple truth man it's simple
and make it very simple for you man i even explain it to you right down into detail
I try to save your I try to save people like you as they try to save your lives and
Yeah, don't you see dumb things? What can I tell you?
You know it's disappointing to see dumb people like you talk. That's what really disappoints me. It's sesame. It's guys like you man
Just too dumb to recognize like the truth when you hear I
Can't help people guys like you I can't help people I can't help guys like you talk
Gotta wake up man. I know how old you are a car man, but you gotta you gotta smarten up son
You gotta wake up in life
Do the right thing man have some integrity put it put down those drugs put down that beer
Get sober man sober up
Start thinking critically man. I'll tell you again start thinking critically and sober up
Maybe you might start learning a few things man
Maybe you might start getting some truths that you haven't gotten before in your entire life
Stop watching that mainstream media stop turn off that TV turn off that TV man throw it out unplug it man
You got your phone there you got your your smartphone your Android phone or your computer whatever do their research on your phone or your computer
You don't need that TV anymore, man
They've been lying to you and when you go on your phone in your computer go to
Go to truthful websites, man. Don't don't watch the mainstream media
Again, you get your truth from YouTube. You know what YouTube is good for it's good for stuff like like these streams
Or maybe watching songs like from the 80s and stuff like that or watching whatever videos cat videos
There's there's good things on YouTube man, but it's garbage when you don't want to know the truth
There's nothing there's no truth on YouTube man. They censor the truth
You got to get that through your head any kind of truth. They're gonna censor it man
They're just gonna keep you dumb down
They're gonna let you watch things like sports and they're gonna watch other things like like the music industry like athletes
I mean like
Actors and actresses movies. That's that's a distraction man
If you really want to know that you do what I told you go on bitch you look up your rope with the last battle full documentary and
Look up the greatest story never told on bitch you to run rumble around Odyssey. I just gave it to you right there
I just gave you the sources man. You got no more excuse now. You know got any more excuse
I told you what to do. I told you where to look for and what to find I told you what to write
Europe of the last battle full documentary the greatest story never told find it on bit shoot
It's that simple man, it's that simple
What don't you you you lip-tart clowns get don't you lip-tart idiots get hypocrites idiots good grief
Astonishing how people can be dumb and you just you rather walk off a cliff at the government
Let me ask you a question Tark your guys like Tark as like those those lip-tart is there
If the government asks you it tells you to jump off a bridge because it's safe for you
You're gonna do it because you already did it with your with the injections
They told you to take an injection. They didn't tell you what the ingredients were you blindly listen to them
You blindly took it
So if you did that then if the government tells you then the media and the governments
They're gonna tell you to jump off a bridge. Are you gonna do it too because you already did it by taking the injections
And by taking that PCR test crap
Then it goes right through your blood-brain barrier
They poison you it poison you with that when it goes through your blood-brain barrier your blood-brain barrier and
Goes right to your brain and the injections they poison your entire body
And they give you end up giving you blood clots and they load with they load your body with a graphene oxide
They wipe out your immune system. I just told you what it does the injections
Wipes out your immune system after three injections you've wiped out not 70% of your immune system
You know that the human body needs an immune system
You know the year very like a risk if of of not being able to heal that if you catch like any kind of infection or
Severe cold you can actually die if you don't got an immune system
Then you've compromised your immune system if you're taking two or three injections or more
Even one's too much man, but definitely two or three definitely three or more men. You've literally you're living on borrowed time
I don't want to I don't want to scare you man or or give you negative news, but then give you sad news
That's the reality, man. You compromise your immune system and you're gonna get that that it's either gonna be fast cancer slow cancer
But it's gonna develop man
There's a reason why they didn't tell you the ingredients man
There's a reason why you can't sue them once people die once they get sick
You know how many people in the world across the world and if every different country they got sick and they got disabled for an entire life
I mean for their entire lives. They got disabled like all kinds of disease. They can't walk anymore. They got
Trembling and shaking they can't stop a bunch of problems man half of their face paralyzed
I got my growth my brother's girlfriend half of her face got paralyzed
She took four more injections ever since she took the injections half of her face got paralyzed
You think that's acquaintances you're gonna tell me that's acquaintances dark you faggot you idiot wake up man
That's not a coincidence. It's a poison injections that did that to her
I even said to my brother my brothers just like you like idiots like you like a talk
Just like ignorant people like that. Hey, my brother says to me. Oh, I just want to talk about this
Okay, but how come your girlfriend have her face paralyzed? I didn't want to tell him that I want to tell him that actually
But I did because I got a heart. I don't want to tell them that I want to tell the truth
But I can't he doesn't want to talk about that's why I don't talk to him anymore. He doesn't want to the truth
I can't help
But happened that the fact remains he wonders why his girlfriend half of her face paralyzed because she took the injections man
Look what it did to her body it poisoned her and that's what happened man
They took the inject they blindly took something that they didn't know what it was they didn't do any research
They didn't even take the time of doing your research
It's just hurried up and got in line and took that poison injection like many others like like 80% of sheep out there took them
70 to 80% of the people worldwide took those injections. Come on man
Gotta be smarter than that man. You can't play with your life
They threw out the throw away their lives out of simply being ignorant and being too busy to do
Do it like a few hours of research a few hours of their lives could have saved their lives
A few hours of research could have saved their lives
It saved my life man
It only took a few hours of research for me to find the truth for me to avoid taking those poison jacks
Why because I simply had the desire to know the truth. I said to myself are these things safe?
I asked myself critical questions
And sincere questions are these things safe? What's the real point of it? What's the real reason behind it now?
Come they don't tell the same greenest and where are these side effects are there side effects to it?
You know like I was worried about I was concerned
Took the time to do some research. I found out shouldn't take them. It's dangerous didn't take them. I avoided it. Thank goodness
Now it's in our foods at the thing. That's the other problem. That's another story
They're putting in our foods of these injections now
They're able to put in the lettuces and tomatoes and other things that are injecting the animals. They're injecting
pigs and cows and chickens they're able to inject factory factory farms are able to inject animals
with those injections so it's in our food but it's not as bad as the injections but it's just the
same we're being poisoned right now and the only way to go around that is to get this constantly
detox if you're not able to raise your own food and grow your own crops and stuff and you got to
you really really literally got to spend hundreds of dollars on detoxes and and then supplements
that like you see a light supplements stuff like that and i've rebecked in hydrochloroquine if you
Yeah, I can't afford that can't afford to do that. So I'm poisoned like like many other people not as bad as injections
But I'm poisoned too. We're all poison. Everyone's poison
The question is not if things are poison the questions if
Things you gotta ask yourself. What's not poison? It's not it's not if things are poisonous
What's not poisoned? That's the real thing. That's a real question
But that's it. That's
It's what it is. How can I tell you?
Yeah, look how well I'm doing yeah, but Jim I already had a mental health problems Mary had depression like I struggled depression for a long time
I'm not as bad as now
I'm sure like the poison or food man the poison that they put in our poison or food supply and our water supply
The fluoride and everything that's it's gotten to me. No, I've been drinking water my entire life
I've been drinking water from the faucet like tap water my entire life, man
That's I'm afraid it's it's done harm to me too man
It's what fluoride does it shrinks it shrinks our pineal gland in our brains and our brains
We had I think all the pineal gland in the shrink's or pineal gland the fluoride they put water
And they put all kinds of other stuff too in water. That's
that you don't even know about, it's microscopic, you can't see it, you got to put it under a microscope.
By the way, you want to talk about microscope, like I said earlier, those injections,
and the so-called virus, if there ever was a virus, they were never able to isolate any virus
under a microscope. Now, what does that tell you? That's another proof out there. That's another
proof that the whole pandemic thing was a lie. It was a, it was a pandemic.
why do you think they call it a pandemic? Even some of their leaders, some of the world governments,
they accidentally called the pandemic out live on camera once. Once there was a press secretary
a couple of years ago, she said that, she had red hair, I forgot her name.
She said as she accidentally said that she accidentally said the plantemic you know
Because she knew because they got meetings know that the summits that she summits and then the meetings that he got in private
They talk about these things what they're gonna do and how they're gonna use the media and the government stuff fool everyone
And now they can all be part of the same agenda and what they're gonna say the people whether they're planning on doing over the long term
They got a long-term picture, you know
They're agenda 25 and they're Jenna 23. They got a long-term
Projection and picture of what they're doing to humanity. It's these things are not by accident
It's too bad because it's sophisticated, but for the wrong hands, you know, it's it's crimes against humanity man
It's terrible. It's terrible that to think that they got the technology and they're using it like that
You know, like, you know, you think you think God's not upset me think Jesus Christ
You think he's happy when he watches what's happening on earth men
There's so much evil and corruption on earth men. It's it's terrible, but he sees Jesus Christ sees the injustice
You know heavenly father sees the injustices that are happening to us on earth. He sees everything has been done man
It's crimes against you many it's crimes against animals. There's just no justice man
Just see out there. It's distractions, man. You're what you see is it's not really what's what's really going on
It's an illusion what you you're living in a matrix and it's a it's an illusion bottom line to give you the general picture
They're keeping you busy and distracted while they're never telling you the truth
You're gonna go through your entire life not knowing the truth if you don't do your own research
If you don't do your own research if you do your own research, you might snap out of it
You might get out of the matrix. You might at least see what's going on
If you can afford to get out of the matrix you can afford to detox and take supplements and they get out of the big cities
And and grow your own food and your own crops if you're lucky enough to live on the countryside
But if for us that were stuck in the city who and anyone that stuck in the cities and they're poor
We're in a bad situation guys like me. I'm poor. I'm in a big city. I can't do nothing right now
It's it's easier said than done. You know when you you're forced to drink the tap water you're forced to drink that the foster water that's
Well, you got to buy a water purifier or reverse osmosis water purifier if you want to purify your water
By the way to throw that in there you can purify your own water
But you need to reverse osmosis water filter that you need to connect to your faucet of your tap water
But if you can't if you're not willing to do those things you can't afford if you're not willing to do that
Then then you're gonna be poisoned man
You're not gonna be able to to avoid it man because it's in our food and water
On top of the on top of them springer crops and by the way, that's another thing
There's they're paying their farmers man
They're paying the farmers and they're buying them off and they're bribing them off and they're even
scaring of intimidating
They're they're getting these tractors and these machines that they go through the crops of the farms of the fields of
Every field there that the fields are like their fruits and vegetables
There's springer fruits and vegetables with poison with a bunch of stuff man
Stuff that you can't even wash off with water and from the documentaries. I've seen it
Stuff that you can't wash off potatoes and tomatoes and apples and and oranges and other stuff and other fruits and vegetables
That's what they're putting toxic poisons on our food
They're injecting the animals with poison. They're poisoning our fruits and vegetables. What's not poison?
What's left? It's not poison with the seeds even the seeds and the nuts the seeds are poisoning
It's just hardly anything that's not poison anymore
Whatever whether it's it's meat or fruits and vegetables or or flour or cheese or anything
It's everything the dairy if he's thinking that the dairy's poisonous contaminated the inject the cows
So that's the entire
Steaks the milk the cheese as poisoned to
the
And you're not getting reality from watching TV every day. That's why I say through all your TV
Or else you're gonna keep being lied to you want to keep being lied to where you want to know the truth
If you want to stay dumb down your entire life, that's your choice. Go ahead. It's your choice
You want to know the truth man do what I told you? It's as simple as that
I don't know what else to tell you. It's as simple as that
It's that simple
No, you can save the world and one person at a time. Maybe you got to speak the truth, man, but it's it's a never-ending battle
I only got so much energy, man. Like I I lost interest. I don't talk to people anymore. You know what from people like you, man
I'll tell you that for me. It's like do you they call us conspirators. It is like you
Always the time and it's to moralize. You know why because I drain myself of my time and energy
I waste my time and energy trying to tell you idiots people like you not everyone but dumb ignorant people like you
That's a dumb comments like that. They're too ignorant too dumb
Like too immature and childish
Actually be serious and to take something seriously for once in their lives take something seriously
I even told you I said don't take my word for it do your own research
Check out the sources. I gave you but if you're not willing to do that
I can't help you and you you're only gonna prove yourself to be ignorant dumb
You're proving right now that you're dumb in your ignorant me. I'm not dumb and ignorant me. I'm not saying crazy conspiracy theories me
I'm telling you the truth man. I'm dealing with reality. I'm doing what Jesus Christ would do man
I speak the truth no matter what and I'll die telling the truth. I'll never sell out like you man
I'm never gonna do it like certain people not in everyone in general. I'm saying certain people now
I'm never gonna sell my soul man
I do what's right, man. I do what the Lord would do, man
When you got a pure heart, a sincere heart, man, and you turn to Jesus Christ's full purpose of heart, man
It changes the way you live, man
it changes with you. I'm not perfect. I make a bunch of mistakes too, man. Sometimes I do dumb
things, but darn it, man. I stand for you, man. I don't do anything bad, you know? I don't go out of
my way to hurt people. I go out of my way to help people. I go out of my way to save idiots like
you, idiots that are hypocrites, idiots that are ignorant like you. I go out of my way to try to
save you, just like the Lord would with tendons hand to you, his arms of mercy. I try to help
you too. I try to reach out and help you. I try to reach out and touch someone, you know?
No, but intended I try to reach out and touch someone it helps someone by by speaking the truth man
If that's the only thing I can do that I try to do it
It's it's bigger than it's stronger than me sometimes. I gotta tell the truth man
I want to help people man my entire life. I always try to help people when I can I just
Can I tell you man? I just it's how I am. I try to do what's right always try to do it
Oh, I always stood up for what's right stood up for what's right my entire life
The way it should be man the ways people should
You got integrity man. It's true happiness man. You can't
Can't buy a happiness man. Even if you're a millionaire, man
If you're a rotten person, you're not a good person, man
You're not gonna be happy you can be miserable and that's not true happiness wickedness never was happiness man
Now that's what the Lord said wickedness never was happiness a
Piece of mind that comes from obeying the Lord's commandments. That's priceless. That's true happiness man
That's peace of mind, peace in your heart, peace in your soul, you know?
Yeah, Jen, how's it hanging, Jen? How are the chickens?
I was just trying to speak I was rattling off some some subjects and some truths
You know I was talking about many different subjects, but it's all related to the same thing
It's all related to the crimes against you many from the globalists. I just went full circle
I mean I I talk about every subject, you know the poison Jaxons the 5g towers the the weather mod the weather modification
The corruption and the media and the governments everything
I just I literally nailed it nailed everything you know like one after another one subject after another
I talked about I don't think I was gonna talk about these things tonight, but
this morning, but I did
See, I guess you can say that you tuned into the right time you checked it out at the right time
Is you're not gonna see that again. You're never gonna see another guy like me again. You're gonna see drunks and
Drunks and people high on drugs like you usually see but you're not gonna see guys like me often
This this was a once in a lifetime maybe occurrence, you know
once in a lifetime event
These things don't happen often. I'll tell you that
I don't know, I think you're interested in telling the truth, man, or else you'd stop watching it, man.
You got to get on board, man, the train of truth, man. The righteous train, you know?
I'm telling you to talk a guy like you talk
I would just tell you man turn your heart to Jesus Christ turn to turn to Jesus Christ in full purpose hard man
Stop being a hypocrite that's just be honest with yourself be honest with God be honest with Jesus Christ beyond to yourself
Then you can be honest with others you gotta be honest literally with this one comes down to be honest with God
With Jesus Christ be honest with yourself, and then you can be honest with others. That's what I do man
I'm not bragging. I'm not bragging just saying I
Joke around about a bunch of stuff man, but I don't joke around about truthful subjects
about what's going on on earth I
Was once happy man, but I'm sold up with these these globalists and maybe so depressed by poisoning me and
Making everyone dumb down like it's sorry. It's hard for me to find any joy. I don't got any more joy
It's depressing, but that's just I'm depressed too like I got my own problems
My mental problems I struggled with but it's really gone worse man. I was happy before then 10 years ago
I was happy well, it's five years ago. I was happier. You know, it's really the last five years man
It's you got admit it's the worst time we've ever lived in right things were better before things were better five years ago
10 years ago 15 years ago 20 years ago things were way better in the 2000s even in the early 2010s
2015 to start getting worse in 2000 the only good thing about the 2000s the 2010s Trump got elected in 2016 man in November 2016 he finally won
The finally they're all their problems one and then they finally had some some leadership
You know for the USA things are going well in 2017 18 and 19
But then everything turned around Trump sold out to the globalists at the end and they gave him orders and he took them
Then we had we were stuck with Biden for four years
And look what happened
You see how the country got worse?
how it uh
Was it was not about corruption and incompetence for four years now?
You finally got someone that's actually doing something good. He's still taking orders from the globalist, but it's it's far less better
It's that the lesser of two evils, you know
It's it's far less bad than it would be under the Democrats man
The Democrats would have literally like a he would have collapsed our country already at least Trump was we still got a small chance to survive
at least the criminals are getting deported now, some of them, but that's also a puppet show to appease the sheeple
not enough it's getting done, but at least there's good things getting done
it's not enough, but there's good things getting done
and finally some truth, some competent people are there, like Caroline Levitt, the press secretary for the White House
at least she's competent, there's other good people like Pam Bundy, the Attorney General
There's good people now in leadership and we got we got Tom Holman the director of national security
I think yeah, there's good people now in power. There's good people in the White House and
In charge, there's still many corrupt people. There's you still got some corrupt
Governors like in California in the liberal states, you know, it's
Democrat states, it's too much corruption. It was gonna be corruption. That's life on earth
Yeah, you know the 5g man and they use it as excuses. It's fast. That's an excuse man
It's the you know, I told you I told people before the 5g was only meant that the harm you man
That that internet thing that fast speed internet, that's a pretext. That's an excuse man that to put that out there
They never asked for a permission to put those towers man
Those things are meant to give your radiation poisoning and look it up with 5g tower dusty
Look it up with 5g radiation dusty man when it does to the human body to the human brain and the vital organs
What does it do to your vital organs in your brain? Look that up man. You're gonna see what 5g does
Go ahead go on bitch you and search a man once again. Don't take my word for it
Find out and see what you see you find out with radiation frequencies with frequent frequency radiation poisoning from 5g towers
That's radiation man. You don't see it. These things are called
Invisible weapons for silent wars. Okay. I'll say it again. Listen pay attention
Invisible weapons for silent wars and they kill you off slowly without even firing off a shot
They don't even need to fire a gun. They just use their silent weapons, man
They're quite weapons or silent weapons for quite wars
Invisible weapons for silent wars because the radiation poisoning. It's invisible. You can't see it
It penetrates right through a right through a building a concrete building it can go through concrete bricks
They can go through
Go right through a building man of a of a of a distance of up to two three kilometers far away
And that's why they this they strategically place 5g towers towers
Throughout a city throughout a town in a city at certain spots
They strategically place them so that they encircle you the encircle you with with 5g radiation, man
They're able to zap you man. They're able to like poison you and with the radiation poisoning every day
You're losing your eyesight slowly those headaches that you get sometimes those terrible headaches man
You didn't get those before you didn't get those five years ago. Why do you think where you think your vision is going down?
Why it's the 5g towers man. It said radiation poisoning from the 5g towers. That's radiation poisoning
That's doing that to you. Why are you developing cancers faster than the poison injections that you took?
Those are the reasons man people are getting sick people are getting all kinds of cancers cancers are many different things
They've never got why you think they can't explain the cancer the cancer rates the cancer rates are through the roof
They have never seen that it's an increase of like 300% of cancers cancer rates went up like two or three hundred percent
And they can't explain and they can't explain they won't explain because they can't tell you the truth on the mainstream medium
Go on the alternative media you're gonna find out right away. Why it went up like that. It's those
Injections man, they don't tell you what's in those injections and they're not liable. You can't sue them for it
It's part of a well-designed plan, but for the wrong purposes, man
If you can't see that by now, man, what can I tell you?
Not able to get through you unable to help you if you can't see it
If you know if you don't even want to do the research you mean you may not believe me now
But once you do the research if you take the time take it take just one hour
I think do a little bit of research and you can ask yourself more questions
You're gonna want to know more and once you learn the truth
You can't unlearn the truth once you find out certain things you can't unlearn that you know once you find out the truth and the deception
So you're gonna be very surprised first of all and then very upset you're gonna go through the stages man
You're gonna be upset depressed shocked
Disappointed all that stuff, but at least you're gonna know the truth, man
You deserve no truth, man. You deserve to know the truth
If you don't want a little truth and stay ignorant keep watching the television man keep watching the mainstream media and stay dumb
What can I tell you stay dumb down and keep writing dumb comments in the in the comments section?
Well, she want to be a man and you want to stand up for what's right?
And if you want to do it for yourself first and then do it for others
And then once you find the truth then you can do like me and try to share the truth with other people once you find the truth
First learn it for yourself first find out the truth for yourself
Then you can share with other people man what you learned and if people call you conspiracy theorists
And then you're gonna then you're gonna know how I feel because I did because I feel like that
They've been calling me a conspiracy theorist ever since I found out the truth man before I was like you maybe 10 years 15 years ago
I was ignorant, but I knew about things a long time ago
But especially but really especially the last five years my my eyes really open man
I really like it saw things that I can't believe we can't believe it
I knew about it, but I knew about the corruptions and the crimes against humanity and the anti-white narrative and stuff like that
Like how they're harming us white Christians and trying to depopulate us and trying to race us white Christians
I knew about that for 15 years now 20 years now, but now I really not know everything that I want to brag
But I I don't think there's anything I don't know now
Pretty much know everything about what they're doing to us
There them, you know the globalists the bankers
What aren't they doing? But you can't go out on the street and like say like I wouldn't go on the street and start talking like that
I don't like I think they're really gonna think I'm crazy and say lock this guy up
He's crazy. He's a conspiracy there. So you put him in a mental hospital
He can't he got it certain
There's a certain way to say these things when the conversation comes up and when someone's willing to listen like right now
I'm saying these things on the internet
But I couldn't go out on the streets and say this stuff like that unless I want to get arrested
And unless I'm looking to get arrested or put in a mental hospital. I can't do that. Yeah
I'll give you one last example. You only rolled out the PCR test man and people are lined up
They were lined up outside and close to where I live. I'll tell you this one last story thing before I get off
And I saw people waiting outside it like in 2021 to those late 2020 and early 2021
It was early 2021
I think and people were lined up to get those PCR tests
You have to go inside like a little clinic, but some there's such a line of they have to wait outside
I was telling people outside. Don't go in there. Don't get those PCR tests. They're gonna poison it
You're gonna get poised that things gonna go right through your blood brain barrier and once you get that in your body
You can't get it out
That's dangerous. Not good for you. Don't take these jacks if you love your kid
Don't they they have their kids waiting for them in line. They're holding their kids
That's it. Don't go in there man. I said trust me on this. I know you don't know me
I know I'm a stranger, but I did some research. I found out things
Please at least do some research get out of this lineup go back to your house do some research on it before you take it
Trust me on this. I told them that just take my word for it, man
I know you don't know me, but I'm trying to tell you the truth here trying to save your life and your kids life, too
Don't take it and don't go in there
Many people didn't listen to me. I just talked to a few guys outside a few people outside
They were asking me questions asked me stuff, and I was answering I was trying to answer them as best I could
That was in 2021
I tried but it's just to say man. I did everything I could then I realized I can't save everyone
Then I stopped like I stopped like talking about so much. You know, like I saw that I can't help everyone
I want to help everyone. I want to save them
I was I want to save as many lives as I could but I couldn't because I know that it's gonna come across as
It's crazy. It's gonna look crazy. I'm gonna get called a conspiracy. There's but worse
Someone's gonna call the police and they can see this guy's crazy. He's bothering people
So they get him arrested and put him in in the mental hospital
You know, so you gotta be careful how you go about you know, you just the fine line now
I know you want to tell it some people told me you said I know you want to tell it you want to save lives but you can't
You can't some people are not gonna they're not willing to listen some people are just too ignorant and they're just they're too dumb
Some people are just too plain dumb. They're just plain dumb
And they're just ignorant some people you can't help it's like it's like someone told me once this guy called da told me
It's like a triage in a hospital
You save the ones you can and the ones you can't save well
You got to leave them behind and you got to move on to the next person because you won't be able to save everyone
And there's many people are gonna die and it's a tragedy. It's terrible and it's sad and it's disappointing
It's very sad and disappointing but depressing
But you can't save everyone so you got to move and keep moving on and save the next person save as many as you can
And the ones you can't save well, it's too bad
It's their choice. They didn't want to listen
Are they fell to the the peer pressure they came to the that's what some of the people in the side chat
I'm usually they came to the peer pressure, but I bet you if I talk to you one-on-one in person man
You're gonna smarten up you're gonna like take what I say seriously
You're gonna we're gonna look each other in the eyes like in person. I'll look at you right in the eye, man
You're gonna see I'm not lying to you're gonna see that I'm not telling you the truth
I'm straight up man. I don't I don't play games
I tell you that I tell you to you like it is like I okay
I joke around about other things like liposuction surgery, okay, but a certain things man like these things
I'm talking to you right now. I don't joke around about that bit. I'm telling the truth
I don't play games with that man when it comes to like telling the truth and
And doing what we're doing doing doing what our savior Jesus Christ would do and standing over what's right for humanity for animals
Oh, and I always do the right thing and I'm dead serious
I'll mess around still got a sense of humor and believe me I can laugh and really want to help you
I don't try to
Don't try to leave and I don't try to lead anyone into like
Into bad things. I try to help people man. That's my entire goal my entire desire. It's the welfare of people's souls
Man, it's their welfare. It's a save lives here. It's about saving lives
It's about helping people if anything just help them to know the truth man plant that seed in their head of
Of a righteousness truth, man
You doubt these things man if you just ask yourself man just think about it really think about it ponder it man ponder in your heart
Think about it in your head a little bit. You're gonna see that. He's gonna see that guy's not so crazy after all
He's he's so he's telling the truth in his own way
I'm telling the truth in my own way the only way I know how to do it man
The only way I've ever done it the only way I know how to do it
Do it the way I do it now
That's it. It's about
Boys I'm running out of battery. I'm gonna look at the comments section down
You're gonna need to leave
Get out of here. I've said enough man. I
Said enough man, you're gonna call me crazy
Some people some ungrateful people are gonna call me crazy and I called me as a conspiracy person trying to mock me
Sometimes once in a while guys you gotta know that you gotta hear the truth you you got it you got it
Sometimes it's good for you man to hear some truth, man
No, you might not expect to hear that and then I even make sense of it
but
After the way I describe and I try to tell it to you and then plain is some in simplicity
How can you not see it the obvious? Can I see the obvious man?
The truth man in plain is
Right before your eyes man in plain is that just like the Lord man
You tell him the truth and plain is and they still don't get it
That's the Lord himself saying that the certain he said that the people once
You tell the truth and plain as as plain as work can be
Yeah, they they they're led they're led a forestry by the devil the devil leads certain people away men into darkness
into confusion
The Lord's about truth man about righteousness
Jesus Christ, man. He's about truth and righteousness
Why do you think Jesus Christ atone for your sins man, so you can be saved what you gotta want if you got a
You got to ask you to reach out for help and you got to reach out reach out to his hand
And it starts with a sincere desire in your heart. You can't you can't you know, you can't fool a word
You can't lie. I mean you can't lie to Lord. He knows your heart. He knows your thoughts
He knows your thoughts in your heart. He knows your mind in your heart
He knows if you really want to know truth if you really want to do the right thing
He knows you man heavenly father knows you and Jesus Christ knows you that's a thing
You be honest with yourself be honest with Jesus Christ yourself and be honest with others man. You can't go wrong
That's how you got to go through life, man. You got to be honest. You got to be a good person and you got to stop being a
If you're not living a righteous life and you you're like you've been to that person your entire life
Well, it's time you wake up and you're smart enough
You start doing the right things and you repent repent sincerely. It's not too late
That's all I'm gonna tell you about that
See what I can tell you just repent sincerely man turn away from your sins and start doing this right turn away from your sins and
Turn to Jesus Christ instead turn to Jesus Christ the full purpose of heart. It's that simple then
Do it it's so easy like the point of like the message of life that Jesus Christ's message so simple man repent
Turn to the Lord and repent and be baptized man and find eternal life man be saved
Through his mercy through his grace through his brain through through Jesus Christ's merits his atonement is his
Mercy and his grace and his mercy and his longsuffering his longsuffering towards the children of men turn to him man
You'll find your happiness. You'll be saved by turn to him turn to Jesus Christ
Do what's right. Stop being a slave to the system. Stop being a slave to the globalists
Change certain things in your life. Start doing a bit of research. It's it's all I'm asking it's not hard
I'm not saying to quit your job. I'm not saying to change your entire life. I'm just saying to do certain things differently
Yes, try to be honest with yourself may be also there's men start doing good around you starts start sharing that
Start sharing the truth with people when you can at the right time
Don't sound like a career. Don't try to sound like a crazy conspiracy. There's like, you know, like they're gonna call you that
Don't sound crazy. Don't go don't go overboard. You know the Lord say I'll tell you what the Lord said once
He said use boldness, but not overbearance. That's what I try to do
I know sometimes I may use I may try to be I may seem to be overbearing, but I try not to I
Try not to I try to be bold. I try to be bold but not overbearing
says you use boldness but not overbearing speak the truth with boldness man with boldness like
it'll shock people sometimes that's with boldness and speak the truth with boldness but don't be
overbearing help them spiritually and temporally spiritually with knowledge of the truth and
Feed the poor and the naked that don't give them food and water if they need that's what that's what he means
But that's what Jesus Christ means by you'll you'll help them spiritually and temporarily
If you don't help the beggar, man
If you don't help the poor person if you don't help someone that needs your help as someone that's starving on the street
Or that it needs to ask for your help
They're not asking for money but ask for your help
See someone starving in the street and you refuse to give them water or food then you got no interest in the kingdom of God
If you want to go to heaven if you want to be saved man start by helping others start by being Christ like start by helping others
Man doing good things doing what Jesus Christ would do
Follow him and follow his perfect example. You can't go wrong man
Then you're gonna find true happiness. You're gonna find peace to your soul. You're gonna find a you're gonna find the eternal life
You know find happiness on earth and happiness in the next life happiness for an attorney it starts
Turning her up to Jesus Christ turn eternal fulpers are that's what?
So it goes on you're gonna deal with problems your entire life
I'm not saying you're not gonna go through life. You're gonna go through problems and hardships
You're gonna go through problems and trials as trials and hardships
Man, you got to go through hardships on life. Look at this life on earth. It's hardships already
Look what we're going through. Look what we're being put through method the corruption the injustices
We got to fend for ourselves. We're gonna find the truth for ourselves because we're being fed lies by the mainstream media
But that's what life's about. It's about enduring this life on earth
We got to endure to the end we got to get through these hardships and these trials and these injustices are done to us
These terrible injustices are done to us. We're gonna be patient
Just like Jesus Christ was patients when he was like he was patient when he was on earth, man
He took everything. He did everything that
Voluntarily he did that he he gave his life for us
No, he didn't need to do that. He did it because he out of love. He did it for us out of love
When he said he suffered and died for sins man
Jesus Christ suffered and died for since he had toned for a sense because he loves us
That's the simple message of Jesus Christ
Love God and love your neighbors
The teacher is no better than the student the student is no better than the teacher
Everyone no one's better than anyone on earth. Everyone. It was fair. Everyone's equal man. It's gotta be fair
Everyone deserves like a justice and and kindness man. No one deserves to suffer no one
Every person on earth is a child of God every single person
No one deserves suffering no one deserves to suffer. I don't want to see anyone suffer
I don't want to see my worst enemy suffer man. That's how I feel if you want to know I feel I don't wish anyone dead
I don't wish harm on anyone
I simply wish for my enemies and for the bad people and the evil people out there to smarten up and to change their ways man
I'd like to maybe see them slap around a bit, but I don't want to see them suffer
I don't want to see anyone suffer not the worst people
I'm willing to forgive anyone that wants to to change their lives though anyone that's ever wronged me
I forgive them
Because if you don't forgive others Jesus Jesus Christ says if you don't forgive others
Then you can't expect to be forgiven for your own sins
He says you shall forgive others
He says I will forgive you for your trespasses against me as often as you repent sincerely as often user as often as you
Were you see no he says as often as you repent in the sincerity of your heart?
I shall forgive you and you shall forgive others for their trespasses against you for those that don't forgive their trust
The trespasses of others or go for those that don't forgive the trespasses of others. They've got no interest in the king of God
You got a free that's what his message on that was you got to forgive others
If you want to you want to be forgiven and forgive others
You can have peace of mind even if it's very hard sometimes you still get a fine in your heart
You got to dig deep you got to dig very deep sometimes and you got to forgive others man
That way you're doing what the Lord would do you're doing God's will you're doing what Jesus Christ would do
You can have peace of mind you can have true happiness because if you hold on to like certain things man
You can you're only gonna hurt yourself
You end up end up hurting yourself more than others more than anything and that's what Satan wants
Man, he's putting people in your way and he wants to harm you and wants to bring you down
He doesn't want you to turn Jesus Christ wants to pull you down
You gotta go you gotta break free from those chains man. You gotta you gotta rise above it man. Yeah
That's what it comes down to men is where we here on earth for men
We get a job. We make a living be supportive. We have families or supporter families
But you also gotta do good things you gotta stand up for what's right, man. Just Jesus go through your life
Not standing up for anything
Yeah, you gotta help others man. It's just it comes naturally if you really want to do what's good
You already got a good heart man. You're a good person comes naturally, man. You're gonna do us, right?
You know is he brought some people who probably already know these things and what I'm talking
I was just speaking for the people that don't know these things
I'm sure many people out there that are listening to whoever's listening
He probably knows what I'm talking about and believes it or can relate to it
I thought I just want everyone I would just want
I want the crimes against us white Christians and colored Christians. I want the crimes against humanity to end
That's what I want. Ivana. I want the injustices to stop, you know, I want the truth to be told
I want there to be justice for everyone
Because the riskier richer and the poor get poorer and I want the poor to finally
Stop suffering, you know, because we're suffering here
Look what's happening
Now there's no more middle class. There's no more middle class and it's either you're very rich or you're very poor right now
The middle class it's disappearing every day every every year is getting worse
He's getting worse by the month you're getting will the growth story more buy a can of soup under four bucks
And the middle class is disappearing, you know
It's hard now. It's getting harder. You know, it's they're doing that on purpose. That's by design
They want a financial collapse once they collect collapse economy
They're gonna it's gonna be food shortages
There's gonna be there's gonna be chaos and they're gonna lead to martial law
And once there's martial law, they're gonna lock everything down again
And then it's gonna do worse again to send people to prison camps the people that didn't take the injections the people that stand up to
the government's they're gonna send them first of the
Concentration camps to the to the prison camps the camps the camps the so-called
The internment camps and stuff. How do you say how they call me call my politically correct words?
So you don't call it British camp. They don't want you to call it a prison camp
The quarantine camps, you know, like that the things like
They see the people I could hold this and what prison can't they'll hold the you know that right that's the entire
I said that before the entire covert thing was a scam is it's combat
It's a plan themic the plan themic was it was a big scam was a big hoax one of the biggest lies ever perp ever
Purposuated on humanity
The entire pandemic since 2020, okay, not the pandemic, the pandemic was the biggest scam of the 20th century, of the 21st century, was the biggest scam in the last 200 years other than the lies that they told people about World War I and II.
Other than the fact that they lied about World War I and II, this pandemic that we just lived through the past five, six years, it's been the worst.
Then the worst crimes against humanity we've ever had because there's over two billion people worldwide. They got side-effects on those injections from those poison injections
And over 40 million killed worldwide
But they don't tell you that on the news never tell you that if you want those numbers
You really want the facts and the statistics you want the real statistics
You got to go on bit shoot
Rumble erotic and look it up on alternative sources alternative media
As they're gonna hide that they're paid millions of dollars to hide the truth from you, but I've talked about that earlier
I don't want to talk about it yet
I've talked about it before bottom deal that buying guy that Joe buying guy is not even the real Joe Biden. That's a clone
They got the technology that's nothing I didn't touch on yet. They got the technology to clone people
They've had it for for years now for even a few decades
They can they got technology to clone someone you can tell if that guy's not wearing it the actor playing Joe Biden
It's either an actor with a face mask or it's a it's a clone
It's either a clone or someone wearing a face mask. They got skin masks. It's called look that up
I'm bitching another thing skin masks
They can put a mask of anyone and it looks like a real face. It looks like the real thing
You'd never be able to tell
you know that the real Hillary Clinton, the real Joe Biden, the real Bill Gates, they're dead!
They've been dead for years! All these actors you see in Hollywood, these women in Hollywood,
that's another thing, one of the last things I'm going to touch on.
These so-called actresses, many of them are transsexuals, they're transgenders, they're male to female transsexuals, MTF, MTFs, male to female transsexuals, and even female to male transsexuals.
Most of these actresses are men, women, so-called women guys, people like Sandra Bullock and Cindy Crawford, the model, and other people like Julia Robertson and Taylor Swift, a bunch of others, they're men.
You know the Williams sisters and the so-called Williams sisters and tennis, you know the two tennis players that they look usually look like men
They got men arms and muscles and stuff. What do you think those are men? That's terrible. That's proven
There's many people that you think are women. They're actually men. They got surgeries to do is that they change how they look
They can they can shave the Adam's apple. They can they get all kinds of facial
Reconstruction surgeries. They got hip surgeries. They can they can make them look like a woman. They got voice changing surgeries
They got hormone blockers
They get them at a young age and they change they got voice changing things. So they sound like women these men
They portrayed themselves as as actors as actresses are actually actors. It's guys. It's it's men
It's real men. It's biological men that they're the these so-called actresses that you see like Sandra Bullock
I'll give you an example. You know that the name Sandra Bullock the last name Bullock, you know that stands for you
Know that if you break that word down in and another language, I think Spanish Bullock means a castrated bull
They're giving you clues guys
They give you clues with just their names and some of the things they say in the interviews that's a
Bullock means a castrated bull. You know that castrated bull means what do you think she is the castries castrated man?
She had a sex change. She had a section. She's a man. She's a man
Look at look at a picture of I dare you to look at a picture of Sandra Bullock from 1989 where she was in an interview
You can clearly see her before she got the surgery before she got the Adam's apple shaved
You can clearly see the Adam's apple in her in her neck
You can clearly see the the the the masculine traits in her face before she got the surgeries man
You can tell and many of these actresses these little actresses when they get older
They they look even more you can tell like it comes out even more that they're actually men and other people like like Michelle Pfeiffer
And Nicole Kidman. I found out that they were men too and I thought they were women. I even thought they were very beautiful
I even lessen after them. I thought they were women. No, they're guys. They were their guys too. Just like
This it's terrible. It's you wouldn't believe how much deception the level of deception and lies and utter like
Corruption and lies and deception. It's just that the seagulls they get off on that. You know, like they love fooling us the goyim
You know, they call us goyim the non-jews. They they fool us us christians us white christians and color christians
They fool us they love they get off on that yummy these it's such we've been lied to and decided look how they told people to wear face masks
in two thousand twenty two thousand twenty one two thousand twenty two when they rolled out the
pandemic they fooled everyone into wearing face diapers on their face face masks face diapers
you can arrest or you uh infection for wearing those things you can't even breathe i was walking in
the bus and the
In the street, I used to take the metro the subway system. I saw many people wearing those face diapers
Everyone fell for I'm one of the few people that didn't wear that face diaper
And I stood out in the crowd and people said, oh, he doesn't got his face diaper on
He's got to be crazy conspiracy theorist. He's not like else. He's not a brainwash sheep
Why he's not wearing his face diaper because I didn't fall for that crap and I did some research
I don't do like ever I don't leave I don't get a lid off a cliff. I don't jump off a bridge if the government tells me
If they know if they tell me to jump off a bridge, I'm not gonna jump off a bridge
Whatever they tell you don't do it. What if they tell the they don't tell you they tell you not to do do it
You know, that's what it's about
Whatever they tell you it's lies, whatever they tell you that are lies
Those are the truth. Those are the true things
If they tell you that something's a lie, well, that's the truth
And if they tell you something that if they tell you something
That happens to be if they tell you something that they want you to believe that it's the truth. It's actually a lie
You know what I mean?
Whatever they tell you man, it's not the way it is. It's not the way it appears to be
They've been doing that for us fooling us their entire lives
For the phase diapers and they fooled us they fool everyone to wear phase diapers now that was a joke
That was an entire joke and they laugh they leave it
They had interviews and they took them off and you see the pose for the camera
They pretend to take an injection in front of the camera
It was nothing in those injections that they took in the present certain present certain people they took an injection at the shoulder
People that they get people that they can fit they even asked celebrities to do commercials to take the injections
that that badly they push it on people they bright people and they try to like a
The fool people do it by bribing them at the taking those injections by giving them giving them giving away like
Contests and money and stuff and prizes and stuff. It's it's still like scandalous. It's so ridiculous
And yes, anyone that's intelligent can see right through that. It's only the dumb people and unfortunately, there's 70 to 80% dumb people out there
Like no offense that you guys the certain people that took them
But it's unfortunate 70 80% people that don't do any research that they're just there may be too kind or too gullible and too naive to
Do any research that actually take their word for them so many people like that they believe the government
They thought they weren't what being lied to you know the government's not your friend. They're lying to you
They liked my family. They liked them my friends. I lost many friends and family over that
You know, I'm not the only one anyone that stole the truth and the stupper was right lost family members and lost friends
Okay, it's happened to me. It's happened to many other people. That's how that's how I went down. Yeah, that's what happened
They were saying that the they took injections of it was empty injections. It was nothing in those injections
It was it was saline. They put it they put nothing as it was nothing was water
That's just a fool people the the actual injections
It's only people that took them they never took the actual injections the world leaders
You know the so-called world leaders the world's criminals you may believe it the world criminals and governments the world governments
They never took the actual injections. They know it. They know it was boys
They were told not to take them because it's boys. They only had that the population the people of the earth take them
the population, the general population, the general public take those injections.
Anyway, that's enough. I've had enough talking about all these things that I think I've said enough
about to leave. That's just about enough.
I'm going to read the side chat here.
Well, I ain't a cool man. I'm still alive, man. I'm still going.
That's one of the few people that didn't die man other people. They died spiritually and mentally man. Yeah, I'm just very depressed and I
Struggles anxiety and depression, but I'm still very much alive. I'm worried about that still life
I got back pain and stuff and not the same guy used to be
And not as healthy as I was in my 20s and 30s, but darn it. I'm still alive man at 44
I'm still alive and I'm still trying to endure this life on earth. I
Haven't given up yet
Yeah, man. I'm not gonna ask for any money. The truth of information is free, man
I like to give out truth of information for free, man. I don't ask for anything
I don't expect anything man
That's just if I can help just one person out of the crowd if I can save one life tonight
If I can help one person at least to know the truth and it's good then then good, you know, I'll feel a little bit better
And you help people you can feel better about yourself you can forget about your own problems and feel a little bit better when you help someone else
You know helping someone cost nothing. It's free. It's a free gift. You help people. It's free
Always free to help people
When you help people you should do it out of your heart man or the kindness of your heart
And you shouldn't expect anything out of return when I help people man in my life
And they help people with strangers outside, man. I don't do it. I don't expect anything that I expect just a smile and a thank you
That's it. It's the only thing I expect. It's a smile and a shake and shake. Oh, that's it. I don't appreciate it
I don't expect anything else
Yeah, we got one life, huh? Yeah, we go with life
That's tough. I'm not perfectly, but I've been struggling with depression for years. It's not easy
Depression anxiety
Trying to make the best of it. I'm not gonna complain. I got an apartment. I got my cat
Got a basic necessities maybe poor but uh I
Got my freedom. I got my privacy. I got my apartment. I got a lovely cat
I can't I can't complain
Some people are on the street some people are homeless. I'm not gonna complain. I appreciate the little things
You know, they're actually big things
Some people won't even got that in third world countries, man. They're dying of thirst
They don't got nothing to eat or nothing to drink and they don't got clean water
I got a shower. I got a bathtub. You can take a shower a bath of any time I want
You know some people in the country's only got that they're on the street
You know they can't even like stay clean or they can't even feed themselves or they can't drink clean water
No, those things you got to appreciate
Yeah, I'm a true. I'm a true humanitarian man. I'm a true Christian man. I'm a true father of Jesus Christ
I'm down to 4% battery I gotta get off I gotta go charge my phone
I didn't realize that I have 4% battery here. I've been talking for such a long time
They even check the battery
I gotta plug it in
How about they get off here? I'm gonna read this section the comments section
I'm gonna scroll up here real fast
4% battery unbelievable. I went from like 90% battery to 4% battery. I asked what I want to say before
I don't know if I said I said the
1% of people the 1% in the world the globalists they're 1% okay the billionaires the trillionaires
They're 1%
The you know the ones in the governments the corrupt people the evil people the world the ones with billionaires and the trillionaires
They got the money in the power the 1% don't want us the 5% us the people the so-called conspiracy theorists
Us the people that tell the truth that stand up for humanity
They don't want they don't want us the 5% to wake up the other 90% that are
Sleeping that are ignorant that are calling us conspiracy theorists the 90% that don't know what's going on the good people
There's good people in that 90% so many good people, but there
Don't know what's going on with taxpayers that view that they go blindly not knowing the truth their entire lives
They don't want us the 5% the 1% don't want us the 5% to wake up the 90% that's how things work
90% of people in the world that don't know what's going on. They don't know the truth
Unfortunately, it's that bad. It's it's really like 90%
But it's an even like maybe 95% that know know the entire truth of what would happen in World War one and two
And they know don't know the entire history another thing. I want to say before I leave the entire
History was rewritten they rewrote history
They lied to us about World War one and two and they lied to us about many other things
But they rewrote history and the victors of the wars are able to write the rewrite a
History they're able to rewrite history and write the future
We don't learn anything from the past wars. We're doomed to make the same mistakes
And we're doomed for the same fate as what happened before in the 19 in the 1910s in the 1930s from the world
We're one and two and other wars before that before
When the Vikings finally took care of that the problem back in like the 1500s and the 1600s the 14 hours
I don't know which decades was centuries. I mean which centuries but the Vikings and the Crusades really took care of it
but then
later on you know like
The Jews and the group people in the world that started taking
Taking everything with the media and started
Managing everything and fooling people for the last 200 years last 150 years the newspapers and the TVs came out and they liked us
They've been like they've been lying to us for entire lives. Literally. You want to know the truth?
You gotta search it for yourself
You'll never get any truth on any media any any mainstream media. You're not gonna get the truth
You're gonna get distracts and sometimes you're gonna get like some some nice stories like if people helping people
It's the things like like some happy stories there
But really like the generally and basically it's gonna be nothing but the distract you they're never gonna get to the real issues
The real points is to keep you distracted long enough for them to get away with their stuff
And as they further their agendas as they advance their agenda
They're keeping you distracted and dumbed down day by day and you're getting dumbered by the day
You're getting sicker by the day. You're getting more problems physically and mentally by the day
They're keep they keep as they keep the entire population dumbed down
That's their entire goal. That's the entire purpose that they're depopulating us one by one slowly
But surely they're doing that. That's been going on for the last especially the last five years since 2020
Five years six years now going on six years. We've really been the
We've been hit hard by the globalists
Anyways, that's what's happening. So I'm sorry short. You want to know the truth search it for yourself search for the truth
Stop believing the lies start thinking critically start doing it do it for yourself and your family and your loved ones your friends
Doesn't need to be gloom and doom every day
I mean just we thought I talked about that for now like it's been my subject for the past hour. I think our
an hour and a half and I don't even know what I've been talking about but
I'm just saying once in a while you need a you need a wake-up call you know you
are very serious talking about what's going on but it doesn't need to be like always
gloom and doom you can talk about good things too I'm just saying no I've talked about these
things and I said so many things I know it's going to come across weird it's going to come
across as conspiracy there's conspiracy theories but it's not it's just the truth
this is saying deal with the truth man and turn your heart to Jesus Christ that's the best thing
You only got one life, you know because once you die once you're you're no longer on this earth your your your
Your time on earth will be done
You can't like a you can go back and change it
You know like whatever you do on this earth is gonna decide it's gonna determine where you go in the next life, you know
If you want to if want to get back to living with Heavenly Father and Jesus Christ and you want to get saved
And you want to go to a good place in the spirit paradise instead of prison spirit prison instead of going to
The hell and like outer darkness and and if you want to go like it not everyone's gonna go to hell
Because it's just the worst people the worst murders worst killers to go to hell is you really?
Most people are gonna go somewhere
But they're not gonna be in the presence of God and Jesus Christ if they don't like repent of their sins and turn away
And they don't turn to Jesus Christ with full purse of heart. She got a
Gotta save your soul you got a soul to your due responsible for your destiny and on earth in life and this life on earth and the moral life
On earth. There's only one life like this. You got one shot at it
Make sure you do what's right save your life in your soul
Save your family save your friends if you can
There's many people as you can
But literally everyone's responsible for their own destiny. It comes down to you. You're the only one that can do it for yourself
That's that's between you and God, you know between you and Jesus Christ
Do what's right. You got nothing to fear. You got nothing to fear. Perfect love casteth out casteth out
Every fear, you know, that's what those Jesus Christ is perfect love castes out fear
You do what's right. You got nothing to fear because you can live in
enough peace of mind knowing that you're doing so right knowing that you got Jesus Christ on your side and knowing that he
Understands you he knows you he knows your heart and he knows what you've done
He sees your works if you've got if you do good works
He sees it if you do bad works to see that dude
He sees everything that you do you got to do good works. You see the good things that you do. I
Got nothing to worry about
You got to get through this life you get undurred I say to myself every day
I got to remind myself that pretty much every day. I got a
I'd give up and keep on going and try to take it one day at a time.
Some days are worse, some days are better than others, some days are worse.
But that's part of life. That's part of the trials on Earth.
You know, we really got nothing to complain about there's many people out there. They're really suffering
They're on the street and they got nothing and they got no money and some people are really poor
Some people are like locked up in prisons or they're in hospitals or they don't got a perfect body
They're not even able to walk some people there
You know, if you got your health and your freedom you got it so much like that's rich
I mean that's worth so much like you're a rich person if you got your health and your freedom
And you got somewhere to live like a house or an apartment
Gotta appreciate the good things you got you gotta live in gratitude. That's what I want to say
Anyways, that's it Tark
That's the last time you hear any truth for me Tark. I mean, that's the last time you hear anyone say the truth
You're gonna hear a back to your regular
Programmed dumb things on the internet and these internet chats start. Maybe you appreciate that better
Someone that's drunk or high on drugs
Talking nonsense and using vulgarity. Have you noticed guys one thing I haven't used one F word one vulgarity
I don't use vulgarity by the way. I know why I do that two things
I try to use clean language to invite the spirit, you know with me
Spirit of the Lord, you know they keep a good spirit and to set a good example
I try not to set a bad example
You're gonna hear me say things I the worst thing I call someone is a dumb person, but I don't call someone enough this and that
I try to I'm not perfect. I'm not saying I'm perfect. I'm just saying I try not to use okay
That's really one of my strong points. I got rid of my unclean language a long time ago years ago
I used to see the F word before and I'll do I change it from night to day
I decide to just stop using will carry
I try to use clean language
Try to set a good example because when you use a constant vulgarity every day
You know like you can't expect the Lord's spirit to be with you, man
If you want the spirit of Jesus Christ to be with you the Holy Spirit
You can't be using vulgarity man that pushes away the spirit pushes away the spirit of God
It pushes away the spirit of Jesus Christ. Can you see what I mean? I don't know if you can relate to that
But that's that's what it does when you use clean language, man, you're inviting the spirit into your heart into your mind
Gotta do us right. You gotta live it. You know, you can't just say it
You gotta live you gotta walk the walk you gotta talk the talk and walk the walk
You know, you can't just talk the talk and not walk you gotta do both
You gotta talk the talk and walk the walk
You gotta do it man. You gotta you gotta live you gotta
Gotta be real man
Gotta be gotta be authentic
Yeah, do us right
The other 4% Jim I don't know I was just saying I was just saying it's 1% of me too
I was wondering the guy said that once in the video said the 1% want the 5%
The 1% don't want the 5% to tell the other 90% what's really going on
Maybe he said maybe meant like maybe 94% or whatever like the 9% maybe the 1% don't want the 9%
To tell the other 90% what's really going on something like that Jim if you're still there
But anyways, it's just like a thing. It's a saying, you know, it gives you representation of the fact that the globalists are only 1% of the world that the evil corrupt people
the ones that got money and the ones that
Give words to the the world governments and stuff. They're only 1% and thus the population were like 95%
You know, there's 5% people that know the truth. They really know the truth of 5 to 10% of people there. You know, it's it's bad man
It's bad
90% it's a big number, but that's that's how bad it is. You know, like how many people watch mainstream media
How many how many people know don't know what I'm talking about right now only people
that these things are conspiracy theories how many people think that i'm just some crazy conspiracy
theories you know too many it's too bad it's too bad it has to be like that because if there was any
kind of transparency if there's any justice on earth that we wouldn't have these problems that
we're dealing with we wouldn't be in the mess we're in right now you know like if jesus christ
letter world governance there wouldn't be any problems man there'd be justice for everyone there
wouldn't be one poor person out there there wouldn't be one starving person on the street man if
jesus christ was in charge of the world when he comes back though for the millennium when jesus christ
Then they'll be justice then Satan won't be won't have power over people on earth anymore
There's not gonna be any more corruption lies. There's not gonna be any more pornography
There's not gonna be more violence and even any more wars or anything man
There's not gonna be any more of those gonna be under there's gonna be a hundred percent peace
It's gonna be peace and justice for everyone for a thousand years man
The good souls are gonna stay on earth of bad people are gonna get taken away
They're gonna get taken off the earth man off the face of the earth
Well, that's it man
That's it
JT you know that JT. I'm a machine of truth man. I'm a I'm a spark plug
You know DA call me that a spark plug once like Trump, you know, like speak the truth, man
But even better than Trump at the braying
Again, what you see was what you get with me man, there's no BS now
The only thing I do I joke around about a few things you see with me is what you get
You know what you're getting with me. You're getting the truth man. I stand by what I say man
I stand by what I say. I live it. I believe it
I stand up for it. I speak for that. I speak the truth. I speak my heart now
I don't mess around. I don't know if you play games. I you've seen a play games GT
I don't play games like you man. I'm not your kind of person man. I'm not a guy like you man. I'm not your type
Don't play games man. I don't like playing mind games
I like joking around I joked around like for years on the internet chess
But when I start speaking about the truth when I started getting on her on a roll
You know like I talk about the truth and like a truthful rant, you know
So I start speaking about the truth man. I don't I don't mess around
I don't I don't cut cork or I don't I don't cut any corners and I'll take four ways to say something
I'll beat around the bush. I just come out and say it man
I come out and tell you the truth man. It's good for you. It's good for everyone
It's good to hear the truth once in a while once you agree, man
It's good to finally hear the truth
After hearing you lies and deceptions and crap and nonsense and dumb things every day, man
Aren't you don't you find it refreshing to hear silent finally someone that says the truth man says what the silent majority think I?
Think it's refreshing man. I think it's much better
Anyways, that's it now
It's a game GT it's reality
Let's see here. What else people say?
scrolling up
Checking what people are saying. I
Just plugged my phone in the charger, but I'm still gonna leave man. I'm up
I'm at 11% battery now
But because I plugged my phone and the charger I'm about to leave man. It's seven four
I can't believe I've been talking for like for what two hours now
Unreal that two hours of talking on the internet. That's the first answer record man
I think I never went on this this long for talking on a panel
So once in a lifetime thing
What's the point the point is man
Do us right man the points to know the truth and to get the truth out there and turn your heart to Jesus Christ
And to stand up for what's right and for you many and for animals. That's the point to the person that asked me that
That's the point
Oh, I'm losing my voice to Mickey man. I'm like voice. I've been talking for like two hours man two hours and a half
I need a drink of water, man
I'm tired too man. I've been slept at 7.40. I've been up all night the entire night the entire evening
Think I'm gonna go to bed pretty soon
Why
All right as I said enough guys you've heard enough
I was able to help anyone tonight
And good they wasn't for nothing if I wasn't at the very least if it entertained you
They gave you something else to see something in a different viewpoint in different ways you really see things differently than good to me
Well, there'd be a my fans or my my haters
There'd be people that support me or people that try to put me down I
Don't wish anyone any hard man. I spoke for everyone tonight everyone
It's good enough for everyone
They're about telling the truth man, that's what's important me telling the truth and maybe entertaining people with few jokes once in a while
It's it
About to retire anyways. I don't think you guys I don't think you guys are gonna see me anymore in the chats
I wanted to retire for a long time now, and I'm gonna walk away from the chats. I've been chatting since 2019
I think it's been six years now enough. I gotta do something else my life
Besides it's the end man. That's almost the end
Things are gonna collapse soon the financial collapse the food shortages the world's gonna collapse man
That's the end of the world soon the apocalypse man
It's the end. Yeah, it's near the end
Nearing the end and last call man last call for people on earth for us on earth here
You're gonna need to buckle up and it's gonna be a wild ride
You need to buckle up pretty soon
Strap in strap yourself in and be careful man
Enjoy the riding it's gonna get rough man
It's gonna get a bit dangerous man, it's gonna get a bit rough
Yeah
I'll walk away GT man. I gotta retire. I go out as a legend though, man. I got a retire on top
Was a legend man the best there is the best there was the best there ever will be
Best there was man, that's you'll get the best you'll get out of the streams man
Simply the best man
Triple a triple a equality
I'm just joking. There's not the best
Just an honest guy. There's people that are more entertaining than me. I know I
Said too many things tonight, man. I said too much truth man. Oh well
Stand by what I said, don't forget that I stand by what I said do your research guys everything. I told you was true
One bit you look of a Europa the last battle. It's a 10-hour documentary
If you don't want to if you don't want to watch it for 10 hours
Just watch at least one hour trust me
You can know you never gonna see things ever the same again
You're gonna get so much like information that you never got you're gonna be happy that you found out the truth man
It's worth your time. Believe me. You only live one life take a few hours of your life that just watch those documentaries
You're open the last battle. That's one documentary and the other one
It's called the greatest story never told you can find those on bit shoot the greatest story never told you're over last battle
You find those on bit shooter rumbler odyssey
Yeah, I'm gonna find on YouTube. It's still available on a bit shoot
Not that I'm trying to plug it not that I'm trying to but I really want people to watch those things so they can finally
I'll choose they can finally see that what I was saying was true
They wasn't lies and there wasn't conspiracy theories
It's not conspiracy theories what I told you guys about those things
It's true about the World War one and two they lied to us about that
They rewrote history those things are true that they rewrote history
Then you don't believe me go ahead do the research
Don't take my word for it do the research yourself check it out for yourself the videos then the pictures
The testimonies of people, everything, if you wanted the information in those documentaries, man, it's verifiable and it's there, man.
Trust me, you're going to be very surprised by it.
Yes.
Of course, they never told you that they can't tell you that if everyone knew that man
The people were revolt man people with turning it turn on the government right away
If people knew just how much they've been lied to and the level of corruption deception if people knew it man
They would people maybe stop working people stop paying their taxes
Maybe if they knew the level of how deep it is out deep it went the level of deception lies and corruption and injustices the injustices of
Humanity and the injustice done to humanity. I mean this is terrible. If you really knew how bad it was man
Then we've been lied to for a hundred years. Think about us. That's not nothing
it's not just now we're being lied to we've been lied to for the past 150 years
they've owned the media for 150 years man what do you think i unplugged my tv like i said earlier
i unplugged my tv in 2020 i threw it out it made a decision i haven't had a tv since 2020 man
since the summer 2020 i was sick of it i started doing my own research man that's how i found out
all these things about what's going on i already knew about many things but there's many other
Took a decision I started being like I started doing my own research
I started educating myself man in the school of life. That's the best school there is man
Then when you get a kid then you can you don't need to send a more public school man
You can you can home teacher
Home school, I mean you can homeschool them and the homeschool is the best it's the best for your kid
Send your kid to a public school. It's nothing but bullying. Oh, if you kid wants to play with people
He can play with people when they're done at their school, whatever like you can play outside with kids
And I'm not telling your kids are not gonna be able to play with anyone
It's just don't send your kid to a public school, man. It's just it's
They're not being taught anything. It's literally like a babysitting center for big kids. These public schools literally
That's what it's what do you learn the school other than reading and writing when you're very young?
That's the only thing I learned in the school. I don't learn any
I didn't learn anything in a public school other than reading and writing at a very early age at a very young age
everything that
The important things that I've learned in my life were in the school of life. I learned at the age of 18
I learned how to weld I learned how to do a bunch of different work
I've learned how to do the instruction work certain things everything I learned was in life was in real life
It's like hands-on stuff in the school life of 44 years old
Start working at the age of 18. I moved out of my mother's house and made a man of myself at a young age man
I did everything for myself eat my stepfather. He didn't get along but he says I'm proud of you
I'm proud of you as you made a man yourself and yet you've worked
You know you worked hard for eight bucks an hour even if it was only eight bucks an hour
You still held the job for years you did that job and you worked hard you worked your butt off
Even drove your bike to work those days up a mountain when I was freezing cold living can't it's really cold up here
Especially in the winters
Anyways, the school of life
I was watching you learn everything a school of life and it makes a man out he makes a good person out you whether you're sure woman
I mean it makes a man out of you like it makes a good person out you know
That's that's what I mean that this schools you don't learn anything in schools
It's it's nothing but bullying and now they're teaching perversions to our kids in school
Why would you want to send your kids to a public school?
it's perversions they're teaching their your kids that they be if they're trying to confuse your kids that whether they're a guy or girl whether they
They're attracted to the guys are gross or the opposite sex
They're trying to confuse your kids completely you believe what they're doing to our kids man
They're trying to turn our little kids are our helpless children like four years old five years old six years old
Little like little children under the age of ten
They're trying to turn them into like faggots and gays and and they're trying to confuse them about their sex and their sexual orientation
They're trying to confuse our poor kids. They're going after it. They're not just going
After us they're going after her poor kids. You believe that well, that's what they do man
Because they serve Satan they don't serve Jesus you think they serve Jesus Christ. They serve Satan by doing that
Jesus Christ sees the injustice man. He's sure he's upset with that
God sees the injustice too many sees everything that's on earth man
And trust me his wrath is gonna come down on those people one day man
If they don't repent if they don't repent speedily and turn their ways man change their ways and turn turn Jesus Christ
They're gonna be judged for what they do what they did to us the crimes against humanity for messing with our children for messing with everyone
These crimes against humanity are gonna one day gonna catch up to man
They're not gonna go unpunished man. They may think they're getting away with it now
They're not gonna they're gonna lose their entire eternity for that. They're gonna lose their attorney
They're they're the ones they're gonna look they're gonna they're gonna be going to hell if they don't turn away from their sins
Man, they're gonna they're not gonna be able to come back to the presence of God one day for serving Satan their entire lives
They need to repent and really like change their hearts, but many of them they're not gonna come back
I'm just saying in an example like don't send you kids to a public school. That was my point. It's terrible
Home school your kids teach your kids good values. That's the best thing you can do if you got kids if you plan on getting kids
There's nothing they're gonna learn in school other than reading and writing and you can even teach them that
Yourself like I could teach my kid if I had a kid out of reading ready. That's not hard
You know, it takes just maybe a few days a few weeks. That's not hard. If you want so worse you can do it yourself. Anyway, that's it
What I have to say
Also, you're up now JC. You're not sleeping anymore, huh?
Are you looking for a discount for liposuction surgery JC? I can't help you with that right now
We're not giving the 40% discounts anymore. It's not available anymore JC. You don't need to lose that fat on your own
You'll need to lose that fat on your body JC on your own because I'm not able to offer you any discounts
But I know you can afford it though
You can afford the liposuction surgery at full price because you're rich like you say, right? You're not poor
A rich woman like you JC you can afford the liposuction surgery
But see when I say jokes, I don't like I don't cross the line. You see that's another example
I say jokes like the layover liposuction surgery. I call people fat sometimes. I don't go too far
That's the farthest I go. I don't use vulgarity. I don't tell people like JC to die
Like JC tells me to go die sometimes he tells oh I have fof and die or go fly a kite and rush her
She tells me to die. She tells me to go die with my cat. She does my cats ugly my cats dumb
now i think maybe you're the one that's dumb gc you you're dumb in your heart you're dumb in your head
you're too ignorant to see what i'm saying you can only make fun of people like me
because maybe it makes you feel better because you're you know you're very ignorant you're empty
and you got nothing in your heart in your life but
Just know that I don't wish any harm to you. So you just know that I have to tell you a special message to you
JC, I don't wish you any harm
I actually wish you good things even though you put me down and other people down that are poor and are depressed and struggle with
Depression anxiety and we're sad and we're suicidal sometimes you try to put us down, but it's not easy to deal with
And we got that people like that in every one of our families like in your family you got people like that
I'm like that in my family. I got problems like a depression and anxiety, but it's not cool for you
It's not very nice you JC to do that to me and other people sometimes. I see how you talk to other people like people like
Anyone like people like auto people like Elvira
You talk to people like anyone he talked to me talk to that Joe guy that Philly Joe guy
Yeah, you tell people to go die. Who says that who says to someone to go die? I never wish you to die JC
I never wish harm on you. I don't wish harm on you. I don't tell people to die
Heck I don't tell my worst enemy to die. How can you tell people that go on your panel or die?
I don't I never got that about you JC like sometimes you you really go too far and you exaggerate
But that's what I had to tell you JC
But I don't wish you any harm though just
Just keep calling me a conspiracy theorist, though, huh, Jason?
Keep calling me a conspiracy theorist, a conspiracy theorist,
and say that conspiracy theorist is the things I say and try to put me down and make fun of me.
Even though I stand for you, man, and you stand for nothing.
What do you stand for, Jason?
You stand for your money and your material things.
What do you stand for?
You like animals because you call my animal ugly and dumb you call my cat ugly and dumb when you when you're not happy
And when you're in a bad mood or when you get high on your drugs that you take sometimes
You're marijuana you take at night whether you take those gummies or whatever the spray is whatever you call it
Anyways, just know I don't wish any harm JC and I don't think it'll see me around too much anymore
That's why I don't go to your stream anymore either because I see them not welcome with your lip darts there on the panel like Angie and Monica
They're gonna stay ignorant for their entire lives and they're probably gonna they're gonna die ignorant
They're gonna they're gonna stay ignorant probably die ignorant not knowing the truth and calling people like me conspiracy theorists
That's okay though. I wish you and everyone else the best. I don't wish you any harm
I wish you no harm whatsoever. I mean, I'm just gonna retire from the chance on that's why you're not gonna see me anymore
I came on this panel earlier yesterday uh tonight this morning
It's my pure chance that I end up being on the panel like this such a long time for two hours and a half
Said what I had to say I stand by what I see I'm just gonna retire and try to do other things now
With my life and move on as I can do better things than waste my time
I can actually get out there and help people I got the capability of helping people I got back problems
My back really hurts lately. That's what's been preventing me from working if you want to know the truth JC. That's for you. I
Can't work full-time anymore. I got a bad back and I got a hard time standing up
I got severe mental health problems anxiety and depression
I'm still trying to live and survive and maybe one day I'll be able to help people to get enough coach
I get out there and really like help people full-time
As they're just talking to people on a panel like this, you know, because that's not really helping enough people my message ain't going far enough
Because I get censored by people like you they try to censor me when I go on your stream
You know, I first I provide good content. Yes censor me. Yeah do everything that
embarrass me and make me look bad
Sometimes you were kind but many times when you got their liptards like Angie and Monica you simply take their side
You take me off the panel you lower my volume you take me back stage
You take me off the panel you ban me a time me out do a bunch of crap
You know a bunch of unfair crap that I've never do to you, but that's you you want to do that
That's your right. That's your business. You're right. It's your stream
But then you're not gonna see me in your stream anymore
I think because of that I'm sick of the you know the double standards the double standards and hypocrisy JC
I just can't
Can't take that anymore. I don't want to get mad at people anymore either. I'm not looking for arguments anymore
And I don't want to get mad. I don't want to raise my blood pressure anymore
I've done that before I made mistakes of raising my blood pressure and letting you and people like you get to me
I don't do that anymore. I'm gonna move on my life and do other things
I know I can do things I can do good things my life and better things because life's short
You know, I want to do other things. I want to stop wasting my time because time's short
Life's going by and I'm wasting time
You help me twice you help me three times GC and you use that ever forever against me
You know GC if I if I had known you would have used that against me
I would have never asked you for your help that one time
I asked for your help twice. I think in two years you help me once and you help me again
You help me twice. I asked for your help and the other time you the third time you offered me help
I was very appreciative and I you know, I told you I even told you in private emails
I thank you. I thank you in front of everyone on the panel and I thank you in private
I even told you I even sent you a long letter saying thank you very much for helping me
And then I helped me I bought some food at that time that time that you help me I bought some food of the growth story
I went straight to the maxi in the grocery. That's the maxi growth storage. You see the super see that but
200 bucks to 300 bucks. You gave me that time. I bought food. Just know that I was happy and I was very grateful for that
But you use that against me every every single time that you you got a problem with me or you
We don't we don't agree with something you try to put me down
You call me a beggar and all that that's not true
If we're whoever's listening and I don't believe those lies
That's she uses that against me every time to lie about me to make me look bad
Don't beg anyone for anything. I haven't asked for anything. I've been sometimes starving here in my apartment
You know waiting for weeks without literally that just eating once a day. I don't ask for anything
I don't beg anyone for anything. Okay. I never beg anyone for anything
I simply asked her for her for her help twice. I asked her for her help twice
Okay, and she offered her help once three times in total. Okay, that's it
So stop the stop with those lies. Just come on use something else and stop using those lies against me
But just know that I appreciate the times that you help me. Okay. I am man enough to say that you help me and I appreciate those times
But I didn't think you're gonna use it against me every single time for the past three years for the past two years
I didn't think you're gonna use it against me or else. I would have never asked for your help to begin with
But anyways
You're dismissed JC. It's okay. Have a good life. Enjoy your stream. Enjoy talking to lip tarts
ignorant people enjoy talking to drunks and
people high on drugs and
Not helping. I'm really just you're just enabling them. You're you're you're making their situation worse
You're not really helping them. You're insulting them. You're putting them down
at your own
Expense for a laugh for your little circle of friends of libtards like Angie and Monica. They're so ignorant
They hog your panel every day for hours
It's too bad to see that. You know, you I think you're better than that. You see you're
Supposed to be a better a smarter person that I know you got good in you Jesus. I know you're a good person
Sometimes you can act
Yeah, pretty selfish and immature sometimes with things and you can be pretty like it mean and hateful and like you can be pretty
Heartless with some of the things you say when you tell people to die when you tell people like me and auto and another people that
Go off and die when they're already suicidal and depressed and struggle with depression anxiety
That's not a very smart thing to do
It's not a very good thing to do for people that watch you because you lose credibility in the
You know, I help people that you say that to you. You only make them worse, you know
You're making them more depressed and putting people down, but that's not fair
But it's like I said, that's you you're not perfect and everyone's not perfect
I make mistakes you make mistakes try to change that maybe just a little advice for you JC
Try to change that but I don't wish you any harm. I still once again. I wish you well
You were kind to me sometimes sometimes we laugh together
You were kind to me
But many times you weren't fair to me and you laughed at me and you put me down and you were you unfair with me
But we had our ups and downs and we forgave each other, but
Hopefully you forgive me and I forgive you for stuff whatever, but I never really did anything wrong to you
But whatever wherever you think I did wrong that I hope you forgive me and I forgive you
I don't hold anything against you
And I'm not gonna talk about you either. I try not to talk about you rarely
I don't often often I don't talk to you. I mean, I don't talk about you often
I try to avoid talking about you so don't worry won't talk about you
You probably won't even see me anymore because I'm retiring. I'm done with the chats. I've had enough
It's about enough for me. That's six years of the scrap. It's about time I move on my life
Yeah, you can either choose yeah, well, I told you enough true for like two hours and a half
I said the truth. I think it's going on three hours now. It's ridiculous. It's one for the record
All right, good person. Jen take care your chickens has nice meeting is nice knowing you. I don't know much about you
You seem like a nice person
Turn to Jesus Christ, Jan. Turn to Jesus Christ. Only Jesus Christ can save you.
Everyone's capable of bad behavior that doesn't make us bad people. Yeah, that's true, Jan.
It's better to set a good example though.
But JC has many good things. She has good quality. She has a good heart
She says sometimes like she really goes overboard with what she says. I don't think she means what she says
You know when JC says certain things
I don't think she I find it hard to believe that she actually means that when she tells someone to go and die
I don't think she actually means that I think I give her the benefit of that like the credit
She has a better heart than that
I think she has a better heart that she wouldn't really want someone to go off and die
I mean who would want that you'd have to be a really like heartless person to want that
I don't think JC is like that. I think I JC actually
has a better heart than sometimes she pretends to have or she comes across as having
her defense and giving her the bone for the young. I think Jay-Z is such a good lad. Sometimes she
really talks through her hat sometimes. She says some pretty ridiculous things sometimes.
I think she's a better person now though. She seems to have a better heart than that.
That's where she wouldn't try to put me down with that stuff so much when she helped me a few times
She helped me out if that was a really good thing to do
Really don't know why she had to use that against me for three years now and everyone thinks that that is true
You know, he keeps using that against me once in a while
Well, the people that know me well know that that ain't true
I asked her help twice and she helped me once and I appreciate her help and it was very helpful
And it was very appreciated. I appreciate and she helped me it through a hard time once I
Bought food and I was happy when she helped me and I thanked her personally in private in a private Gmail on panel too. Oh
Yes, I don't mention you JC. Don't worry, and I'm not gonna mention either
I've tried actually did not mention you for a long time. I
Just simply mentioned you when I saw you pop up pop on the chat when you popped up in the chat JC
Then I mentioned you but before then I didn't mention you
And when I do that when I did mention you it wasn't negative. It wasn't bad. I
Do talk about you sometimes. I don't I try to keep it like a neutral. I don't say anything bad against you
Don't worry about it
But you're not gonna see me anymore. Anyways, I'm gonna need to retire
I'm done. I'm done with the chats. I'm moving on
Gotta move forward
I'll do other things in my life
Even if that means putting your entire department under federal review
Even if that means even JC even if that means putting your entire panel under federal review, I'm just kidding
That's a little joke. See I can joke GC. Can you take a joke, GC? I can take jokes, you know, I joke around
Think if I wouldn't be able to joke around that'd be really depressed
I'm already depressed, but I've been worse. I wasn't able to take a joke in front of my own life
I'd make fun of my own self sometimes, you know, the lightboats are insurging that
I'm making myself look like a clown a bit sometimes. You know, I know that I know that I realize that
I can laugh at myself a little bit, but I don't I don't cross a line sometimes
I don't certain things I don't do I don't cross certain lines and certain lines and boundaries, Jason
certain lines and boundaries should never cross I
Don't threaten people
Don't wish anyone harm. I don't tell people to die not like you do
I'll do that. That's okay. You done it to me before I forgive you and I hope you don't mean it
Don't wish you any harm. Okay. Once this last time I say it. I don't wish any harm. I wish you well
So go your way and I'll go my way.
Keep streaming to where he wants your life. Hope you're happy live out your retirement and enjoy your retirement
You know, you had a long life JC. You're in your 60s now. I know you've done your earlier
You're not in your late 50s. Come on. I'm not dumb. You haven't been 57 years old for the past six years now
You're maybe 62 to 66. You gotta be 62 to 64
But anyways, enjoy your retirement. My point is enjoy your retirement JC
You live a long life you you struggle when you're young you report now you got money. You're rich. Enjoy your life
Have fun and
Try to set a good example at least and try to be kind of people
Other than that you're good person. I wish you well enjoy your retirement. You see no
No, no hard feelings, you know, no hard feelings. No grudges. No hard feelings. Enjoy your life
Have fun have fun with your retirement
Joy your money enjoy your fancy lifestyle
Enjoy it. It's not everyone can enjoy what you enjoy
How everyone has that kind of money that kind of luxury, you know, I
Don't I don't even watch Alex Jones X I don't watch Alex Jones. You got me wrong on that
I used to watch him before then I found out he works for the globalists. I found out he's a he's managed opposition
I don't watch him
I only watch a few of his videos. I don't believe it. Trust that guy. I don't trust that guy
That guy's working that guy's taking orders from the globalists and in some degree in a certain degree
So I don't watch Alice Jones. Just so you know just for the record
Well
No, she didn't kill her husband we talking about that's not true man, you know sometimes people lie about JC
That ain't fair man. Sometimes people go too far
Jaycee loved her husband. I believe she loved her husband and they loved each other and it was it's a hard time what she got
She got through that thing. She went through like a year or two ago when she lost her husband
That's a hard time and shouldn't be making fun of that GT man. That ain't fair. They're right now
You say you go you go too far as I'm says GT you cross the line man like I was saying there's certain things you shouldn't do
You shouldn't cross the line you need the sermon either you shouldn't cross the certain boundaries, man
She loved her husband man, and she I really believe they had a good marriage and they loved each other man
That's what I believe. I don't think that she
Come on, then who who wants to lose their their spouse man when they lived years and maybe they had a good life together
Come on. They loved each other man. Don't be silly. Oh
You're ridiculous JT
Gotta be fair now
Don't do fire sometimes JT hanging right now sir a young kid you got no life experience you're a little punk man
Come on JT
Don't be a punk man
Want to joke around and entertain people but I'll go too far man because that ain't right because I'm just gonna come back on you when
Did what you what goes around comes around JT, huh?
You know the same
But you do comes back out to you. I just send out comes back to you one way or another
All right, man, so I think I'm not jealous man. Don't worry. I'm not jealous
I'm happy the rich people are able to be rich and they're happy and they got every luxury
Then they can afford everything in life without needing to worry about it. Well other people have nothing. I'm happy for the rich man
Don't worry. I'm happy for the rich man. Let them be rich. Let the rich be rich, right?
And the poor before the rich get richer the poor get poor. That's okay, man
You know, you know when you're poor it makes you humble man. It humbles a man that humbles a person
It's a humbling experience. It's a humbling experience. I tell you trust me on that. I know it too well
Even when I work man, I worked at eight bucks now. I've never been rich man
I've been poor my entire life and even my my life was such a surgery business
We didn't make much money man. That's what we had to we had to file for bankruptcy
Because that customers some of our fat customers weren't paying their bills, you know, and that puts us in the
in the deficit
We're unable to pay the mortgage and the surgeons and the staff members and the rent and the electricity and the supplies
And the new machine we got the liposuction zapper 8000 state-of-the-art technology
How do you want to pay to machine like that? How do you want to pay that state-of-the-art technology machine?
When the clients don't even pay their bills, huh? How do you expect to pay that tell me?
Another good machine man the liposuction zapper 8000
You think that that machine is cheap man that machine is worth about 40,000 right there man
How do you think we pay for that? We have to take out another like a loan another loan from the bank, you know
We already had the mortgage and the stuff in the red
And this way you have to file for bankruptcy man. It's just too many things to pay
It wasn't making any money the business not enough people
Not enough customers and the customers that didn't always pay their bills man
They put on credit and they are slow to pay their bills and that's what happens, man. This is the fall for bankers
That'll compare bills because of that
All right, reality Nancy was nice to see you good night
Happy enjoyed the show
You're able to watch it
And here for three hours man. It's ridiculous. It's the last time it's the first and last time I go on a panel for three hours talking non-stop
I still can't believe
But I did it my way just like Elvis I did it my way man
It's my way of the highway
Did it my way
You know, I know how to do it the only way to do it I've ever done it. I'm doing what I do I done it my way
What a nice
Who was recording, huh? Who was recording this truthful information that I gave tonight?
They're gonna use it as evidence to try to cause me problems. They're gonna use it for personal
knowledge and why is that information helpful information?
Of course, Dacey, I never asked you for nothing. I don't plan on asking for anything in the future.
I was happy the times you helped me and it was very much appreciated. Very much appreciated.
You help me two times like a two and a half years ago
Appreciate that but I would also appreciate if you would stop mentioning that every time you get a chance to try to put me down if you're not
You could stop using that against me that'd be good
But you know I can eat to use that against me anyways because I'm just about done with the chest
Not gonna be a Johnny anymore, but you never had a reason anyways use that against me. I never like it puts you down
It's only when you start calling me conspiracy theorists that I stood up to you and I told you that you're just ignorant
You're putting me down. You're not being fair. Other than that. I never did nothing wrong to juice. You got to be fair
I even just defended you right now. I defend you when JT said that
That you enjoyed your as your husband dying. I told him that's not true
I said that you loved your husband. You know, I took your side and defend you there
So you don't need to try that
You don't need to say lies about me as things are not true or put me down because I don't do that to you
I just said that you're you're very ignorant and unfair sometimes with certain things like certain subjects, but I'd never like a I
Never made it personal. That's what I mean. Just I never made a person
You're good enough person. You help me out. That's that's more than I can say for many people
You've helped me out more than many people before you help me out when I needed it
When those two times two years ago, but you get over that out. Just move on from that
I don't use stuff against you. Don't use stuff against me. Just it can only be fair. It's only fair, right?
Make it fair make it right JC like that guy like Mike Holmes. He's got a channel
He's got a show. He says make it right. Well, make it right JC. I
Smarten up if you don't want a spanking
It's a big but the spank
Just kidding old joke
Make it easy JC. We'll joke there
a little joke
Yeah, I'm retiring dark you'll never see another guy like me man
You know I'm believing lies and if you like ignorance and
Not dealing with the truth if you don't like dealing with the truth, then you'll be happy because you're never gonna see me again
You'll never hear this much truth and information
This much truthful information. I'll never see that ever again
This was really a unique stream and unique one's in a lifetime thing I think.
Really nice.
Hold on a second, you're about to say goodbye.
Don't be jealous GT. There's no need for your jealousy
Just admit GT that I am the best I'm joking
No, there's no need to be jealous GT. Just learn from my example, man
That's how you run a stream man. That's how you run a panel
That's how you carry a panel for two and a half hours man for three hours or whatever
How much time I've been there?
Why doesn't always need to be like a talking about the sad things of the world and the justices and stuff
I talk about good things. I talk about everything tonight
I talk about having faith in Jesus Christ about the injustice on earth about many things I joked around me
I gave you guys pretty much everything. I think
Else can you get there's other things good talk about the things I
Made it more like I know I could have made less depressing in a bit
Gonna joke around more, but I just want to be serious. I got into a mood where I want to talk about serious things man
I just decide to talk about some serious things in case some people didn't know just for the for the record for some people
They didn't get a chance to hear it yet. You're the truth about the injustice on earth
That's okay. Usually I don't like I don't like talking about this. You know, I to be honest guys
I rarely talk about those things anymore like it
I'll talk about those things is it's depressing too for me
It makes it depressing to talk about like that the injustice and the unfair things on life
I mean the injustice and the unfair things on earth and
These terrible crimes against humanity. They're doing to us. I don't like it either man
I'd rather be talking about funny things and joking around. I'd rather be talking about life. I'm sure there's or something else to be honest
But I was serious I did serious when I was talking about those things and
Just try to help you a little bit of a try to give a good positive message about
Having open faith in Jesus Christ and having faith in Jesus Christ and hope and charity faith open charity those three things
You got those three things man. You're a good person. You're doing very good
You ought to do that. You ought to try to hold on to faith hope and charity those three things you do those things man
You can have peace of mind and you will be saved man. Go to a good place
The next life you got faith open charity. That's what it comes down to man. You're human you can't you can't buy that and there's no
Yeah
When he can't buy the peace peace of mind that comes from being the command center
Following the Lord's example and doing the right things man. Well, following the Savior's example
Following the Savior's perfect example. There's no peace. There's no money that can buy that. That's that's true happiness
That's true peace of mind
Sometimes you got to talk about these things man. He got to preach a bit of truth
Man, he got to preach the gospel Jesus Christ and once in a while
Yeah, you know life's not a joke guys
I know joke around every day on these panels and these streams but once in a while you got to be serious guys
It was only good for everyone to hear the truth once in a while and I told the truth one I
Provided that truth tonight a bit of the joking around sometimes
No wish anyone any harm once again, man. Not one person. I don't wish one person in that that side chat or anyone
I don't wish anyone any harm
Wish every one of you the guys anyway every one of you people the best
Hold anything against anyone and I forgive any of everyone that's ever wronged me by the way
I just wish they'd smart now, but I still forgive them. I forgive people and I'll hold any gorgeous
No hard feelings. Oh for the record
I'd be a man enough to do that
He's a man who do that with a good heart a man with a good heart a good man a real man
I was a with a good heart to do that
Dick's I've been talking for hours on the panel. It was dark at night now. It's light
Yeah, that's my captain. Yeah, she's hungry. It's time for me to feed her.
I'm gonna close it out with that, and I'm gonna leave you guys just showing you my captain. I'm out of here.
Yeah, there's birds outside at this time early in the morning
She likes to look through the window she loves looking at the birds in the morning
That's her
Yeah, that's my apartment there
As you can see, I got plenty of space
Say I got to be grateful right? I got my own apartment. I got a cat
And my lovely cat I love I
Can't complain. I really can't complain some people don't even go to an apartment. I got a reason to live
Yeah
Get the things to live for them things aren't perfect. I got back pain every day. I got depressed and I struggle in anxiety
It's really depressed sometimes, but I couldn't I can't complain
It could be worse. It could be far worse and some of the people get a worse
That's one of my rooms I got two rooms, that's one room
That's the other
Apple my air conditioning there now because it's was hot recently and I had to set up my air conditioning there
I don't like it. I don't got like GC. I don't got the central air like JC. She has a big air conditioner
Living the high life JC is living the high life with a air conditioner with a central air conditioner in a big house
They're big fancy house. Oh
Just kidding. I'm just getting JC. Don't worry about it. I'll take it the wrong way
Here dude, you are living the high life JC when some of us had a small air conditioning like that
Some of us got a small air conditioning like that. I tell you
Yeah
That's what it looks like put a fan next to my bed because it's so hot you know I put the fan right next to my bed
This is so hot
But now it's okay for now, but it's gonna be a heat wave next week apparently
That's a big week big heat wave coming up. It's gonna be hot again next week
To be a hot one
It'd be hot the entire summer
I'm calling for a very hot summer a long-term forecast
That's it guys you've seen enough
All right guys you've seen enough they've seen enough they don't deserve anymore
I'm turning off the camera now take a bite of my cat with my leaf
You see a bite of my cat have turned off the camera now I've shown you enough
Let's read the the comments one last time in the side chat. Let's see what people are saying now
That's right Mickey
There's always someone worse off than you. I mean look at the J turd
You can be crossed-eyed and into a man drinking offering. Yeah, that's right. Yeah, JT's a bit weird
It's kind of weird. He's that changes ways. No, he needs to repent
He's the smart enough, huh?
Maybe needs a liposuction surgery procedure as well and maybe take off 10 pounds of fat
That might not hurt a man might open
Those leftovers oh
Yeah, you know my friend brought me some of our spaghetti sauce at your time
He brought me a big a big bowl of spaghetti spaghetti sauce that he made he made a really nice spaghetti sauce
He brought me that yesterday actually you want to see it?
You showed it to you
Spaghetti sauce, big big big bowl of spaghetti sauce. It's really good. It's gonna make a nice spaghetti
experience us.
You know, I charged my phone on like a 20 minutes ago got up to 18% I'm right back down 8%
And need to charge it go to bed and charge it
completely
Charge my phone when I go to bed
I've already given a tour of my apartment talk a few times on Jesus panel. I've given a tour of my apartment
About one last
That's the washroom the washing and dry machine. I put a fan there when it's hot
Right here and I'm trying to sink
That's my living room
I got lots of space, you know, that's that's not the problem
I got space. I got so much space. I don't know what to do with
Oh, I thought about renting my room before but I'm not gonna rent it
I'm gonna stay alone. I want to keep living alone in my home
It's not fun to live with someone putting up with someone to really be alone
Even if it cost me a fortune it's cost me 1,100 books that they pay for this apartment for the for the rent and the electricity
Electricity the internet and the apartment cost me 1,100 dollars together in total
still though it's better than
Needing to live with someone some people they got to rent a room
I used to rent a room with people live with people I didn't want to live with people aren't clean
You know, I'm a clean guy like I like things clean in the washroom
Plus, you don't need to worry about other people getting in the way you want to use the washroom
I take a shower take a bath for a long time
You know my cat goes there in the window there. She looks outside. She's got four different rooms for different windows
She got the
The living room uh, patio, there's a window right there
There's another window in my room that she can go there. See that room there? There's a window there in the backyard
And there's got now she looks up through that
You like it
pretty nice it's a nice backyard you know it's pretty good this has got four windows by cap
she goes everywhere
she jumps onto the fridge
She's got a good life, huh?
You got a very good life my cat actually got a better life than me my cat
Not depressed. She always has food like you want to see the proof. She always has food. Look. I got a whole bag of food just for her
Got a whole bag of food for just for her right there
Treats right here
Special treats little treats there
briskeys treats
bag of cat food
spare bag of cat food a
spare toilet paper
I don't got much for me. That's what I got for me, but don't worry my cat always eats my cat never misses
Never misses a meal sheets with me. She eats it when I cook meat
My cat eats at least twice a day. She's got water. It's got two water bowls
Doesn't miss out on anything man
Don't worry about that. I'll go around maybe poor but my cat eats man
My cat eats every day and it's twice a day my cat. She's got love and she's got attention
I think they're loving affection every day
Here we love an affection and
Clean her litter box. Look at the litter box. Yeah, it's clean. It's clean the way blacks. I see something
She plays with her ball I throw her ball
It's got her toys
Having fun she's got a good life my cat don't worry my cat is very happy. She's much happier than me to be honest
I'll tell you that
Back to bed man. Go back to bed Vader Mario. Come on Mario Cruz go back to bed man
He needs to get some rest. You're talking nonsense
And you've also been transferred to personnel Mario you missed a very good show man
You might want to rewind the chat the past two and a half hours. You see what I'm cooking
Talking about some truth and some good stuff
really good stuff
He doesn't delete the stream. He can rewind and watch
No, my cat doesn't have urinary tract problems. My cat's perfectly healthy
And she's two years old as a matter of fact me my cat are gonna celebrate our two-year anniversary together
I got her on July 3rd in 2023. I adopted her when she was four months
That's their two-year anniversary coming up next week. We've been together for two years, man
We're two good years with her on my cat. I love her. I'm really happy that I found her
No, Jesus Christ brought this cat into my life after I lost my other cat
Was heartbroken man. I didn't think I was ever gonna have a cat again. I found her. That's just goes to show you man
It's not by chance. I think the Lord put her put my cat in my life
This new cat in my life to give me company and a friend and like a child
You know to take care of it. She gives me a reason to live to be honest
It gives me a reason to live and I love her
I'm not going outside man. I'm about to go to bed here
Keep saying it. I'm gonna get off the panel. I gotta get off. I'm at 6% battery and I gotta go to bed. It's it's 8 30 here 8 30 a.m
It's enough man. I mean once I get out of the panel the stream is over
I've been trying to carry this panel for and trying to carry the panel for the past
Three hours three and a half hours
It's time I get off the panel. I'm gonna plug it in right now
You're my charger five percent four percent better. Good grief, man
Back down to four percent. It's a good thing. I put
Yeah, I gotta I gotta get off that panel man, it's it's enough what else can I say I said everything, huh?
There's nothing much to talk about anymore
I just read the side chef a little bit
I don't know since I tell you
Huh
No, I'm unhappy for many things JV. I'm not gonna get into it
It's just depression man. I've been struggling with depression for my entire adult life, especially the past 15 years
Especially the past 10 years. I think it's been hard. I
Was happier before
Once again, I
Got good things. I'm not complaining
Could be worse could be could be better could be worse. It's the loneliness and the anxiety and the depression that really gets hard sometimes to be honest
I'm not perfect man never said I wasn't very far from perfect
Make mistakes and
Struggle with mental health problems just like anyone else
I'll take medication though, and I'll take nothing I do also I chose to do it on my own I've been
Never took anything for 44 years. I always chose to deal with everything on my own man
I don't play on taking medication now man. I'm living like this forever
Not taking anything hot taking drugs and not taking medication never gonna drink never gonna smoke never gonna do nothing
Stay clean man. Keep my body clean. Keep my mind clean. I don't need to put any poisons in my in my body or in my mind
That's why I don't do drugs. That's why I don't drink. I
Rather stay sober man
It'd be easy to get drunk and and forget about trying to forget my problems
But it's not good because it first of all it tastes bad
I don't like beer and it's not good for your body so I go for your liver and your kidneys
It's not good for your body whatsoever for your vial organs. You can get liver failure kidney failure
A bunch of other problems, it's not good for you doubles your chance of heart attack
Although I wouldn't mind dying the heart attack or a stroke would be fast especially heart attack and be fast
Might hurt a little bit, but it'd be fast, but I don't want to die just yet
I don't like drinking. I never liked it. It's it doesn't it doesn't taste good when I'm on when I'm thirsty
You know like guys I rather drink with red drink some water some clean water. You know some cold water
I mean that cold water
Or some juice you know some nice refreshing juice or some cold water tastes much better than a beard
I'll just think your alcohol or whatever. I don't like I don't drink wine. I don't drink beer
I don't like it just doesn't taste good. I never liked it
Was never into it. It was never into drinking or smoking or doing joys and never it was never even a temptation not even close
Me my bow was mental health problems in my entire life to be honest
I'm tempted with other things, but not with alcohol and joys and there was tempted by that
Of course JT I did awesome. It was awesome
It was a good night, man
It was nice seeing everyone it was nice seeing the people in the chat
Just a few haters like dark and a few other faggots rather than that as good people some good people there
No, not four hours man, I think it's three hours and a half I think at five o'clock a GT left me on this dream
And it was me, JT and Gotti at like 4 30 a.m. And then everyone left it was just me left on the stream
I think it was at five o'clock
Three hours and a half now
They take my example guys not to brag but do like me guys don't use vulgarity when you guys go on the panel said a good example for others
Try to stop using vulgarity. It just just make that change your life
You're gonna see in your real life. It's gonna be better
It's gonna set a good example of people when you go on the panel and the side chat
But especially in your real life with your family and your friends and at work and everything everywhere you go
Then just clean up your language. There's no need to say the F word use something else replace certain words with other words
That's what I've done
You can say darn or you can say something like crap, you know, but don't be using the effort all the time and other words like that
You don't need to do that. So that's a bad example
You can't feel the spirit of Jesus Christ when you just you talk like that, you know, that's not good man
I know like it might not be a bad person
But that's just not a good language man, and that's not the way Jesus Christ would talk. That's the point
Jesus Christ never used vulgarity man. He used clean language good language
He even says they says use what you're like. What's your thoughts your words and your deeds?
That's what he says in the Bible
And the scripture says watch your thoughts and your words and your deeds set a good example for others because you'll be just for everything
You do everything you think you say and you do we'll be judged by your deeds or our works
Our words or works and our deeds. We're gonna be just for what we do
So set a good example then you have peace of mind you're gonna feel better by yourself
You can be sending an example. That's that's what a real good person would do
I mean, that's what a mature intelligent person would do
Can't go through your entire life using vulgar. I'm not saying that people use vulgar. They're not much. They're not intelligent
I'm not saying that I'm just saying they could do better. You know, there's room for improvement there
There's no need to use vulgarity, man
There's none of that none of that stuff is are putting in the talking about sexual perversions and stuff like guys like Randy
I when I see guys like Randy on a panel and Jesus panel is terrible
He talks he talks about penis. He says he's not gaining. He's talking about penises and he's talking about
Having sex with people like men and women. Come on. He don't talk like that. Yeah, that's not a good example
He's 45 years old and he's talking like he's a kid even kids don't talk like that
That's why I don't get and the guys talking about penises every day for since I've known him for like five years
I seen Randy go on the on Jason's panel talking about penises every day and he says he's not gay
Come on. Everyone knows he's gay when he's talking about gay stuff every day
I mean who talks like that even other people agree with me on that guys like Ziggy and other people say who talk who talks like that
Yeah, and other people come on
You don't talk like that if you're not here if you're 45 years old me
You guys need to smarten up late the guy the guy's holding down a job
Okay, I give him that he works in a car dealership and he's able to hold down a job every day works
Okay, good for him
But other things needs to improve on it see everyone has things to improve on in their life like right now
I'm unemployed. I could be employed. I know I can work on that can be fine a job
But it's hard when you got back problems and other stuff and start to find a job
But Randy he needs to really smart enough like it the way he talks and what he does
That's just not right
He needs to look at himself in the mirror and maybe smarten up. Other than that, he does a good thing and he works hard
He sees self
Sustaining you know he supports himself. Okay good good for him. Just needs to clean up his language and clean up his act a little bit
Smarten up. That's that's what I'm saying about Randy
Yeah, I try to be fair. I try to be fair and reasonable. I don't put people down. I don't try that. I don't go too far
I think I'm reasonable. I don't want to brag, but I think I'm fair. I think I'm fair and reasonable about everyone
I'm not looking at what anyone down here. It was never my intention
It's calling it telling it like it isn't
Calling out certain things, you know
The hypocrisy, you know the double standards
Who's Mario Cruz? You know who's Mario Cruz JT? Come on. That's your friend Vader there
It's his real name other than that childish name that he uses that's his real name
Just call him Mario, don't you think this is
He owes it to be called by his real name and why would you want to call him a fake name?
These people call them so fake names. I use my real this you know, Sebastian's my real name
I've used my real name for six years now, man. I've never that's my real name. How you spell it every word every every letter. I
Don't use a fake name. That's that's my real name. I'll put my last name, but I put my first name
That's my real name, man. It's a common French Canadian name here in Canada my province
That's my real name. I don't mess around. I don't need to hide behind a fake name like like people like Tom
People like draw a Wigan so-called draw a Wigan. That's Tom
No, come on
Come on Tom. We know this. That's your name now. Use your real name. It's gonna be silly
You'll actually look better if you use your real name and you won't look a silly head
Come on this ain't get this ain't a kindergarten class. You know this supposed to be talking to adults or
Some people don't act like adults, but you're talking to adults. You might as well use your real name
You're not at school anymore. You're at school. You maybe use a fake name when you're a kid
But come on you're an adult use your real name user be
Smart enough, you know, I mature at your age, you know
Use your real name. Why the games man? Why play nonsense in real life when you go to the road story?
Go to the bank man. You use your real name
Use your real name. You don't use a fake name
Enough of the nonsense man. That's why I find it's ridiculous. Sometimes I just don't like it is
Fake names
Even tiffani uses a real name
Oh, there's tiffani. Uh speaking of the devil
Speaking of uh of tiffani
Speaking of the attention seeking Tiffany. She's there, but Tiffany aren't you supposed to be at work right now? It's it's 8 40 a.m. I'm still live here
I'm still
I've been running the panel for a while now, but I'm about about to leave
Very soon very shortly have been saying that for three hours now, and I can't believe I'm still on the internet
I mean, I'm still alive. You know, I'm still on the panel
It's amazing
But yeah, you're off today, or are you working Tiffany? What's going on there?
If you're working get back to work stop slacking on the job your break time was over 10 minutes ago Tiffany I
Know we were talking about chocolate
Like Homer and the Simpsons once and he went to chocolate land
And then his boss wake them up and he says he said oh Homer says oh we were talking about chocolate
I says that was 10 minutes ago
that was 10 minutes ago your break time was up 10 minutes ago Tiffany get back to work
I'll be sliding on the job
There's some for you to do there's someone spilled a coffee on the floor there in the food department
No, clean that up. Take a mop
Take the mop with some water in it in the bucket some some detergent some Javex or whatever
Clean that stuff up and then
Continue your work
Continue what you were doing
of the
one of the
It's
Very rare doesn't happen often. I
Still can't believe I stayed on this long. I didn't plan on staying this long
I thought I was gonna stay on for maybe half an hour an hour at tops I
Had to plug in my phone and I went down a 4% battery Tiffany
No, I brought down my phone down a 4% battery
I showed everything I talked about everything I talked about many different subjects
I talked about faith and Jesus Christ to talk about what the globalists are doing the crimes against humanity
I even turn on the camera about like 20 minutes ago 10 minutes ago. I showed my cat if you missed it
Showed my apartment a little bit
Talked about many things. I called out the hypocrisy. I even told JC. I forgave her
I may pay I made peace with it with a JC. I don't really forgive
I also forgive you Tiffany for your trespasses against me
I've also forgiven you for your trends your trespasses against me, Tiffany because you wronged me because
Because I took some very good pictures of you Tiffany. I made you look good
And I I made you look more beautiful than you could ever make your own self look beautiful because I took the best screenshots
Made him even more beautiful by doing like a close-up
You're very best pictures or a very flattering pictures of you of when he did some of the various streams of yours
And your various dreams that you had I took some of the best screenshots that you've ever had and
That was for free, but at least you can say it's thanks
They didn't say that
Didn't even give me a thanks nothing no appreciation no gratitude just nine but shattered dreams and empty promises
And on top of it, not even thanking me, then you blocked me.
But I did absolutely nothing but help you.
And help your image and boost your popularity, which you wanted.
Which is the attention that you craved.
Which is exactly what you wanted.
I gave it to you.
I gave it to you on a silver platter.
And how did you thank me?
By doing absolutely nothing but throw me under the bus.
And trying to make me look bad and getting GC to dox me and stuff.
And blocking me. I'm calling you which I don't
plan on calling you often. I just want to call you a few times. They won't and
Stock you chitchat, you know, I can't even do that
You see you don't talk to people. See you only talk to your lip-dart girlfriends. They're your lip-dart women friends
Well, I offered you my friendship Tiffany
And you pulled out my heart and you rip from you rip my heart right out of my
My chest there. It's terrible. That's okay. Don't worry about it. I
Forgive you, and I got over you. I'm no longer in love with you, Tiffany
You are a beautiful woman, and I do wish you the best, but I'm not in love with you anymore. It's over
The friendship is over Tiffany
The honeymoon is over the friendship is over I
Wish for you and Gary to have a nice life together. I have a very beautiful life
Stop giving these strangers so much attention and maybe focus more on Gary
But I trust that you give Gary enough attention, but but sometimes he deserves more attention
He does support you. He does take care of everything. He's a good man that guy
Such a good man that uh, he's impatient with you and flirting with other guys on the internet
That's not right, but oh well, I know you want the attention sometimes you want that attention the wrong way
If he has a husband, yes, of course he has a husband. So it's exactly what I'm saying and Nicole
that's exactly what I'm talking about and
She had a devourer time order her husband and then these internet chats, but I get it
I know I know Tiffany's born and she's a sometimes in a loan of the house and Tiffany. I mean
Gary's gone. He's working and she gets lonely and she craves a bit of attention. So she goes on the chats. I know that
With her channel and everything, but it's too much. I don't just think of these these videos. Yes. Yes, Tiffany
You work out and you lost weight without liposuction surgery
Congratulations on all your success. You look terrific, Tiffany
But there's no need to flaunt it so much, you know
Yes, we know you go to the gym and you work out and now you got big muscles and everything and you try to show off your
Fat arms of yours and your butt and you got less fat on your butt
And your butts in your hips and your thighs and your butt. Yes, you didn't lose a big amount of weight
And congratulations on that. You know, that was very amazing very awesome
You don't need to brag about it every day on the flaunted taking so many pictures. We already know that you're beautiful Tiffany
We really know that we didn't do it. I mean, I told you I even told you you're very beautiful
I told you many times that you're a beautiful woman Tiffany
Get a glass of water here
Drink of water a little fast
But anyways my point Tiffany just a long story short. There's no eat the
The brag about your your stuff and your your beauty and your body and everything. It's not everything is about the body, you know about the
Images I mean, uh, how do you say?
Yeah, what's the word? I'm so tired. I forget the words. You know, I'm tired right now starting to get tired
I don't know what I'm looking for the word I'm looking for but anyways, no need to the superficial, you know, like a material things on your body
You don't need to
It'll be so obsessed with that. No, I look at me. I'm a very good-looking guy
But don't brag about it. I'm such a good-looking guy that I can't even walk down the street without women trying to get up with me
And I get into me on
Fleur with me and stuff and they look at me with their bedroom eyes
I see them looking at me when I look at them. I see them looking at back at me
I can tell they're very impressed and very uh, very charmed, you know, and very uh,
very impressed with this handsome man that they see right in front of him, but
This lasso can't be tamed, you know
I mean this this stallion this stallion rather can't be tamed can't be lassoed
They're trying to lasso this stallion. They're trying to lasso me when I I can't be tamed
You know like I got to run free like a horse right there and running in the field out there in the field
I got to run free. You know, that's what I'm saying to me. No woman can tame me. I
Rather be running free and I'm my own man and I got my freedom and all these women out there trying to
It's very flatter, you don't by the fact that I turned on by my handsome face and body and piercing gaze at them when I look at them with my better eyes, but that's not to be taken the wrong way though.
I'm looking for the right woman one day and if I can find the right warrant I'm gonna get married to her
But if not, I'm gonna stay alone with my cat
Live out my rest of my life alone and die alone if I need to I'm prepared to die alone
I've already attacked if I need to alone in my apartment. I don't care if that's how it has to be then that's how it has to be
So be it
As I'm saying if you don't need to like emphasize so much on physical appearance. Yeah physical appearance. It's not everything
It's what you got in the heart and in the brain. I
Believe that you got a good heart Tiffany, but I question it sometimes, but I believe you got a good heart
But what's going on inside your brain there?
What's going on Tiffany?
Yeah, using that brain very well sometimes are you?
We're talking to these lip darts and you're letting these lip darts influence you in a bad way Tiffany in a negative way
These lip-tart friends of yours Tiffany many of them not awful. I'm seeing some of them really they're a bad influence for you people like
Monica and Angie and other people like that like Randy come on. How do you talk to these idiots?
I mean, don't you find yourself getting dumber by talking to them?
You're not getting any smarter talking to people like that if you want to get smarter talk to people like me Tiffany
You're very you're awfully impressive Tiffany some of the things you do, but to be a real person
You got to show someone you have to show somebody something Tiffany. So how about it Tiffany?
Let's see what you got. Let's see what you got in your brain there
Let's see what kind of integrity you got there. You've got the body now now that you've worked out
And you've lost those pounds without liposuction surgery. It's very impressive. What do you got now in the brain?
You got a soul Tiffany you got a heart that you got a you got a soul you got a conscience
Don't emphasize so much of your your attention and your your
Your priorities don't put so much priorities on your your body Tiffany. That's not everything. I used to be a very uh
I used to be very in shape. You know, I wasn't better shape than before like I said better days
I wasn't really good shape. I had a six pack before when I was young, okay?
About 10 years ago, 15 years ago, I had a six pack and I was in really good shape and now I put on maybe 20 pounds
I need liposuction surgery, but I still got my brain. I still got my heart. I still got my brain
That's what matters. Forget about the body. The body gets older and we get older we get
Who get worse as the years go on but that's not everything that what you got is the most important thing
That's your brain and your heart your mind and your heart
Game knowledge and then stop wasting your time with certain idiots. You're wasting just too much time
It's my old point. I want to say like make a long story short. If you're still listening
Just stop worrying about what people think about you Tiffany
Stop trying to impress them so much with your body and your appearance by showing pictures every day
Going to the gym and stuff like that worry about other stuff
Take care of your dogs where you've focused that energy more in your dogs and your husband that you love you love Gary
You love Titus and your other big dog and your birds your birds a phoenix and the other bird
Whatever you are you're calling on me birds you got whatever take care your animals and and your husband and your own self
And and your real life and forget about the internet so much these these channels
I mean I mean these videos you made on your channel you made so many videos you've been there and you've done that Tiffany
It's time to move on now. It's just like me. I'm retiring from the chats, and I think you should retire too
Just my I'm just my suggestion. I mean, I'm giving some advice
That's just my advice to you you ought to retire and like stop it like at least like do less of it less streams
And forget about what people say about you forget. You're always gonna have haters if you come on
You know that I got haters you got haters everyone's you got everyone's jealous of everyone
There's always people that are not gonna like you and they're gonna like you you can't please everyone
Some people are jealous me some people like me some people are gonna give me hard time
It's you always gonna get that everywhere. That's why I'm walking away from the chest. I'm retiring
you gotta you don't need to go on the
Go live like two or three times a week or whatever and make these videos
Okay, if you want to pass time and you got nothing else to do
Stop obsessing about letting it by stop letting the drama stop chasing after drama and story lines and stuff and stories and nonsense
You don't need that like you really you're wasting it. I'm wasting my time back with these things too. That's why I'm retiring
I want to do other things stop wasting my time
I've been doing this for six years now these chas and these dreams and you've been there too for a long time
If you know, it's a waste of time, right?
You know what ain't real life? You know that this there's dumb people out there. They say dumb things
They some of these chats like some of these people it brings out the worst in them Tiffany
It brings out that like the worst things they what do they got to offer like they got nothing good to offer
This is all Garity and nonsense and talk about sexual debauchery and stuff like that such terrible things like sexual perversions and stuff
You don't need that. That's not helping your soul. That's not helping your spiritual life your spiritual self
And I'm talking you seriously now
You can do better with your time Tiffany. There's better things. You're a good person
You do many good things you take care of your animals
Good on you for that
But you can do other things and waste so much time energy on these chats so much time energy on these these
Are the drama of the chats you can do better things in your life if you don't need that you know
You can do better things than that
But anyways, I do wish you the best
I was a fan of yours before I
Still like this so the stuff you do but
I've gotten over you Tiffany
I've gotten over you, and I wish you the best just so you know
Smarten up Tiffany and I stopped playing into their games, huh?
And start to talk business
Start to talk business Tiffany. You see what I'm cooking
Of course they can't do anything about the panel Tiffany's like is sleeping
He finally has a good guess. He finally has a guess that makes sense a good good guess like me
What would you rather hear Tiffany?
Would you rather hear a nitty like Randy say gay stuff and and dumb crap and gay disgusting crap and talk about nonsense for hours on end?
Do you rather hear that if you're listening right now, Tiffany if you're watching this because you're interested or else you wouldn't be watching
Otherwise, you're just very curious, but I think you like what you hear
But but anyways, I carry the panel for three and a half hours and I was telling truth
But you missed it earlier you ought to you might want to rewind I was talking about the truth and stuff
I'm over the crimes against humanity much of stuff. And anyways, there's so much stuff
I could tell you and I can teach you but I can show you but I don't got hours and I just wasted another few hours doing that
I could take hours telling you about the truth about stuff, but I can't help you Tiffany
You gotta help yourself one day take some time to do a bit of research and find out what's really going on out there
Cuz it's a crazy world. We live in and that about and that's what I'll tell you Tiffany in case I didn't tell you yet
Do the stuff you want to do now because everything's about to collapse
There's gonna be a financial collapse and there's gonna be a food shortage very soon in the near future
That could be in months now. That could be in a year or two or a few months
We're living on borrowed time and when the fan hits when the when the stuff hits the fan as they say when the stuff hits the fan
Tiffany you're gonna see it's gonna affect everyone is gonna be told chaos and
The freedoms and the luxuries we enjoy we're gonna lose it. It's gonna be taken from us and it's really gonna be a mess
It's gonna get worse before it gets better
But you're gonna see it. That's what I'm saying. I'm trying to tell you that uh, enjoy what you can now
What you want now take your vacations enjoy yourself do your bucket list or whatever
The stuff you want to do now for anyone listening because you're not going to get a chance to do it later on
When stuff does hit the fan when things collapse on the society collapse and they the cost chaos and then they declared martial law
they lock everything down and they shut down the economy and
Money's not worth anything anymore when it becomes a digital currency when it turns into a digital currency guys
And there's food chores no more food and then and then everyone's on a digital currency thing and like has points and stuff
It's gonna be terrible. It's it's only gonna get worse. Trust me. You're gonna remember. I told you you're gonna remember
I told you this in a year or two
You see that crazy guy Sebastian wasn't so crazy after all he was right
You see I warned you about it many times and you guys can call me a guy's called me conspiracy theorists for that
You can call me names or you're gonna see I was right sooner or later will happen other people like me to try to warn you
Said the same thing
It's a matter of time. We're living on bar time. We're lucky. It hasn't happened yet
It happened eventually. It's can't keep things can't keep going like this
It's going bad right now in the world. But anyways, enjoy your time Tiffany while you can enjoy your life and stop wasting
That's my point stop wasting so much time with the chats and start living your real life and forget these chats
Like literally maybe walk away from it. You know, I
Want to be all I'll be bold with you here and give you maybe some bold advice delete your channel
Delete everything delete your videos. Just
Just ended you know like and your channel like deleted you know like you you don't need that stuff anymore
Or maybe keep it as a memory, but stop making these these videos about drama nonsense. It's childish. Come on, Tiffany
You're my age, right? You're 43 you're 44
Grow up now. It's time for you to move on with your life
Take care of your animals and take care of your husband and take care of yourself
Forget these chats in this nonsense. It ain't real life
Yes, there's good people and there's some people they talk about serious things
But most of the time is it's pointless childless drama and it's childish and you know it
And it's just as childish as the nonsense and the people do when they're they're young in schools
you know and the schooling and then and then
In the schoolyard, you know, like it's it's it's bullying. It's mostly bullying and nonsense, you know that right?
Nothing's seriously in these chance like 90% of the time people are messing around and they're not serious
And what do they say they say hello to you and they say hello back and you come on you call that me entertainment
Yes, I won't each other and talk about nonsense for hours on that every day over and over every day
That's what I've seen in the past six years. It's the same crap. That's why I say I'm sick of it
It's hard to walk away from it
But you need to walk away from it and do some way your life or do other things move on to other things and forget about this crap
You know, you've wasted how much time with these things. I mean videos if you made you know, which what does it do?
Really? What does it bring in your life? What does it change?
Does that pay your bills and does that the you know, like it you're real happiness
Enjoy how to be with Gary with your husband and with your animals that you love and that goes for anyone
Your real life your family and your friends and these chats
Even a guy like me. I'm alone and I got I got lots of time on my hands right now
But it's still a waste of time. I could be I could be doing better things with my time
I don't need to waste my time. I don't need this. You know need this crap
I should collaborate with Tiffany. We're talking about Jen
Collaboration is like
Yeah, that's a good idea Jen I can offer the life of suction surgery and she can get them toned up in the gym
That's a pretty good idea. Actually that makes sense
Very good observation there Jen
But I don't think so though
Because Jen I recently had to file for bankruptcy
And that 40% discount for the liposuction series only give me available up to July 8th after the independence to a day a week
Special with 60% off the liposuction series
That's gonna be less discount that I'm gonna be able to offer from July 1st to July 8th limited time only though
Limited time offer 60% off your liposuction surgery procedures
for every new client across our private high-end clinics in the USA and Canada
exclusively
for me
That's a very generous offer to you the clients
Then it's over that I'm filing for bankruptcy for good and we're gonna shut down. We're gonna bankrupt. We're gonna file it
While bankruptcy in the unit for clothes everything
We're shutting the operation down and we're gonna need to
Do other stuff. It's gonna close down
Many people are gonna lose their jobs many surgeons and
Technicians gonna lose their jobs. Unfortunately, that's very sad
but
It's a hard decision needs to be made
and me as a the executive director of
Strategy and operations in the Department of liposuction surgery need to make that very hard and difficult decision
To do that
And it wasn't easy. Trust me. I love that. I loved it like my baby my liposuction surgery business and
Work as director of and of strategy and operations. It was
Very very important to me. I loved it. I enjoyed it actually it was a passion
Such a passion it was is about the same a level of passion that I had when I was a
when I was CEO and president of my then company strike force from
2020 to
and that was very hard for me to
To retire from that what I have to
But I did hard work though very hard work and I helped many people to know the truth
I worked hard for Western kind and and
Western civilization for the rights of animals of our animal rights and well-being the well-being and welfare of animals
That's what we concentrate on strike force
and I see one president
And my company I did that after DA
Gave me the company a turnkey operation from the of course because da founded that company
Found of the company strike force and he did the turnkey operation gave it to me
Of course, and I took the leadership and I took the company under different directions that da could never imagine
You can only dream of but da was busy in da's defense and the defense of da
He was very busy and as a with his work as a mailman for delivering the mail
You know as a postal worker for the United States postal office
He was very busy. That's why he handed the company over to me in case you didn't know that's the story behind that
And he was very proud. He has the best decision ever made the night of the company
The new levels of awesomeness and success that could never be imagined and dreamed of previously
Yeah, but anyways, I was proud of that and they're gonna work and I retire from that and just like I'm gonna retire from my life
With such and surge you work and it comes at a time when every man has to retire
From what they love and when they're passionate and yeah, I gotta move on from something else gotta move on to something else
I mean and it was very uh, oh
Yeah, very much
Very much a joy to do that. Yeah
Well, every good thing has to come to an end sometimes on earth
Yeah, but you can't take anything with you though. If you're gonna take the memories with you know the good memories
Is the liposuction surgery clients they come and go you know and people lose fat the pounds come and go fat people
I don't losing weight
Offer their fat bodies are very happy to lose that weight and they feel better after and then boost your self-confidence
But the memories that they last for a lifetime. You know that you cherish that
You got to cherish the memories like you would cherish the cabin in the woods
When you go out in the woods for camping
Kind of like when you go in the woods, you know in the winter time and you can feel that cold breeze
You know through the through the window of your cabin, you know, it's very very refreshing. You know, it's a brisket
Briska wind breeze
Chairs that you know, I can remember you chair some memories of the cabin when you chair some memories for life and
Things you enjoyed doing
No incognito
This person ain't on drugs. I don't do drugs sir. Never did never will
And I'm about to go off I'm about to sign off here about the
Exit I'm about to leave because I'm tired. I've been up for a very long time now been up for
actually since yesterday evening
Since yesterday afternoon actually after I got up for my nap
I've been carrying the panel for four hours now, but it's enough. You know I've done enough
I've provided enough entertainment for one night and for one morning
They don't deserve anymore. They've seen enough. They don't deserve anymore
That's another big person of course under a fake account calling incognito trying to make himself look good or trolling
Of course, there's many trolls out there
But I was the best troll of them all I was the best troll that they've ever seen
Let me understand this Tiffany. Let me get this straight Tiffany one last time before I leave
You're proud. You're you're pleased Tiffany with your current appearance
Yeah, you're pleased your current appearance Tiffany. Is that what you're saying?
My good woman my good lady
You're the fattest thing I've ever seen
And I've been on Safari
The fattest thing I've ever seen Tiffany and I've been on Safari
Now I'm just kidding
I'm just kidding. I'm pulling your leg. That was from the Simpsons. That's mr. Burns
That was in the early 90s. He was talking to Marge. Okay, if you want to know where that came from that's I got that from that I
Got that material from that. I didn't make it up. I took it from mr. Burns, okay
The fattest thing I've ever seen I've been on Safari. That's from mr. Burns for the record
I'm not that depressed
You didn't give up your
Yeah, yeah
I'll never give this chance again, huh? I wonder whether I wonder what a psyche's gonna say about that
He maybe he's gonna be happy. I carry this panel. It's if anything is gonna bring in viewers, man
I made him popular. I'm helping him actually it's good for a stream. It's it's a different take
You know, it's a different kind of thing, you know that he's providing usually he usually provides a different kind of thing
but
I was able to find some different material and provide something different that he wasn't able to offer while I offered it to him for free
I gave it to him on a silver platter on a silver platter, man of gold. I gave it to him
As a token of my generosity to him and it was play it was my pleasure, man
The pleasure was all mine. It was mine. It was my pleasure to be honest
Now it's time for me to
To call it a night unfortunately to call it a day
There's been a very long day very long night. I'm gonna need to say goodbye though. It's good things come to an end
Tiffany has a known liar who cheats on her husband that may be so JT, but that's not for you to judge her
She needs to repent man needs to change her ways man in the end it comes down to her man
She's the one that needs to live with that if that's true
But no, it's perfect. Everyone makes mistakes
She's a good girl, but she's in place. She's easily influenced by a she's easily easily negatively influenced by the wrong people
I noticed that she surrounds herself with lip tars and I pointed that out earlier
I said that to where I said stop hanging around these lip tarts and talking to so many dumb lip tars like Angie and Monica
She's wasting her time literally with them
There it's it's ridiculous, man
You put a bunch of dumb people together and they become even dumber
But you'd separate those dumb people and they get a bit smarter and they start thinking they're using their brains a bit more
You know it's that that's one of the reasons why I'm smart man
I'm usually alone and I operate alone man, and I never take anyone with me and I go on my missions alone man
I take no prisoners man. If you see what I'm cooking if you see what I mean when I'm talking about I operate alone
Man, it's a one operation. It's a one. It's a one-man operation guys
It's a one-man operation
I'm running on I'm running on every cylinder every cylinder is running man. It's like a smooth operation
It's a well-oiled machine so to speak well-oiled machine guys running on a on every cylinder
Yeah, just like a machine in the factory man
Very well maintained very well oiled
Yeah, although I don't use any oil of the well-oiled machine
I don't smoke any crack a savage oil a savage ass
Savage owl. I mean, yeah savage owl. I don't smoke any crack man. I don't do any drugs
I'm just getting a bit tired now. Maybe I'm seeing nonsense here. Maybe I'm talking a bit too much
I'm getting a bit of tired here now starting to feel it. I'm starting to feel the
Starting to feel the drowsiness here. I haven't slept for like a day here
Been carrying the bell on my back man for four hours, man. I like to see you do that. I like to see you try that man
Yeah, punk I
Like to see you try that
What are you gonna do build your own little casino in your little treehouse, I'd like to see that
Yeah, no credibility, huh? That's right, JT
Their animals are right
But fear not
They won't get too far
Not while I'm nibbling at their heels
You know Santa
Some things are very sad, you know some tragedy some of the crimes are tragic and very sad
But they're less sadding to me
Because I've got yet to meet a kidnapper that I could not outwit
Hell yeah, Jason says you're the best. Yeah, he sounds like a smart man. I'd like to meet him some day
Didn't he send you here?
Yes, exactly
It's another one liner that's another little line from a movie there
Which movie I'll tell you the movie called Harry Crumb
1989 with John Candy. No, John Candy was a very good actor guys. It's a Canadian actor. He's a pride of Canada
He was a pride of Canada, I tell you
He was one of the best comedians we ever had in Canada if not the best
He was a very good man a very funny guy
Almost as funny as me. No, he was funny way fun
It's luster's coat it's elegant stride it was the pride of an entire village
Yes, Tiffany, that's right. You don't lie and you've never touched another man. I never will. Oh, that's very good, Tiffany
I'm proud of you. That's very good
Gary deserves it. He deserves your unconditional love
The lucky guy
He's a very lucky guy as a matter of fact
If I may say so
Well done, Tiffany
outstanding
Outstanding Tiffany
You don't know anything about it Vader
Mario you puck
We all go through hard times man when we lose the loved ones we will when we lose someone we love a loved one an animal
Animals are our children man. We don't got any children of our own these animals or these pets are our children as Tiffany
She knows that
These these animals of ours there are our pets there are children man. They're like our kids
I don't think you know anything about that man. You live in your mother's house Vader
Mario Cruz you live in your mother's house, man. Look at you, man. You're a little punk man
You're not even a man. You're a kid. You still live with your mom. How old are you Vader?
How old are you Mario? You're like a 38 or 40 and you live with your mom
Come on. You live in your mom's house
I don't just try being a real man like me or someone like Tiffany that lives alone and they made a life, you know that
Take care of animals. Take care of something. Well, you don't even take care of your own mother man
Watch it. Maybe get a cat man. Take care of a cat. I don't think you can love a cat
You don't seem to have too much love in your heart there Vader
Why am I calling you they I'm gonna call you Mario man enough of this Vader and another this crap enough calling you dumb
Childless names. I'm gonna call you Mario cruise you punk
You're gonna address me a sir. You're gonna address me as mr. Sebastian or sir from now on you little punk
What do you think of that?
the
You gotta do like me if you want to impress the women then I know you're trying to press the chicks out there Mario
But you're not doing well, man. You're you're failing miserably. Come on. I can see it
It's obvious and I had to block you because it is your nonsense and your utter
lack of
Competence and you're not sense man. You're childish ways. You're very incompetent man
I wouldn't even hire you for it to work in my company. Be honest
You wouldn't even be wiping the the toilets man. You want to be working a sanitary
Sanitation manager or a janitor in my company man to be honest. I wouldn't hire you. I wouldn't employ someone like you. I
Don't know. What can you do Vader? What kind of skills you got? What can you do?
Have you ever worked? Have you ever had a job in your life Vader? Have you had a job in your life Mario?
Have you ever had a girlfriend?
Do you know what it's like to love a woman, man? Have you ever really loved a woman like bright Adams?
Let me ask you Vader. Have you ever really loved a woman?
So tell me Vader tell me have you ever really really really ever loved a woman? Oh
But come on seriously man, yeah, it's not impressive and it's it's bad man. It's embarrassing come on
the
You don't bother me man. Oh, I got peace man. I gave my cat a good life for 16 long years
Me and my cat live together my my last cat. I love that cat more than life itself
I still got memories of my cat now. I got another beautiful cat. I love her man. She's a child
She's my child. She's the love of my life
I don't know if you'll ever have that you'll ever be able to love us someone like that like I love my cat before
Probably never man because maybe you got an empty heart. Not me man
Don't be trying to troll me about my cat man. That's uh, that's that's very cowardly man of you man
That shows how desperate you are man
You're not a serious person man
I know it in person you wouldn't be talking to someone like that on the street because you get knocked out for that
But not me man. I forgive you
But you're gonna do that to the wrong person one day and really get knocked out there really get knocked out Mario
So be careful man. I worry for your safety. I worry for your well-being too
So smart enough Mario
All right, now you're dismissed man. I'll move on to someone else now
How's it going Dougie
Doug D. Good good meeting you good to meet you. I saw you in the chat at the other time
You were making some good points man. You were bringing up some good points
Pleasure to meet you sir
Yeah, I'm having the time of my life roasting people dark target faggot
No target. I don't know why you gave me a hard time man. If you got to know me in life, you'd see I'm a really cool guy
I'm a very cool guy man. I'm cool as a I'm cool as a cold glass of water in the summer, man
Really cool, man right out of the freezer right out of the fridge. You know, you know what I mean?
I'm a cool cat. I'm a cool cat. I'm a cool client. I'm a cool customer, man
I stay cool here my air conditioner my family gets really hot
See what I mean
But you shouldn't have tried to troll me so much man in JC stream before man, but
I once again I forgive you to because I forgive people that wrong me. I've forgiven your trespasses against me
Which had a smart enough Tark you punk?
That's that's what I had to say about that
Yeah, panel guest rules no hate no hate speech no threats no doxing no slander no nudity no spamming in chat
Yep, I haven't done any of that. I've been respecting those rules and abiding by those rules
Yeah, that's right. No doxing. Well doxing, you know, that's a dumb word. That's a childish word
I like to call people by their real names, you know, like Mario Vader. I call by his real name. His name is Mario
There's a little punk. That's looking for attention
He's looking at
No, I was trying to write my coattails and he's a bit jealous of me
Well, he's not gonna get any
Any good attention out of doing that
That's why I had to tell him I had to put him in his place. You know, I had to I had to correct him, you know
Just like that guy in the shining, you know, remember that shining in the movie when Jack Nicholson
The guy he was talking to him in the in the washroom in the bathroom there
And he said when his children got out of line with them his children got out of line with him
He corrected them and when his wife tried to stop him from doing his duty as a father
He corrected her
My children got out of line when I corrected them
and when my wife tried to stop me from doing my duty as a father I corrected her
Well, that's what I did. I corrected Mario
Sometimes these little punks need to be corrected need to be taught a lesson
Need to be corrected, you know
Nothing personal, but they try to make it personal with me. You see what he said about me, man
You see what he tried to he tried to hurt my feelings, but it didn't work man
Because I'm a bit smarter than he thinks and he gives me credit for
He gave me a he did try to do a low hit. You know, like he was talking about my last cat. You know, it's terrible
Love that cat anyway, so he's low-punk. He doesn't doesn't affect me. I laugh it off
I'm at peace myth. I love 60 only 16 long years of that guy. I love that cat
We had a long life and I keep telling myself we got many good memories
And I'm gonna see my cat again one day in heaven one day
I'll be in heaven with my dog and my two cats that I loved
And that's the truth man
That's the real scoop. That's a real thing. That's a real a thing man. It's a real story, you know, I
Believe that that one day I'll see my animals. I love one day by endure this life on earth and I live a good life
No, let Jesus Christ will save me and I'll see my animals one day in heaven
Go to a good place man
Do good works on earth man. It's your works that save you
We'll be judged by our works. We'll be judged by everything we say by our thoughts or words in our deeds
Everything you say and do Mario will be held against you will be used against you men will be will come back to you over
The word of restoration
We're fully condemned to the sinner and justify them not at all not whatsoever. I
Can tell you this Justin I mean I can tell you this Mario
You've got the right to remain silent
You you're under arrest Vader at this time at this time are you actually under arrest?
I like to read your rights. You've got the right to remain silent
You've got the right to an attorney and anything you say will be held against you in a court of law
If you cannot provide an attorney one
Attorney will provide for you Mario an attorney will provide you be provided to you as at no additional cost
But if you cannot afford an attorney one will be provided to you if you refuse to
Have an attorney you can represent yourself as well in court defending your case
At this time you'll need to be taken into custody and taken down to the police station for finger for fingerprinting a Mario
You need to take your finger pick your fingerprints in your picture
Again make a file, you know criminal file criminal charges, you know, gotta make a file get open a file against you
Putting in the database, you know the police database
But maybe you already have a criminal file though. Maybe you're you're familiar with that
Nonetheless, you're being taken into custody right now
You're under arrest right now Vader this time you're gonna be taking the police station there for further questioning
And you're gonna be detained for eight hours until you sober up until you sober up Vader
You'll be detained. No, you'll be released with a promise to the period court later on at a further date
That'll give you
Yeah, he's certainly paying attention. Yeah, he's paying attention me Nicole
The gems I didn't see gems guys. I don't look at the chat often
I've been trying to look at the chat, but I've been saying a bunch of stuff. Oh
There's nothing about soft about crying about God first of all I wasn't crying about my cat
I was talking about my cat you've never seen me cry in the panel
I've never cried but even a man when you cries I cried many times in my personal life when I'm alone
I never cry in a panel, but I've cried many times alone man, and then there's nothing wrong with that Vader
There's nothing wrong with that Mario when you cry that that's a real man cries is when you cry you got a heart
A man that doesn't cry doesn't have a heart man
When you cry that shows you have empathy it shows you have love in your heart for for others for the ones you've lost
That's that's a real man Vader. That's that's real talk man. If you want to talk about real things. That's
That's real talk man
That's the truth a real man cries about things that they love not in a
Not in a soft way like you see her in a childish way, but alone like yeah, I hold back the tears man
Sometimes I don't talk about I don't cry for anything. I got my pride. Don't worry about that. Don't get me wrong
I got my pride man. I'm very actually I should swallow my prize sometimes
Don't let anyone see me from the kind of person that's gonna go off and die alone in the woods
I don't like a dog. You don't want to die when a dog's injured or an animal's injured. They go and die off alone
That's my style man. I go and die off alone. I'm not gonna tell you that I'm dying like I'm not gonna tell you that I'm hurt
I'm hurting bad man. I usually don't say it like I may say I'm depressed and stuff and I feel bad
And I don't feel good, but you don't know how bad I feel man. I'm not gonna tell you that
I ain't soft like he's maybe you're soft man, and you don't even got the heart to love an animal man
That doesn't make you a man. You're not a man. You're still a little boy Mario Vader
You're still a little boy, man, and he can't even use your real name
That's besides the point man. You're even if you use your real name, you're still not a real man
You're not a real man like me or other people even Tiffany's more a real man than you man. She loves animals
She has a heart
People that they can cry and further animals that they love when they lose their animals man that shows they have a heart
I wasn't crying on a panel so stop saying that man again get it right man and stop trying to troll me
It's very weak your little troll game. You might want to
Step it up and re-examine it
You make yourself look like an idiot there to anyone that's smart anyone that's intelligent that is
But you suck man, you suck you suck nonetheless, man. You're not uh, you're not someone I call a real man
I wouldn't call you a real man Vader. You're a little boy to me man. You live in your mom's house, man
You're really a little boy, man
Yeah, I moved out when I was 18 man try doing that try getting a job when you're 18 and working any books an hour in a factory and
Driving your bike every day to work up a hill up a mountain with a bike in the snowstorms man when snowing outside when it's the blizzard
I was driving my bike in a blizzard. Have you ever done that? Have you ever lifted anything heavy?
Have you ever worked with tools, man?
Have you ever lifted anything heavy that it's so heavy that at the end of the day you're racking and your entire body hurts man
Have you ever had a real job?
Don't think you have I think you did I think every did any of that
You got no experience in life, man. You may be a you're old man. You haven't done nothing with it
What have you done with your life? I don't think getting drunk or getting high on drugs
But if you don't man, I've never done that stuff man. I worked my entire life
But it's just the past few years. I didn't work. I worked my entire life before man
Had everything had a car and a girlfriend and jobs and everything. I've lived it. I've lived the life
I'm retired now, man. I'm living my I'm living my golden years now to be honest
These are my golden years man before the collapse before the apocalypse, you know before everything collapses
I'm trying to enjoy my golden years here, and I'm not really enjoying it too much
I'm bored and I'm and I'm depressed and I struggle with the anxiety and depression
But but I'm living out my golden years
No, what do you do with your life man to try to put people down?
Not a man Vader. You're not a man Mario. I can't respect a guy like you
You suck and you got no respect in my eyes. You got no credibility with me whatsoever. I'd never hire a guy like you
You're the definition of a loser man, yeah, I'm not a loser me. I've done stuff. I've accomplished stuff in my life before man
Every day I still accomplish stuff even if it doesn't seem like I'm doing stuff right now
I still do good things once in a while. I talk to people
But anyways, that's beside the point. But anyways, you're a punk man. You're a punk enough about you, man
You got no credibility stats man. You're and you're wasting your time tuned how much more time you're gonna waste on the chat
So Peter Mario, just try doing some of your life now and try being constructive and doing something good helping people instead of
Acting dumb, you know, you're making yourself look like an idiot to be honest
That's really what's happening here. You're making yourself look like an idiot there
Yeah, he sucks. He sucks. I got it
That's right now, it's me
Fingerpicking thing fingerprints picture and no not a natal problem. You don't even do that at the police station Jim
Just a fingerprints in the picture for the files
And they put it in the computers now
They fingerprint you they take your picture
But uh put the information in the computer then the release you give you a paper
And you got to go back to court like in a later date
It ain't no fun. Trust me on that
That wouldn't bench in the jail cells and then the police station and the police station in a cell
That wouldn't bench is really hard on the back man
You can't sleep and they fun in there and even though the police is offered
He told me that once once I have that one time one of the police station jail. So he says it ain't meant for comfort
I said ain't comfortable and ain't comfortable. He says yeah, well, it's not meant for comfort
It ain't it ain't a hotel. I know you go in there any fun. You want to avoid me
No one any problems with the law you want to avoid that and a fun just for just one night at the police station any fun
Any fun being a put
Hank I was put on you put in the car man
Being taken into custody. There's nothing fun about that. There's nothing funny about that
Yeah
You gotta behave yourself properly you got to conduct yourself properly to avoid problems like that, you know
Gotta avoid problems. That's why I keep a low profile. I know it's better to stay in your apartment not do anything
They go outside and do stuff you shouldn't be doing or being up to no good or selling drugs or whatever getting into trouble
Are going to bars or
Clubs and stuff. That's not good man
You're only looking for trouble where there's alcohol and there's drugs and beer and stuff and alcohol and people are either
And they argue and they fight it's just not good. You're better off staying you alone in your apartment with your cat
You're better off staying alone in your apartment with your cat
And then taking a nap or doing something else or let's just watch and just watching the the wind
Outside just watching the trees or whatever
Staying you better stay in your house and then go outside doing stuff. You shouldn't be doing being up to no good out there
Now go out anymore, I used to go out before I learned that it's not good minutes
It ain't good man. I go out. It's just nothing good about it
Saying good is good to go out but not like at night like in clubs and in bars
There's nothing good about bars man. I went to bars before for many years, and there's nothing good about bars
There's nothing good that gets done in bars. Trust me. It's a bad crowd. It's bad things in there
It's it's alcohol and drugs and gambling. It's it's not good. There's nothing good about bars
There's nothing good about that
Oh everyone knows a certain names like Marguer, that's that's a common knowledge man
Few names like Tom the Tom draw a wig and everyone knows his name his name's Tom
Are you a cruiser? It's ridiculous. I think I said fuck
It's a joke man. He's a joke
That's why people block me and make it sick of his nonsense in this crap. He only sucks man
And maybe he's gay too. I think he's gay. He looks gay forget him. He ain't a real man
He sucks
No, I don't take any meds, man. Never, never took any medication.
44 years old, never took medication.
I don't, I don't take anything for not, not for the pain, not for the mental pain or the physical pain, nothing.
Oh man, I just live a very quiet life a very simple life man right now man my only joy in my life
It's my cat taking care of my cat and just surviving and taking it one day at a time to be honest
I can be honest. It's just taking one day at a time
Taking easy living out my golden years before the collapse before the apocalypse
Before everything collapses before the the stuff hits the fan
You know before the financial collapse and the food shortages before something big happens
You know like I'm just waiting it out because I live my life before man. I've lived it
It's it's over man. It's we're not gonna make it
We're not gonna live another 10 years the way things are going in it
Trust me something big's gonna happen very soon in the next few months or the next few years at worst
At best at best. We got a few years left at best. We got a few years left
Not to not to dash your hopes or anything or not to make you depressed, but that's what's that's the reality
We don't got much time left. We're living on borrowed time
I got much time left man. It's the system is about to collapse everything is about to collapse right before us
And we can't do nothing about it unfortunately because it's a corrupt system
They're cut they're collapsing everything on purpose man. They're collapsing our western nations
There's gonna be food shortages and there's gonna be a financial collapse and once that happens once once there's a financial collapse
And money's not worth anything anymore, and it gets changed to a digital currency
We lose our freedom once we lose our freedom
We got nothing left and then it's gonna be chaos once the chaos starts they're gonna put martial law
Once there's martial law, they're gonna lock people down
They're gonna put people in prison camps and that's the end of our freedom. You understand. That's what it's about
That's the the general picture. I just
Give it to you in a nutshell. That's the general picture of what's we're looking at. That's the outcome. That's what it's going towards
Everything's going towards that right now
As going towards a digital currency, you know, then what's the point man?
You might as well spend your money now and take a vacation now and do all the stuff you want to do now
Do the things you want to do now because you're not gonna get to do later on if you're waiting five to ten years
Forget it then you need to look at the next few months in the next few years and do everything now
Because you're living on borrowed time in case you didn't know you're living on borrowed time and that's not a conspiracy theory
That's that's the reality right now. Look around you. You got the proof and the signs are there the signs and the proof
It's there
Just look man, open your eyes and use your brain. You're gonna see that's what's happening
Yeah, then there man, I've done it
I lived my life and I've done enough man. That's enough man. I'm just waiting
I'm just waiting for the end man. You're gonna see everything's gonna collapse in front of us man
There's nothing we can do about it. It's gonna collapse
The corrupt system man. They're trying to depopulate. They're trying to collapse their
They're collapsing our western nations on purpose. There's nothing we can do about it. So that's that's what's happening
Nothing can do about it, man
Mark my words on this man. You're not gonna see another guest like me. There's not there's only one other guy
I think that was talking to truth like me. That's Harry that there's this one guy called Harry
Does that get something that he's a great guy?
He's the only guy that the other yeah, the only other guy that makes sense that talks the truth and boldness
That's not afraid to say the truth tonight and this morning. I told I told the truth man before earlier
I told the truth that no one else no one else have the courage to say and I told the truth
No one else had that courage to say that say the things that I said
Not gonna see that again, man. Trust me. You're gonna get back to it. Trust me. Don't worry
You're gonna see that your regular
Junkies and people high on drugs and and drunks gonna see the regular dumb people saying nonsense
Every day saying pointless nonsense and pointless dribble every day. Don't worry, man. You're gonna see that
You're never gonna see another guy like me probably ever again
This was a one-time unique thing a one-time happening thing. Yeah
One time occurrence a one-time thing
To enjoy it man because it's not gonna happen again
That's true Tiffany JT and Gotti try to get panels taken down that's right
That's very true. I
Notice that I notice they try to do that
that's right man well maybe they got a boring life Tiffany uh maybe that's why they got nothing
else to do with their lives these guys like JT and Gotti especially JT though he seems to have
nothing going for him that guy too he's a young guy he's got no life experience you know he hasn't
done what you and I've done we've worked well I've worked I know I know I've worked man I've
paid my dues and then some more than anyone 25 years of hard labor I've paid my dues
I'm retired now
I've retired I
Think there's nothing to do with their lives. That's why they're wasting their time and they're trying to take streams down tiffing. That's why
I'm very bored. I look for something to do, right I'm trying to
Trying to cause problems a cousin problems
and
First of all, you need help with getting out of your mother's house, man
Stop living with your mother move out on your own make a man yourself, man
Until then I just can't take you seriously
You got no credibility in my eyes Mario
Mario cruise Vader your joke man here
You're not a man
You're a wimp first of all you're a wimp you're not a man
I'm more special than you Mario. I'm one of a kind
But you Vader are nothing and you know what else you're fired you're fired Vader
Watch out the office right now
Aka the premises immediately or the hounds will be released Smithers released the hounds
Bar you you leave mr. Burns out of this
Yes, Tiffany, you're welcome you're welcome Tiffany the pleasure was all buying the pleasure was mine
Make a left of me the way you used to in Wayland no
What's wrong? It's that awful mr. Burns, isn't it you leave mr. Burns out of this?
You leave mr. Burns out of this Mario
It doesn't concern him
It doesn't concern him it concerns you
It only concerns you Mario
And your cowardly life that you live by living in your mother's house
You've never made a man yourself once Mario he's ain't people take you seriously
at least tiffany lives on her own she has a job she takes care of her animals she's married
i can respect that you know i can admire that i give her the credit for that not like you mario
yeah good idea tiffany block the idiots block them
take care of yourself out there Leonie
All right, lock them
Lock the gates
Remove the stone of shame attach the stone of triumph
Don't attach any stones simply remove the stone of shame I
Got bad news for you Mario you've been banished
from the chat world, and you've been transferred to Personnel.
Let me tell you, I was in Personnel for 10 years. There's nothing funny about that.
There's nothing enjoyable about being a, there's nothing too fun or spectacular
about being down to Personnel. You'll soon find that out. The hard way
the
for as long as it stays up because I've been carrying this panel for the past four hours now CB
for your eyes only for your ears only
never see anything like that ever again because this was my last appearance I retire after this one
I retire on top I may retire
as a winner
I'll go down in history. It's the best the best there is the best there was the best river will be
Never to be re
Never to be duplicated or matched
Never to be done over again by anyone
There's so much comments. I got a scroll down here. There's too many comments in the comments section here
I'm behind on everything. I can't read every comment. I wanted to read everything, but I can't there's just too many comments out there
Yeah, that's right
Let's see here
You think you're better than me don't you
of
the
She's no stranger to the gym. She's no stranger to lifting heavy weights
Very impressive
Pretty impressive for a woman. You don't see too many women do what Tiffany does
But remember remember now looks aren't everything
You need to be strong mentally as much as you are strong physically Tiffany
Sometimes Tiffany in order to win a spiritual battle. You must confront in a physical combat
Sometimes to win a physical combat you must engage in a spiritual battle a mental battle
You must use your brain you need to use your brain
Gonna be smart
You gotta know when to hold them and you gotta know when to fold them
And sometimes folding them is harder than knowing it went to hold them. You see what I'm cooking
You see what I'm talking about, huh if you see what the rock is cooking
And that's the bottom line and that's the bottom line because I said so
Oh, yeah, if you weren't mentally strong
the
Well, he's just like I said, yeah, you gotta stop these chats differently. Honestly, it's wasting. It's a waste of time in your energy
It's wasting your time and energy. He don't need that. You can do better stuff with your time
Maybe you're bored sometimes, but still you can do better stuff. So there's something else you can do, right?
You don't need that
You don't need these strangers that judging you, right? They don't know you just like you judge me. They don't know me
What's the point right? I know it's probably it's providing a bit of entertainment, but really what is it?
What does it bring you the other day?
Other than like uh, you not being bored
Or distracting you temporarily
It doesn't really
Do much it doesn't change much
It doesn't change anything
So I say to myself sometimes
Had a train of thought I forgot if I want to say something. See I'm tired. I got to go to bed
So I'm gonna get off the panel any minute now. I'm getting off the panel. I'm dead tired here. It's 944. I've been up since yesterday
I didn't even go to bed yet
That's right Vicki she had a fueler time she had a fueler fire was spending time with her husband with Gary with Mr.
Gary Duncan
She needs to give him the attention that he rightfully deserves. He rightfully deserves that attention
Why is a good guy is a good guy carry
He's a hard worker. He provides a living for for his girlfriend for his wife. Good man
Good guy
I
Haters fuel your fire, huh?
Maybe it's time that you you turn off a fire and you doused it, you know and you did something else of your time in your life
Yeah, you get dogs because nothing is private
There's nothing good about the chats man. It's it's mostly a
Bad stuff
Really childish when you think of it held that adult sac like that when you think of it
You know, yeah, I joke around but I don't go too far like I was saying early on across the line
But some people they would go way too far and they cross the line like it's so childish when I read some of these comments
That I see in the chats seriously guys in the comment sections when I read this some of your comments
Just saved myself how do the how do adults like a talk like that see if they do it do they act like that in real life?
Or it can't they can't be that dumb
They can't be that childish or immature or dumb like that in real life, right?
They can't be like that in real life. They got to be smarter or more mature than that
More intelligent than that surely surely they can't be that dumb and childish in real life
Do they do that in person in the real life when they go outside and in public?
You know hopefully not because
It's a terrible
depressing society, so
Tiffany's a doctor and she tried to dox me the other time
Everyone's been doxed pretty much
When you're doing the the streams and the chaps is it's part of the game, right?
It ain't fun to be a dox though. I ain't fun to your personal information being put out there any fun. That's for sure
any right
I'm gonna sleep in my bed very soon, man. I'm about to leave here. I'm dead tired
Yeah, that's a good, that's a good question why she hears so much
I think because Gary works and she uh, she wants attention or she's bored man
She's a good girl Tiffany. She's a good person. She takes care of her animals. She loves animals
She's got a good heart. It's just I don't know if she wants attention
She's missing something in her life. She craves a bit of attention. I guess me too. I guess I'm bored sometimes
That's why I go on a chat because it's addictive, right? These chats are addictive these streams
Sometimes they're very boring though, but sometimes it's interesting, but often it's most of the time
It's nonsense, but people they think they look at the chest because they're bored. They don't know what to do with themselves and with their lives
because we didn't have chats before like 10 20 years ago, right before the internet even like
Even 10 15 years ago these chests that didn't exist right? What did people do before that?
They used to go out and do stuff. I did stuff just stuff with their family or their friends. I
Only been chatting for six years, but six years too much my waste is six years of my life with these jets
I don't I still don't know why I
Should have walked away from these chats a long time. Well, that's why I'm retiring now
It's really this really ought to be the last time that anyone sees me like I'm going out on this one
This is the last one
It's gonna be the last panel appearance for me anywhere
This was a probably the last one then but what a way to go out though, huh?
Five hours going on five hours here. That's it. I gotta I gotta get off
Any minute now I'm gonna go off the panel here go to bed any minute now
Yeah, I'm tired. I'm tired of this
Oh, yeah, Tiffany's a doxing machine is a workout machine. It's a sex machine
Oh, I'm just kidding
She does dox though
She's a workout machine at the gym
Is the man-eater
Watch out watch out. I tell you she'll she'll chew you up. You know, she's a man-eater
Watch out boy. She'll she'll chew you up. She's a man-eater
Watch out here. She comes
Watch out boy. So she'll chew you up. She's a man eater like that song
That's all the notes. I think it's 1983 that went
You know all those are a bunch of good songs
You know in case you guys don't know Rod Stewart and he did a bunch of good songs
Some of my perfect personal favorites of Rod Stewart were a passion in 1980 the song passion by Rod Stewart
I was a very good one one of his best songs the guitar in the bass was awesome
You guys ought to listen to that one Rod Stewart passion 1980 check that one out and there's another good song
He made it's called. Uh, what's it called some guys of all the luck
By Ross Stewart in 1984 and then he did a couple other good songs later on in his career like in 1988 this one
One song called the crazy about her that was 1988 by Ross Stewart
and then he did another good song one hit wonder with uh with this guy called uh
I forgot he did a duet with a guy with a some black guy had a duet in 1989
It was called this old heart of mine by Ross Stewart. Then in 1991 he collaborated with uh
with uh
Oh, man, I forget. I think he was a collaborator to a song called the oh, yeah with this this group is four singers
It's called the old Motown records by by Rod Stewart old Motown records
The by the Temptations. Yeah, he collaborated with this group called the Temptations these four black singers
You know Motown they're really good the Temptations
I did a song called a this old hardbinder. There's any
This old Motown records in 1991 that was in 1991. I did a bunch of other good songs
But my personal favorites are the ones I just mentioned
The Rod Stewart, but I'm pretty much more into Phil Collins and Genesis you guys want to know
I was always into Genesis and Phil Collins soul career and then with Genesis
I was a big Phil Collins fans before it's a big Phil Collins fan before and I also enjoy some of Elton John's songs
Many didn't many good songs on John, but but I promise John. He's gay. He's a good guy, but he's gay darn it
That's I can't wrap my mind around that but oh well
It's his business
But Elton John, man, he had talent that he was able to play that piano and sing at the same time
That's a very special talent and not too many people have only guys like Phil Collins can do it Elton John
Did on the piano and on the vocals at the same time and they were even better live sometimes and they were doing
Then on the studio recordings, you know, they were good in the studio recordings
But sometimes they were even better live in some of their concerts that you guys I don't know if you've seen but trust me
So some of the their songs were better live
And I could go on forever then they made a bunch of good songs
There's a bunch of good ours, but they're the best decade for the music a best decade ever was the 80s
That's for sure and then the 70s
You know means to me of the 80s were absolutely the best and then it's the 70s and the early 90s after that
But really the 80s were
Like no other you know that the absolutely the best the best I tell you
You'll never get another decade like the 80s and those those are good times good living you know the best time to be alive
Easy living, you know, and I grew up in the 80s and 90s even the 90s are good, but now today. It's depressing
There's nothing good. It's a very depressing world and I feel bad for the kids today
You know that this generation today of these dumb kids these spoiled kids never got to know to know how good it was before and
How things were before now these these kids are this they got such a dumb mentality and they're spoiled
You know spoiled little brats that never had a
Well, they don't appreciate anything and they got no respect for anyone. They don't got any respect for their elders
You know they suck
Just to say that they don't
They don't know what it's like. You know, they missed it
They missed out on the best we're the last generation the generation next you know
We live them through the 80s and 90s for the last generation to see how good it was to live a really good good life
How it was before
to me everything went downhill after 2005 really after 2005 things started going downhill especially after 2010
I think after 2010 everything everything really sucked really really sucked after that like the last 15 years now
2025 last 15 years since 2010 been the worst for me personally been the worst because been depressing its
I see I see now society's gotten the people again
They get more and more like rude and and disrespectful and then and just miserable and unkind and just just got a dumb mentality about them
Yes, I can't describe it, but it's it's the way that how society has become and it's become the worst, you know
You know, I think y'all John did it so I can says as I can't describe it
It's something about the way you look tonight takes my breath away the way you look tonight. Who sings that one?
I think that's all John
I think it's Elton John he did a bunch of good songs and throughout the 80s in the 70s. Oh
One of the best man one of the best singers ever come out of Britain Elton John Phil Collins
And Rod Stewart, of course those three right out there the best
Yeah, your name is Mario Cruz Mario. I've already talked to you punk, but everyone knows that it's common knowledge by now
Your name's out there everywhere. Mario. Why don't you just admit that's your name and deal with it and embrace your name
Don't you like your name Mario?
Yeah, punk
How would your mother feel if you not being proud of your name? What's wrong with you Mario? Come on
I'll give you a tarot reading Tiffany. What do you think of that? I'll tell you how I'll tell you where your future holds
I'll tell you what the future has in store for you, Tiffany, and I'll do it for you free of cost
I'll give you a reading all right
Yeah, you think so Jim
He's gonna be happy man. He's gonna be proud of me that I carried the panel for five hours Jim. I
Begged to differ. I
Think the contrary to that man. He's gonna he's gonna be happy. I held it down, man
I was his best guess that he have ever had that see that he's ever had in this is a YouTube career
In his time on YouTube and I was the best guess he's ever had not the brag
Not the brag of course, but I held it down, man. I did it for him. I did it for everyone
Hit it for my fans even my haters even the haters out there
And for the people that don't know me I did it for everyone then I did it for the right reasons man
I told the truth and I
Entertain the people for five hours, man. How many people can say they've done that?
Go down in history the Hall of Fame in the chat
As one of the best they all guess ever
Yes, Tiffany, you've done nothing wrong. You've done absolutely nothing wrong, Tiffany
Absolutely nothing
Absolutely gorgeous Tiffany
Remember Tiffany I made you more beautiful than anyone of those with those pictures
No one has ever made you as beautiful as I've made you with those screenshot pictures
No one's ever appreciated your beauty quite like me
There's only two guys that maybe appreciate your beauty. Maybe guys like you like Gary and me really appreciated your beauty
But you're welcome
And I wish you and Gary the best
I'm just keeping it real man, I've been keeping it real for for the entire night
I've always kept it real
My entire life
I'll sell out to the globalists. I don't sell out to anyone. I keep it real on myself every day every day
I'm the same guy
Stand for what I believe in I stand up for my Christian values
I'm a Christian man. I'm a conservative man. I'm a patriotic white Christian. I stand for my country. I love Canada
I love the USA. I love my Western nations
my Western countries men and across Europe
Love my ancestors my culture my identity my heritage my history
I love it. I love animals. I stand for what I believe in man. I
Don't take anything back by the way everything I said I stand by it. I'll take anything back
I said nothing wrong. I stood up for the truth. I
Joked around a bit
But I stand for what I believe in I stand for what I say man. I didn't say I didn't go too far
I can say I didn't go too far and I didn't I didn't cross the line
I never crossed the line
You know I say within the way the reasonable boundaries of good taste you gotta admit that man
You didn't hear me say one swear word. You didn't hear me say one fault one vulgarity
You didn't hear me say one vulgar word in five hours. How many people can say that?
Nobody no one
All right, I'm leaving I'm done I'm out of here
Good advice. I'm out of your house. I've said enough one last check
Yeah, I get to leave sassy
It's a good advice can't take your advice actually
Let's see here
I would have been a good social worker, man. I would have been a good psychologist too a good therapist
Yeah, look at yourself in the mirror mario, maybe that's you that does that not me
The women get turned on by me, man one look at them with my bedroom eyes
My piercing gaze one look at them with my piercing gaze
And they melt like chocolate man right in your hands
They melt like chocolate on a hot day outside
Like a candy bar, you know that you leave like a piece of candy that you leave in the hot sun
They melt man
They've never seen such awesomeness man this this level of awesomeness they've never seen never seen or heard
They're absolutely smitten with my with my handsomeness and my awesomeness there's smitten
Yeah, I'm talking about music. I was talking about the songs earlier. Yeah
That's why that's the time to leave when I'm running out of things to talk about. It's about time. I call it a night
Yeah, he was he was really tired sassy the last time I saw him his eyes were like closing
He was tired. I think around 4 30 in the morning. He was really tired. I think he dosed off. He was sleeping
He's probably gonna get up any minute now actually
He's probably gonna get up pretty soon
That was a pleasure holding down the panel for him. It was my pleasure
It was a ritual was a pleasure a celebration of life. I
Could give Darrell readings heck. Oh, yeah
That's a terrible picture Vicky CB. That's not very polite for you to give the finger like that in that picture
I suggest you change that picture CB or else
You'll be given a spanking. I'll give you a spanking. Don't make me come down there to Alabama there CB. Oh spank you
That's what you need a spanking you I don't I don't condone that I don't encourage that if you given a finger like that in your picture Tiffany
You ought to be ashamed. You ought to be embarrassed come on now CB smart enough you can do better than that
I
Held it down man. I held it down
I'm still here JT. I'm about to leave any minute now any second now the show is over man. The show is done
You may vacate the premises at once
Oh, you change your picture for good very good, Tiffany. I mean very good CP very good
Change your picture, did you oh
Yeah, I've been a good therapist five hours man five hours session like Jim says I just ring down the chaps real fast
Sebastian's therapist needed therapist after his visit. Yeah, I don't think so man
No, no therapists and no psychologists can handle me man. No doctor can handle me. I'm too much man
Not too awesome. I'm too much truth. I'm smarter than them not to be not to brag, but I'm smarter than them. Oh
No, I support women Tiffany. I mean a Vicky if anything I support them
And I'm telling you to smarten up if you don't want to spanking, but I support women none the less though
Don't get me wrong
Don't take it the wrong way don't interpret it the wrong way there CB
Now let's see you come on the panel for five hours CB, let's see if you can do that
Let's see you provide the entertainment and provide the laughs and the giggles and the jokes and the one-liners and
everything and the entertainment
All right, I'm at the bottom of the thing there the
The comments I went through the comment section
Oh, it's not gonna happen again, man, that's maybe the last time I ever go on a panel. Well, that's it. I'm done
Was good talking you guys I
Gotta I gotta go now. I gotta I gotta leave I gotta go like the like the song of Phil Collins
I must be going now. I must be going that was this his CD title of 1982
Phil Collins, I must be going 1982
Yeah, I must be going now guys. I got to call it a night. I got to call it a day
Been a long night
Been a pleasure talking to you
Good night. Be well
Be good be brave be well
All right. Goodbye. Take care. Take care guys
I'm out of here
It's done